Chapter 87: Turn of Events 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Peng!

Garen’s arms stopped in front of the man’s face as if an invisible wall completely blocked his attack. Pieces of broken, transparent debris shot out into the air in a crisp sound like a glass breaking.

Garen’s distorted face was completely red, he made a fierce inhale and, as his muscles instantly swelled up, he grew from 178 cm to over two meters tall. His arms resembled steel pincers, and he clamped his arms with all his might.

"Roar!"

In a cracking sound, the protective screen in front of the man shattered, and the dark blue arms that looked like steel beams scissored towards the man’s neck.

However, a strange thing happened: Garen’s arms went through the man’s neck without touching anything solid.

What he cut through was an illusion, and on the ground not far from here, the man slowly appeared again.

"Brother taught you nothing, did he?" He raised his chin, a trace of disappointment gleamed in his eyes. "I’ve heard reports that you killed a few psychokinetics, and I thought that I would be able to see my brother’s Everlasting Night Stars… but you are just so worthless."

"Who are you calling worthless?!" Garen squinted his eyes, as he took a breath, his body inflated and deflated as if he was a real mammoth with huge lung capacity. His voice was so strong and deep that the words echoed and lingered in the air.

He stood on the empty ground, his body had an unnatural purple-black color.

"Since you are a worthless and incompetent, I will take back what belongs to my brother…" The man reached out his hand and pointed at Garen.

Shoo!

An invisible force crashed down on Garen like a clump of dried glue.

Garen suddenly felt that his whole body was immobilized.

"Trying to chain me up?" A sharp light flashed in his eyes, his arm and elbow stroke to the side with a loud crash.

A crisp crackle resounded, and the man’s expression changed.

"A mortal like you…" He flicked his finger, another invisible force crashed onto Garen.

Vroom!

A giant spherical force field formed within ten meters of Garen.

The sand and weed on the ground, the daffodil seeds floated in the air, dust fell off from the stone walls, and a few dried leaves were blown airborne by the wind.

Everything was frozen and restrained.

Garen was standing in the center of the sphere, his muscles and veins jumped following his heart beat. His heart was frantically pumping blood, and his veins seemed like they were about to explode. His vigorous heart was strongly resisting against the forcefield outside.

Sss…

His skin had tightened from the pressure, and his heart seemed like it was going to blow up. A faint painful feeling came from his left chest, his heart was failing under the influence of the forcefield.

The massive force and pressure restrained his body, he could not even breathe, and his face was gradually turning purple and red.

"It’s over." The man took back his index finger as he slowly walked towards Garen. "Like an insect stuck in an amber, pathetic."

Crackle!

Suddenly, an astounded expression rose on his face. "The Layered Levitation Finger… You broke free?"

Boom!

The forcefield around Garen was completely shattered, he felt his power and strength exploding like a volcano, his sight went black for a second, and a tearing pain came from his muscles.

He lowered his head and saw the necklace hidden in his shirt slowly rising up, floating in front of his face. A line of words emerged on the necklace.

"Ain Gregoria, Third Life Ritual – Protection."

"Everlasting Night Star… It was on you this whole time. I didn’t expect Brother to leave this on you." The man instantly lifted his cloak, revealing his seaweed-like long and dark hair.

His eyes were glued on the necklace, this necklace in the shape of an open book was exactly what he was looking for.

"A treasure like this is such a waste on you." His hand slowly reached out and gripped at Garen.

Peng!

Garen wanted to dodge, but as soon as he took two steps to the side, he felt everything go black as an invisible hand was choking him by the neck and prevented him from breathing.

"The difference in strength is too much!" His heart was mixed with disappointment and rage. "There is still hope!" His hands tightly gripped the invisible hand on his neck, trying to break himself free. His attention turned to the Skill Pane at the bottom of his vision.

Within the Skill Pane, behind the Mammoth Secret Technique, the transparent and blurry word "Explosive" was gradually turning opaque and clear.

He had the feeling that when this Mammoth Secret Technique finally reached the point of "Explosive", his body would have a dramatic change. His strength would increase by a large margin.

"Damn it, come on, faster!" Drops of blood emerged on his face from under his skin from overusing his explosive force.

At this moment, the man in the dark cloak was already standing in front of him, he reached out and grabbed the necklace.

"Everlasting Night Stars, it’s mine now."

Bam!

Suddenly, a dark blue fist fiercely punched his right cheek.

Garen finally broke free of the psychokinetic hand and swung a hard blow.

"Got you!"

He sprinted over, let out a frenzied roar, and kneed the man in the black cloak who was still staggering.

Crackle! The sound of stone rupturing came from the man’s body, he froze bending down.

Garen gave him an uppercut, precisely smashing the location of his heart on the man’s left chest.

"Pathetic…" the man’s voice came from somewhere.

A massive force smashed into the back of Garen’s head.

Pong!

Garen shuddered and froze. His vision went black, and his body felt limp and numb as he lost control of his body.

The man in the dark cloak in front of him vanished, turning into a giant yellow stone.

"A mere Hallucinogenic Force Field… could put you on the brink of insanity?"

The man’s voice came from behind.

"As soon as you met me, you were hallucinated and indulged in the illusions, then you were attacking the rocks like a madman, thinking I was the stone wall."

Garen turned around with all his effort, staring at the man at the original spot he was standing on.

"Who… who are you?"

"Me?" The man chuckled, "My name is Sylphalan. Pitiful mortal… you don’t even have the right to look at me straight. I have been behind you the whole time…"

Garen’s vision blurred, he couldn’t see the man again, and as he turned around, he saw the man standing right behind him, smiling at him with his cold expression.

Bam!

His eyes blurred again, he realized that he was still standing at the original spot, he had not moved an inch, his right fist was on top of his own chest, a strong pain came from his heart.

In a low thud, he felt pain on the back of his head, Garen limped on the ground without any strength, a foot turned his face around to face the sky.

"Your master used to lick my boot and begged me to let you go, why don’t you lick it as well? Maybe I could spare you if my mood got better," the man’s voice came with a glimmer of a smile.

The boot grinded on Garen’s face, and the dirt and the grass mixed with some mud smeared all over his face.

"Roar!" He suddenly pushed himself up and swung his fist at Sylphalan.

Bang!

Garen was sent flying, hitting the stone wall. A few pieces of rubble shattered off the wall and landed on him. He could feel pain from every bone in his body, he was on the verge of collapse.

The man slowly strutted next to him, he could only see a pair of dark gold linen boots.

"Die!" Garen suddenly reached towards the man’s feet.

Bam!

Another foot stomped on his waist, in the sound of a crackle, the impact broke one of his back bones.

"A worthless thing like you, I can’t believe Gregor wasted his time on you, what an idiot."

"Talentless mortals, no matter how hard they try are still just worthless."

Garen could not speak anymore.

"I will die if this goes on!"

He felt himself getting weaker and weaker, he was exhausted and wanted to sleep.

"There’s no other way… Next time I see you, I will kill you!" Garen stared at the blurry silhouette, his mind was calm. He memorized the man’s handsome and cold face in his heart.

He didn’t expect to get outmatched like this, he was almost defenseless! From start to finish, he didn’t even know if he had touched the opponent. He didn’t know if he was a friend or foe and underestimated the gap between their strengths, this was his fault.

Sylphalan… this name was engraved into his heart.

It was strange, he should be angry, but he only felt calm and peaceful. He had a feeling that the opponent did not really want to kill him.

"I have to gamble…" He slowly closed his eyes, not that he could see anything anyway. His muscle started trembling and deflating. Soon he had returned to his normal body size.

He slowly started a technique he had learned from the dojo’s library, it was a simple technique that could allow someone to fake his death.

This was the first time he used it, it was a simple technique, or one could call a trick. This trick was a part of the Mammoth Secret Techniques included in the notebook. One of the predecessors experimented and invented this little trick to save his life.

When he saw this trick that day, he memorized it just in case of a dangerous situation. It was a simple technique that adjusted one’s breathing patterns. But he didn’t expect to put it to use so soon.

He imagined all his strength and blood to relax and rest, and gradually flowed into his brain and heart.

Then he lost consciousness.

Sylphalan raised his head and gazed at the new moon, his foot was still on Garen’s head.

"He’s dead?" He boringly kicked Garen again. "His life was so fragile…"

He snatched Everlasting Night Stars from Garen’s neck and put it on his arms. Sylphalan put on the cloak and hid into the dark night.

Wind gusted by, lifting the hem of his cloak.

He turned to glance at Garen one last time. His expression looked complicated. He turned around and jumped, his shadow disappeared into the forest like a bird.

Right as he left, a blurry silhouette approached Garen.

"Sylphalan… Hehe… you think you could trick everyone?"

Chapter 88: Turn of Events 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After a long while, Garen slowly regained consciousness, everything looked blurry as if something was wrong with his eyes and could barely catch a glimpse of the moonlight with his right eye.

Someone was pulling him by his hair, and he felt like he was being

dragged on the floor.

His vision was too blurry to see anything, after getting knocked unconscious, he felt as if his brain was disconnected with his body.

Sss…

He could vaguely see the dirt and the sand move below his legs.

After a short while.

Whap!

He was thrown into a deep dirt hole.

"Universal nerve damage, 80% bones broken, cardiac rupture, internal bleeding."

"Poor guy, why did you have to piss off people from Immortal Palace. Which one of those crazy bastards isn’t a psycho, yet inhumanly strong?"

An aged voice came from above the dirt hole.

"Young man, if you reincarnate in the next life, try to be a common folk, don’t get involved in these things."

The person exclaimed and started shoveling dirt into the hole.

Garen laid quietly in the hole and felt his whole body being buried slowly. He didn’t need to breathe, but he was paralyzed and could only feel a small part of his head.

"I did it… I tricked him." He waited until he was fully buried and hearing that the person burying him had walked away. He could faintly hear the "hoot, hoot" sounds from owls.

Garen waited a bit more and slowly adjusted his breathing to lift the technique.

Phew…

He puffed out all the gas waste inside his lungs.

His body still felt powerless.

"I should put the saved attribute point to use."

He had one point of attribute unused, in case something like this happened.

His focus landed on Vitality, and after three seconds, the last attribute point was slowly added.

His Vitality went from 1.88 to 2.08

Vroom!

In an instant, Garen felt a hot stream from his brain flowing down his spine into his back. The stream spread into every muscle in his limbs like a wildfire.

The once weak body suddenly regained power. The warmth from his whole body felt comforting.

He lifted his leg and kicked up.

Blam!

The still soft dirt above was kicked open.

Garen quickly dusted off the dirt that covered his body, even though he was seriously injured, he still had enough strength to clean up himself.

Climbing out of the dirt and sitting on the grass, Garen looked around himself.

The dim moonlight shined on the grass, and the shadow of the trees crisscrossed each other on the ground while the night wind stirred up the leaves.

As Garen sat in the dirt and grass, he felt and itch in his nose and ears, he blew his nose hard, and a few ants flew out of his nostrils.

"Shit!"

He quickly found a small branch to clean his ears, a fat worm that looked like a maggot rolled out of his ear.

This worm was stuck on the inside of his ears trying to bite off some of Garen’s flesh, but his skin had been hardened by the Explosive Fist Arts, so the worm could not even bite into the surface. In the end, it was squashed by Garen’s hands.

Sitting on the ground resting, Garen’s body gradually recovered. He felt a little strange, there was a numbing feeling coming from his limbs.

He distinctly remembered that his bones were mostly broken or fractured before he fainted.

Other than a few ribs that were still not healed, they had almost recovered by themselves without the attribute point’s help.

He reached and stroked over some of the bones in his body.

"They are all joined? Is this the effect of Master’s medicine?"

Even though his bones were set, some of them had grown together without aligning correctly, Garen broke them again, and bearing the pain, the hot stream from the attribute point quickly covered the broken bones and started healing.

The strange thing was that his regeneration from the attribute point was usually not this strong, but now, it has grown a lot stronger for some reason. The broken bones had healed together after twenty minutes.

"This has to be the work of that medicine…" Garen was sure the medicine caused the quickened healing. "Looks like Master gave me something incredible…"

After resting for about two hours, the bones had fully grown together. As to his nerves, they were the first to recover.

Garen stood up, dark and bloody sweat oozed out of his skin. It was the congested blood from his internal organs which, after the healing process, discharged from his skin.

"Sylphalan…" he murmured the name. This was his first defeat, and a tragic one, without the help of his master’s medicine and his attribute point, he could still be seriously injured. He might have even suffocated under the ground.

He started thinking about the words from the old man who had buried him.

At that moment, within the technique pane at the bottom of his vision, the words "Explosive" for his Mammoth Secret Technique finally condensed and became opaque.

A strange feeling emerged in his heart. It felt like blood formed a spherical and scorching hot blood ball in the center of his body, the ball radiated hot stream and warmed his body.

Wherever the hot stream touched, brand new power emerged. His recovery speed had returned to normal, and his injuries had mostly healed.

"The Immortal Palace…" Garen clenched his fists as he lowered his head. "I will find you…"

He covered the hole on the ground again and strode out of the forest.

****************

After getting back to his room, it was already late in the night, Garen took a shower in the bathroom and changed into a white training suit.

He found it odd that other disciples were not present.

Garen drank a cup of water on the sofa and relaxed his muscles. He couldn’t deal with Sylphalan at this time, he had to leave the thought in the back of his mind to improve himself, and one day he would be strong enough to go and find him.

Even though he had a new breakthrough with the Explosive Mammoth Secret Technique, thinking about the opponent’s mysterious moves, he still wasn’t sure if he could beat Sylphalan. It was a type of power he had not seen before, and he needed more preparation.

"But at least, I know how the old man died…" He reached in the collar, to his surprise, the necklace was still there, but the letters on it were gone.

He snapped out of the gaze and got a little worried.

"Where did Collin and the others go this late in the night?"

Suddenly he heard some footsteps nearing... a group of men were approaching.

Knock Knock Knock!

"Senior brother, are you there? Have you come back yet?"

"I just heard the door shut, he might be back!"

Garen’s expression turned cold, he rushed over to open the door.

The door cracked open, Collin and Carrie were standing at the door.

Collin had his fist raised, ready to knock again. He froze for a second as he saw Garen opening the door. Then, he could not hold his tear anymore.

"Se… Senior Brother… Someone wounded master!!"

Collin’s voice choked up with tears, Carrie was also crying on the side without a word.

"What!!" Garen’s eyes shook and asked, "Where is Master now!?"

"He is at the tournament platform we used during the day!!"

"Come!" Garen rushed out without closing the door, pulling the two disciples with him.

***********************

Crack!

"Ahhhh!" Simon’s arm got snapped by a young man with short and green hair, the arm was instantly bent backward and slumped on his back.

The young man pushed Simon and kicked him on the ground.

People from different sects surrounded the white platform in the night, the masters of Celestial Star Gate and Crimson Sand Sword sat next to each other, and watched the battle with their brows wrinkled.

Whispers and chitchat noise came from the crowd.

"White Cloud Gate is done," the master of Celestial Star Gate, Rolexia, said. "Fighting Association’s president had historical conflicts with White Cloud Gate’s master. To ask for a battle today, he is taking advantage of White Cloud Gate’s distress."

"There are reasons." The master of Crimson Sand Sword was a handsome man with red hair, he held a glass of wine in his hand without drinking it, appreciating the beauty of the wine’s color through the crystal-clear glass.

He had a faint smile on his face as if nothing mattered to him.

"White Cloud Gate’s senior disciple Rosetta defected, second disciple Farak had gone missing during a mission. If I were the president of Fighting Association, I’d chose to challenge them at first instance as well. Not to mention someone had just challenged the Southern Twelve Gates and injured Fei Baiyun."

"Indeed, when strengths are equal, the deciding factor for victory is the status. Combined with getting challengers previously, the Fighting Association’s President is a wise man."

Rolexia nodded in agreement. "Now that their master was injured, of the two backbones, senior disciple defected, second senior disciple had gone missing, the White Cloud Gate is over. I heard that Rosetta is affiliated with Behemoth Gate."

"I’m not sure, but not only the White Cloud Gate but also the Southern Twelve Gates will all take a toll." Crimson Sand Sword’s master shook his head.

At this time, the green haired man stood with his hands in the back and watched as Simon was carried down.

"So much for the formidable Southern Twelve Gates. The masters can’t beat ours, disciples are all worthless too!"

This had caused commotion and noises around the platform, the disciples of Southern Twelve Gates gathered together, surrounding Fei Baiyun and eleven other masters, some of them were unconscious, some were bleeding, some had their arms broken, they were all injured at different levels.

The disciples hearing what the young man said, though very angry, dared not to speak up. Some other sects had already stepped away from these twelve gates.

"You!"

A red haired man was about to rush onto the platform but was stopped by his companions.

"Don’t! You are no match for him!!"

Fei Baiyun’s face was pale like a sheet of paper, he slumped in a chair, Simon was taking care of him bearing the pain from a broken arm.

"Si.. Simon.. Go! Go find your senior brother… Tell him to get everyone out… out of here!" his head was injured, he held on to the last bit of consciousness and ordered.

"Master! Senior brother can definitely beat that guy!" Simon gritted his teeth and said.

"Those challengers… are not what I’m afraid of… they weren’t heavy handed with us, and we can recover if we get back… the true danger is our enemies!"

Fei Baiyun pushed Simon with his shaky hands. "The Southern Twelve Gates have too many enemies, this is not our territory, we must… get back now!!"

Chapter 89: Adverse Circumstance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You are right Simon, we must go back now and scatter out in different directions!" A disciple of the Southern Twelve Gates answered with a worried expression. "My master told me to bring you a word."

"What is it?" Simon raised his head and urged him to go on.

"Someone might use extreme measures against us! My master warned master Fei to be careful. At this time, it’s every man for himself."

The disciple hurried out after these words, and only then Simon realized the disciple had a black backpack in his hand.

At this moment, Simon felt his mind was chaotic.

Senior Sister Rosetta defected, Second Senior Brother was still missing, and now Master was injured as well. Senior Brother Garen was nowhere to be found either.

"How great would it be if Senior Brother Garen was here!!" He thought to himself.

Suddenly, a few silhouettes walked in from the entrance. Leading the group was a tall and young man with a sturdy build with wine-red eyes, wearing a white martial arts training uniform.

"It’s Senior Brother Garen!"

"Senior Brother Garen is here!"

"Senior Brother Garen!"

The Southern Twelve Gates’ disciples suddenly found someone they could depend on; the surprised cheers gradually spread over the crowd of disciples.

"Master!" Garen immediately saw Fei Baiyun after entering the platform, lying in an armchair. Garen’s expression changed and he rushed to his master’s side.

"Master! How do you feel? Are you hurt?!"

"Get out of here! Take everyone and leave!" Fei Baiyun let out a relieved sigh after finally seeing Garen, his expression relaxed a little.

Garen checked Fei Baiyun’s pulse and breathing. Everything was normal, so he wasn’t seriously injured. He was only having a hard time speaking due to concussion, thus Garen felt relieved.

"Is that who they call the strongest among the Southern Twelve Gates, Senior Brother Garen?" The green-haired young man on the stage shouted abruptly. "Looks like the Southern Twelve Gates had put all of their hopes on you. Do you dare come up and challenge me?"

Garen stood up, glancing at the surrounding crowd.

The Southern Twelve Gates’ disciples all had their eyes on him, along with that Margent he had defeated and a few other masters who were still conscious.

Garen sneered and jittered his shoulders, then jumped onto the stage.

"You are digging your own grave." His expression was ruthless; his eyes became even redder.

He was feeling down from his defeat earlier, so his anger erupted like a volcano.

"You sure talk big!" The green-haired young man mocked and dashed forward, instantly closing in on Garen.

Boom Boom!!

The two traded dozens of blows in seconds; the sound of their fists and elbows clashing filled the platform.

Peng!

The young man’s face turned pale and he stuttered a few steps back while clenching his chest, unable to catch his breath.

Garen suddenly jumped back, and his whole body came to a stop. He stretched his two hands out like he was holding two invisible spheres. A manic and hot stream came out of his body, caused by his rapidly increasing skin temperature.

As his eyes turned increasingly red, his deep breath echoed like the calls of a mammoth. He looked like a suppressed bomb, waiting to explode.

"S***!!" A man with similar green hair sitting below the platform jumped on it and quickly charged toward Garen.

The masters of the other sects all had grim faces.

The masters of Celestial Star Gate and Crimson Sand Sword both leaned forward in shock.

Suddenly, the master of Crimson Sand Sword remembered something.

"That’s…!" If he was already surprised before, now he couldn’t close his mouth.

Kaboom!

A loud noise came from the stage. Along with it came the scattered pieces of someone’s clothes.

Garen’s muscles fiercely inflated and he stood there like a powerful creature from ancient history. His body towering over two meters looked overwhelming. His cold red eyes stared at the green-haired men.

"Master is out to protect his worthless disciple?"

The green-haired man held his unconscious disciple in his arms, but he was knocked back ten steps. His clothes were falling apart. He was out of breath and could not speak a word.

When he opened his mouth to speak, he spurted a mouthful of blood and bent down on the ground.

"Fine, nice, okay. Garen of White Cloud Gate, I’ll remember this, and you will pay for it some day!!" He let out a sad smile and quickly ran into the crowd with his disciple; he was fast like a swallow flying in the rain.

Garen’s glanced around the platform, turned back and jumped off.

"Pack your stuff, we’re getting out of here!"

"Yes! Senior Brother!" Collin and the others answered. One of them supported Simon while Garen scooped up his master, and they all left through the exit. His body had not fully recovered yet, so he couldn’t keep on fighting. Otherwise he would have tried to force the green-haired master and disciple to stay.

Just as they stepped out, a stream of blood came out of Garen’s mouth.

"Senior brother!!" Collin saw this and came up to try to support him, but Garen raised his hand to stop her.

"We must leave now! If the words were true, we are in great danger. This place isn’t safe." Garen picked up his pace and walked on.

The group followed behind him. There were a dozen disciples from other sects behind them as well.

"Why are you following us?" Garen asked with a deep voice.

"We… We are headed for the same direction as you! Could Senior Brother Garen protect us on the way back?" A silver-haired young man stood out and begged. A few disciples behind him were supporting two elders who were unconscious, they were in the same boat with White Cloud Gate.

"Follow up then!" Protecting four or fourteen men was all the same, so Garen thought he might as well help these people in need.

"My name is Rampas, I’m going to represent my gate!" The silver-haired youngster introduced himself.

Garen nodded mutely.

The men packed their belongings and asked Celestial Star Gate if they could borrow their cars. The Celestial Star Gate wanted to stay neutral and out of this mess, so they refused the request.

Inside the parking lot, Garen and the group stood together, staring down at the Celestial Star Gate disciples.

The leader of those disciples was a blue-haired man wearing a black suit. His arms were exposed and a black cross was tattooed on his right arm.

"I’m Tenstar Ni. Master gave us orders. No one is to borrow our cars at this moment, so please leave us." The man crossed his arms and drawled.

"We were invited to join this exchange, but now that we are in trouble you wouldn’t even let us use your cars… you!!" Collin was so mad he couldn’t speak.

"I’m just following orders. It’s not just you guys, the other Southern Twelve Gates are not allowed to borrow our cars either. Senior Brother has already gone to the other side." Tenstar Ni lowered his hands and clenched his fists. "With Senior Brother here, even your masters dare not make a move. Why don’t you give up now, turn around and walk back to where you came?"

The Celestial Star Gate disciples behind him had no expression on their faces. Hearing Tenstar Ni’s words, they all lowered their right hand and started stretching their fingers. A thrilling sensation permeated the air.

Garen stared at Tenstar Ni with his cold eyes. He could feel the opponent’s strength; it was close to his level. If they were to fight right now, the result would be up to fate.

This is also the reason both sides remained humble since the beginning; the strongest of the two groups both feared their opponent. Having improved his power, Garen could now tell the someone’s strength by their slightest movements and the way they acted and talked. He could feel the threat from Tenstar Ni.

"Fine! Very well! Celestial Star Gate, I’ll remember this!" Garen turned around. Even though he was confident in his own strength, this was on Celestial Star Gate’s turf, and thus it wouldn’t be wise to get in conflict with them right now.

More importantly, he was still injured.

"The challenge must be premeditated, it’s a plot against the Southern Twelve Gates!" Simon said while holding his broken arm. "Why are they targeting no one but Southern Twelve Gates! The masters are either injured or passed out. There must be someone trying to overthrow us!"

The group quickly left the parking lot and moved away from the cars.

Tenstar Ni finally felt relieved as he stared at Garen’s back.

"Mastering a third-tier Mammoth Secret Technique to this level …" Remembering the scene on the platform, he murmured. "It must be… That’s definitely…"

Garen and the group were quickly leaving toward the exit.

"It’s not the time to discuss that right now. The Twelve Gates are busy with their own affairs. Collin said that every sect is having significant internal problems, is it true?" Garen asked as he led the way.

"It’s true!" Simon nodded, "It’s obviously a plot against us, and our enemies must have paid off Celestial Star Gate. They might have some secret agreements too! We must be careful!"

"No matter how careful you are, at times like this brute force is the only way out."

Right as they left the parking lot, they saw on their left some other disciples from Southern Twelve Gates walk out of the exit from the other parking lot. A middle-aged couple led the way, and their disciples followed.

They slightly nodded as they saw Garen, and led the way to the left.

"They are heading toward the military camps. It looks like they have connections within the army! Should we follow them, Senior Brother?" Collin asked in a quiet voice.

Garen raised his head and looked up. On the floors above them, disciples from other sects were looking at them from the inside. Among them was Raydon couple who were close to him earlier. He was wondering where they were when he was competing in the tournament. It looked like they had received words in advance.

"If they had the capabilities to help us, they would have done so. Since they have left on their own, obviously they can’t help us. Let’s go back the way we came. I’m curious as to what kind of methods they have prepared for us!" Garen sneered and led the way to the right.

The white cement road was wide enough for four carriages to ride side by side. The group followed Garen outside the Celestial Star Gate’s front gate, where carriages were parked.

The white and black horses huffed and puffed, grubbing their hoofs. They were tied to a tree trunk on the side of the road.

Garen walked directly toward the biggest carriage, which was pulled by four horses and had two rows. He instantly pulled the rope that tied the carriage, tearing it easily.

"Get on!"

The group jumped in without hesitation.

Garen found another large carriage behind the first and organized everyone else to get on.

"Those are our carriages! What do you think you are doing!" A shouting came from behind.

Garen ignored the shouting and asked the driving disciple to lash on the horses with the whip. The two carriages quickly turned and sped onto the road. Garen sat next to the driver and squinted his eyes, immersed in his own mind to check his condition.

After his Mammoth Secret Technique evolved to Explosive level, he was not sure what his current strength was. He only knew he was stronger, a lot stronger!

A small blood sphere in his chest was spinning and rotating, radiating hot streams into his body. The streams spread out like small creeks and came back after running through his whole body. It was a continuous cycle.

His injuries were not completely healed but he still had to fight the green-haired man earlier. The strong trait of Mammoth Secret Technique is its explosiveness, but when the user fights someone with similar strength or someone with an even stronger body, this explosiveness would turn into a counterforce and injure the user as well.

Garen’s injury got worse after this fight.

"It shouldn’t matter too much." Strangely, the blood sphere in his chest was repairing his body like the attribute points did. "At this rate. I’ll be fine and able to regain my full strength after half an hour."

Garen estimated and thought to himself.

Chapter 90: Adverse Circumstance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Collin, tell me exactly what happened at White Cloud Gate." Garen turned around to speak to Collin.

"Okay!" The girl cleaned her sweaty forehead. Knowing the urgency in the situation, she tried her best to explain everything with brevity.

"Right now, Senior Sister betrayed the Gate, Second Senior Brother went missing, and Third Senior Brother could not withstand the situation. The people below our gate have always been ambitious. I’m afraid they might take this opportunity to carve up the gate.

"This is a terrible situation for us to be in! Master is still unconscious. Also, the Southern Twelve Gates had always supported each other in times of hardships, but now all our allies are paralyzed or have lost contact with us. It must be chaotic at the gate, so we need someone to stand up and take charge of it! Senior Brother, you must get back now and accept the responsibilities."

"Our enemies won’t let this opportunity slip through their hands. We will surely meet some trouble on the way back!"

"We’ll have to see how much trouble they could bring!" Garen’s expression was cold.

At that instant, a group of masked men walked out from the side of the road. Their body sizes varied, but they all uniformly wore black bandana masks. There was a strong warrior’s aura around them.

These masked men sneered and blocked the road. A skinny woman who was leading them stepped out with a smirk.

"Fei Baiyun, you didn’t think there would be a day like this, did you?" The voice was dry and hoarse, and her body was young and curvy. She had a great body, but her voice was unpleasant to hear.

A little further ahead on the road, a few more people came out of the woods. They were in red and white clothing, and none of them were masked. A dozen young men followed behind them. All in all, they looked like a secret arts sect.

"The Crimson Scorpion Angela went first. Nice, let her test the water for us."

A short and chubby elderly man, whose nose had been sliced off, squinted his eyes. "We’re not the only ones preying on White Cloud Gate. Countless sects are after the Southern Twelve Gates, since this is a fat piece of meat. If we don’t act fast we might not even get a taste of the soup."

"We’ve waited patiently for so long. It’s finally the time to take a slice of the cake. Fei Baiyun is still unconscious, leaving behind a disciple who is so tender we can squeeze water out of him. Two of their core disciples have gone missing as well."

"The White Cloud Gate does not have any chance to resist, we just have to watch out for others." Another woman dressed in white whispered.

"The Southern Twelve Gates suppressed us for all these years, this time we can finally get rid of them altogether!" The old man said with a chuckle. "Although we’ll have to watch out for Fei Baiyun’s last struggle."

"No problem, the Fighting Association’s President is right behind us; he is waiting for Fei Baiyun." The woman sneered. "Our Jade Mountain Gate will take care of the others."

Garen sat on the carriage and carefully observed the road blockers. His eyes glanced through the woods on the side of the road. Who knew how many unknown threats were still hiding in the glooms.

"You guys keep going. I’ll take care of them!" Garen’s eyes turned cold and he jumped off the carriage without waiting for Collin’s response.

He strode toward the woman in black mask up front.

"Give us Fei Baiyun…"

Shoo!

Garen didn’t say a word. He simply jumped forward and brought his right arm down with a Shot Form.

The woman was swift; she dodged with a sidestep, and her hands ensnared Garen’s arm. "I’ll break this arm first!" She said cruelly as she infused all her force into her movement. However, just like entangling a steel beam, her arms couldn’t move the opponent even an inch.

Garen’s arms abruptly exerted a huge force and the woman was sent flying like a jute bag filled with grass. She was knocked into a dozen back flips on the ground, and ended up smashed into a tree trunk. She turned pale and cried out in pain, tightly covering her chest.

She was unable to speak a word at the moment.

Garen didn’t stop to analyze the outcome of his attack. He charged straight at two machetes that were thrown at him. With a crackling sound the machetes broke into pieces, along with the bones of three masked men; they were blasted away and knocked out on the ground.

Garen’s expression was indifferent. His arms expanded to both sides in Shot Form. He caught two masked men’s hair and effortlessly pulled, resulting in two bloody scalps being torn off from their heads. The men screamed in pain, staggering.

Bang!

Along with an abrupt gunshot, Garen felt a small pain in his stomach. He lowered his head and saw a copper bullet bouncing off of his skin and it fell to the ground in a series of tinkling sound.

At that moment, everyone froze astonished.

"Even bullet can’t… pierce through his skin!!" Someone said in a shaken voice. The men in masks started backing off, horrified.

Garen whipped over a masked man on his right with his foot. A cracking sound came from the target’s waist while his spine bent back in an unnatural shape as he rolled back on the ground. There was no sound from where he was lying down.

Garen charged at the masked woman under the tree. He didn’t need to look at her to know she was the one who shot him.

He used the Step Form and, with a huge thud noise, the woman’s magnificent breasts blew up from under his foot, while a huge hole appeared in the middle of her chest. She died instantly without a whimper. The pistol in her hand slid to the side.

Garen picked up the pistol and threw it into the carriage, then turned around and sprinted deep into the woods.

The astonishment had not vanished from the faces of the short elderly man and the woman in white, their disciples spread out into a defensive fan shape. Garen was already charging at them without any emotion.

Bam Bam Bam!

With three consecutive thuds, Garen barbarically knocked three disciples into the air. The disciples hit either had their spine broken or exploded into flesh and blood under the impact. Suddenly no one else dared to stand in front of him.

The short and chubby old man pulled out a short cutlass. His hands glowed blue as he swiftly looped around to Garen’s side and fiercely stabbed at Garen’s waist.

The woman in white sneered. She wore a silver bladed-knuckle on one of her hands, and thus she ripped her fist through the air, attacking Garen. The fist broke into three different fist doppelgangers attacking Garen’s face, chest, and stomach at the same time.

Their attacks hit Garen simultaneously, but other than scraping off some of his clothes, they were completely ineffective. The two were both shocked, pushing down their toes in a hurry to try to escape, but it was too late.

"Double Shot Form!"

Garen closed his eyes, completely ignoring their attacks, and flicked his fingers as they swept past the two opponent’s necks.

With two crisp sounds of impact, the old man and the woman both slipped past Garen.

Without looking behind, Garen once more charged deeper into the forest.

The two stood in a stupor, a thin line emerged from their neck. Their heads fell from their necks with a thrilling sound of flesh and bones breaking. Blood streamed from their veins while the bodies slowly hit the ground.

After gazing for a few seconds, their disciples all screamed in terror.

"This is a massacre!"

Collin and the crew, who were still on the carriage, watched with faces pale as Garen rampaged through the enemies, anyone who dared stand in the way was blown up into a blood mist, like an air balloon. He was unstoppable.

Simon and the disciples from other sects were astonished; the gore and blood scared a few girls.

"Let’s hurry out of here, we are just burdens if we stay!" Simon realized something and whipped the horse hard to speed up the carriage.

"This level of strength… Senior Brother Garen is so strong!!" The leaders of other two sects, the silver-haired youngster Rampas accelerated as well. He held down the urge to vomit and exclaimed in an envious tone.

"Senior Brother Rampas, are we safe now?" A cute little girl asked while covering her mouth, her face was ghastly pale."

"Not entirely. Even though Senior Brother Garen from White Cloud Gate could protect us for a while, we must get back to our own gates later. You have to take charge as the Senior Sister of your sect."

"The Southern Twelve Gates are in chaos, and our masters have been badly injured." Rampas looked decisive as he glanced at the White Cloud Gate disciples in front of them.‘’

Garen raced into the woods toward two slim silhouettes with their hands in their back.

One of them was a middle-aged man, wearing a tight black leather suit with the word "Fighting" printed on his right chest. His two hands rested on a pair of dark scimitars.

The other man looked aged and was wearing a loose black training suit, with a short white staff on one hand. The shock from the carnage only left his face when he saw Garen approaching.

"White Cloud Gate’s Garen! The strongest of the Southern Twelve Gates! Let’s see how much stamina you have!" The old man stepped back, as the middle-aged man came forward to face Garen.

Shoo shoo shoo!

Three consecutive blades swung at Garen’s face, two of them aimed at his eyes.

The man in black suit was ruthless, swinging out three attacks right at the moment he was about to run into Garen. His right knee concurrently tackled at Garen’s lower abdomen with a spiked kneecap that appeared suddenly on his knees.

"Chain Swing Form!"

Garen’s upper body spun around like a spinning top. His arms flexed out like the propellers of a helicopter, bouncing back the scimitars and cleaving at the opponent’s neck.

The spin simultaneously dodged the knee attack.

Bam Bam!

The three blades were knocked flying, but the man’s strength was surprising as he only took one step back before he continued his attack by clawing at Garen’s face.

"Heh!" Garen recklessly punched at the attacker, ready to trade blow for blow.

He closed his eyes and felt his steel-hard eyelids blocked the opponent’s clawing attack.

Clang!!

A sound of metal clashing came as his fist came in contact with the enemy’s chest; something hard was blocking his fist.

Garen sneered and suddenly pushed down again with even more power.

Crackle!! Pui!!

After a loud thud, he heard the middle-aged man spitting blood.

He opened his eyes and saw his enemy embedded into the tree trunk. A large piece of a metal breastplate was ripped inward, showing a bloody hollow that pierced the body and sunk deep into the tree.

Without resting for a second, Garen charged directly toward the other man.

"Cain!! The breastplate was pierced through!! How is that possible?"

The old man was sweating while holding his short staff. He raised his arms and the staff turned into many shadows that surrounded Garen’s upper body.

However, the strength and the speed from the attack was far worse than the ones from the middle-aged man. Apparently the man was old and way past his prime shape.

Garen used a Dash Form, raising his fist and smashing into the old man’s chest.

Shoo!

A beam of silver light dashed in front of him, stopping his attack.

Garen stood still and squinted his eyes.

"You again?"

Tenstar Ni walked out from behind a tree with a smile on his face and a silver sword in his hand.

"You can’t kill him. He is the president of the Fighting Association, an ally of our Celestial Circle Gate."

"Isn’t the Celestial Circle Gate worrying too much about other people’s problems?" Garen’s voice was low and his face turned cold.

"Too much or too little, that’s our problem. Do you want to try my sword?" Tenstar Ni’s eyes glowed with ruthless light. As he stared at Garen’s neck, a mysterious aura emerged from his body.

Garen could feel that threat.

"Celestial Circle Gate …" He controlled his rage and turned around. He had younger disciples to take care of back in White Cloud Gate, so he could not afford to keep fighting here. Up until now he had not used his secret arts to inflate his muscles, because he wanted to save his stamina for the real danger later. The true threat had yet to come.

Chapter 91: The Way Back 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Quickly catching up to the carriage that had already pulled ahead, Garen jumped onto it.

The two black carriages rapidly ran in parallel on the winding road. The noise of rolling wheels and horse hooves hitting the cement road sounded especially crisp in the quiet surroundings as if these were the only two carriages around.

With a calm expression, Garen sat next to the driver.

"This exchange was plotted by our enemies and was a mission against the Southern Twelve Gates as a whole. Our opponent could instantly expose each Gate’s internal weakness and combine this with attacks from the outside. They were able to assemble forces from so many different backgrounds…" Garen then thought about his fight against Sylphalan, "Why did it have to be last night? All combat forces have now been eliminated, so they must be planning to overthrow the Southern Twelve Gates …"

He became even more cautious.

"With this situation, the hidden masterminds behind this mission will not let us slip away that easily. However, covered by the military forces, our allied gates are running in different directions and the enemy men would have to split up to chase us as well."

Garen closed his eyes, stopped thinking, and started meditating. In the end, all he could do right now was fight with whoever was in his way. The clowns from earlier were just an appetizer and the real trouble had yet to come.

Having mastered the White Cloud Gate’s secret arts and transcended to a level no man had ever reached before, he knew his own strengths very well. As exaggerated and powerful as it sounded, even he was not sure of what he could do.

Garen could only compare himself to the competition he had met recently.

The only person who could rival him right now would be Celestial Star Gate’s Tenstar Ni. Garen could feel a subtle, yet dangerous, aura from him.

As Garen traveled on the carriage, he organized his thoughts and prepared his body for the next storm.

The other disciples were feeling much more secure after Garen had returned. Carrie was in charge of caring for Fei Baiyun, who was still in a coma. She frequently wiped away sweat from his brow.

"Collin, do you know who our biggest rival is?" Garen suddenly asked.

"It would be the Fighting Association. Their president has held a long grudge against Master Fei for many years, so he won’t let this opportunity slip by!" Collin seemed worried.

"Fighting Association…" Garen was not worried about the Fighting Association, but concerned about the powers behind them. After all, most of Fighting Association’s forces had been wiped out and the rest would not pose a threat to him.

******************

On the side of the road near the outer edge of the city, an old man with a silver beard and hair stood beside a window on the second floor of a small hotel as he waited for the approaching carriages.

"Looks like the Fighting Association couldn’t stop these three gates, so we’ll have to do it ourselves."

"It can’t be helped." In the shadows behind him, a woman with a pale face answered in a low voice. "A small sect like the Fighting Association didn’t have anyone strong to begin with. They were all second to third class fighters and barely able to make a name for themselves. What did you expect from them?"

While dressed in a black suit, the lady played with a small dagger in her hands. Her suit did not have a left sleeve and her exposed arm revealed a tattoo of a huge spotted python on her pale skin. The dagger twirled and cut through the air, making swoosh noises.

"Any word from the other squads?"

The old man nodded. "We just learned that of the ten squads that went on the mission, three of them were unsuccessful. One of them failed because Eastern Pole Gate’s master woke up and struggled with his last bit of strength to fight off our men. In addition to that squad, the squads that faced off against White Cloud Gate and the Lucene Brotherhood also failed. The Lucene Brotherhood’s master was seriously injured, but his second eldest son showed up. This young man had arms harder than steel and he was so fast that bullets couldn’t hit him, so he must have mastered the secret techniques of the Wind of Lucene and the Lucene Steel Fists."

He paused to take a breath and continued, "White Cloud Gate’s senior disciple Garen has mastered the gate’s only secret technique, the Mammoth Secret Technique. His strength is on par with his master when his master was young."

"Are they both Grade E?"

"I’m sure." The old man nodded.

"Are we going to stop them ourselves?" The woman was starting to doubt herself.

"No need. We can wait and let others deplete their energy first. Only in times of hardship like this can one see the true strengths of a sect. Just look at the Lucene Brotherhood and now the White Cloud Gate. We should remain patient. What if some other strong force was to intervene? Then we’d be in real trouble." The old man sounded like he was speaking to the woman, but also talking to himself.

**********************

In the woods across from the road, it was completely quiet without the chirping of birds or insects. Behind some tall bushes and thick tree trunks, the faint sounds of breathing could be heard.

There were countless men hiding in this forest by the road.

This was the last stretch of road before reaching the city.

Sitting next to the driver, Garen raised his alertness while everyone in the carriages lowered their heads and hid behind the sides. Fortunately, the sides of these carriages were more than a meter tall and more than enough for them to hide behind.

Garen knew that they would be safe once they were inside the city. After all, those people did not dare to kill in public. This was the best place for them to strike.

"Protect yourselves with pistols and jump off immediately if the horse gets shot," Garen warned with a whisper.

"Don’t worry senior brother, we can handle the minions!" Collin responded.

Garen shook his head silently. Two silver carriages were coming toward them and each had two or three passengers. The driver of the first carriage had a sharp gaze, was well built, and looked like a normal driver from his appearance, but Garen could sense danger from him.

The carriage behind them seemed to have a normal family. The father was handling the horse, his wife sat next to him, and two adorable young girls laughed and chatted while sitting in the cart behind them. Wearing white ballet dancing dresses and stockings, the girls looked around the age of 15 and must have just left a dancing class.

Garen frowned slightly. This distance…

The two carriages greeted each other. The driver in the first carriage glanced at Garen, but did not make a move and drove the carriage right past them.

Garen felt a sense of danger from the driver and thought they would attack. To his surprise, they did not do anything and just passed by. His body tensed up and was ready for any attacks.

As the first carriage drove past them, all Garen could hear was the sound of horse hooves hitting the road.

After a few seconds, the second carriage approached them. Knowing that the people from the first carriage were not enemies, Garen let out a relieved sigh.

Shoo!

He heard an abrupt, but soft noise. Opening his eyes, Garen slammed behind himself with a backhand.

Snap!

"Mmph."

The woman who had jumped at Garen from behind was hit by Garen’s slam in mid-air. With a crackling noise, she fell like a broken stick of wood as her waist bent back at a 90-degree angle. Blood spilled everywhere as the woman landed on the road and fainted from the pain.

Sneering, Garen jumped off his carriage to chase after the carriage behind them.

The carriage wasn’t traveling very fast and the driver was trying to accelerate, but Garen had already caught up and he struck the horse in the head.

Bang!

The horse fell right as he hit it and the carriage came to a stop. The carriage’s other horse was startled, pulling at the carriage in a frenzy. Garen slapped the head of this horse, causing it to fall to the ground while frothing at the mouth.

The two remaining men looked malicious and both jumped at Garen with trench knives since they knew there was no way out. These two were extremely fast as they zig-zagged their way to Garen. One aimed at Garen’s cheek and the other stabbed toward his waist.

The two trench knives were like slithering snakes as they punctured the air and stabbed toward Garen. The edges of the knives glowed blue, showing that they were obviously poisonous.

"If the knife cuts into your skin, you are dead!" The two men had the same thought, putting all their might into this attack. The poison they put on the blade was called spider venom No. 9. There was no cure for this venom and one drop of this mixed poison could kill a man in 10 minutes.

The knives were just about to hit Garen when he suddenly opened his mouth.

"Roar!" A thunderous roar came out of his lungs. This sudden roar startled the two attackers, slowing down their attacks.

"Double Shot Form!!"

Garen’s arms instantly shot to his sides. A terrifying explosive force erupted as his arms inflated like two giant pythons before smashing into the two men’s chests.

"Chh, Chh!"

With their chests penetrated like kebobs, the two men stood paralyzed. Garen twirled his arms and threw them onto the road.

After killing the assassins, Garen strode toward his carriage. As he passed the carriage of the family, the four family members were still stunned. The two yellow horses were horrified by Garen and recoiled, neighing out of terror.

"Ahhh!" The lady on the carriage screamed aloud, but her husband quickly covered her mouth. The two daughters were petrified when they saw Garen, crawling deeper into the carriage and closing their eyes.

Garen glanced at them, then walked past them with an unperturbed face.

He had to use more effort on these men than the people from before. These two men were much stronger, close to the level of Golden Hoop Number 10 that Garen had met before.

Garen’s merciless, kill on sight method frightened the hidden enemies. The first ones to strike were always people who fought with their lives on the line, yet Garen dealt with them like trivial matters.

Chapter 92: The Way Back (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Jumping back into the carriage, Garen’s expression turned serious.

"The minions wouldn’t dare to challenge us now. If we run into more trouble, our opponents will be the ones that are hard to deal with, so you guys should be careful."

Collin and the group nodded behind him.

"What about Senior Brother Rampas?"

"I can’t take care of them forever. Some matters they will just have to face by themselves. I’m not their nanny." Garen replied casually. He looked calm and peaceful. At times of emergency it was very important to be level-headed, but strike down at the opponents swiftly and mercilessly, acting like it was only a breeze. This was meant to frighten the hidden enemies.

If someone were to attack in a situation like this, then the opponent must be very strong! A lot stronger than the enemies from earlier.

The two carriages moved one after another and strolled closer to the city.

The woods on the sides of the road were becoming less and less dense; occasionally they could see small houses. More farmers and passersby could be seen on the sides of the road. Farmers carrying a basket filled with fruits were calling for buyers.

Not far from where the carriages were, they could already see the taller buildings inside the city.

"Almost there… As soon as we get into the city, we shouldn’t face any more attacks! Now is the best time for them to strike!" Garen was feeling even more alert.

Suddenly, a red-haired woman came out of nowhere and blocked the way of the carriages.

She had an attractive face, and a silver rapier was hanging by her waist. She stood in the middle of the road without speaking a word. However, as she stood there, the horses were startled and started neighing out of terror, and the carriages subsequently stopped.

"She’s an expert!" Garen thought, squinting his eyes.

"Where did all these strong enemies come from? I’ve never even seen them before!" Collin bit her lips as she complained, "I’ve done research on all the top martial adepts, but these people today are…"

Garen hopped off the carriage and walked to the front.

"You are here to cut us off too?" As he walked within ten steps of her, he could feel a sharp and cold aura pinching his face. His sight followed the aura and gazed upon the woman’s rapier hanging on her belt; it was emitting a cold and fierce blue light.

The red-haired woman drew her rapier with a ruthless expression. Her movement was very strange, starting slow but gaining speed as she pulled. Finally, with a crisp sound the sword left the scabbard.

"Don’t blame me, I owe someone a favor. Remember the name of your killer; I am Seacroft, it is your honor to die under my Weeping Sword."

"Seacroft? Weeping Sword?" Garen frowned his eyebrows. He could feel the opponent’s strength was close to his, almost reaching his own level. The blood sphere in his chest was a symbol of reaching this level.

Anyone who was close to this level had mastered at least one secret technique; they were very hard to deal with.

A martial adept at this level had surpassed Fei Baiyun’s levels, and thus a regular faction wouldn’t have enough influence to ask for her favor. Garen closely observed the enemy; she was about thirty years old. Anyone who was over twenty-five had no chance of improving any further.

"If you…" Garen heard a sharp and loud screech and was unable to finish his sentence.

"WEAAW!!"

The screaming noise was strange and unsettling like the weeping of a baby. Seacroft’s rapier flashed as she thrusted it toward Garen’s left chest. The unsettling noise was coming from the vibration of the weapon.

The rapier was extremely fast. Just as Garen heard the noise he saw a silver stripe coming toward him; in the blink of an eye it was already at his chest. Unlike prior times, the sword’s cold and sharp aura pierced through his clothes, making his skin grow a small patch of goosebumps.

The strange noise had affected Garen’s reaction, slowing it down and making him unable to block the attack. Garen kicked up some sand and rubble toward the opponent as he felt the pain on his chest.

Both of them backed off after the first contact, and similarly stood still and observed their opponent. Seacroft’s face was scratched by some small rubbles, while Garen’s shirt was pierced open and a small red dot could be seen through the big hole on his shirt.

Without any words, the two charged at each other once again.

The silver rapier turned into a silver snake, twirling and thrusting against Garen’s fists.

The rapier hit Garen over and over again, leaving small red dents all over his body. However, it still couldn’t pierce through Garen’s skin. On the other hand, Garen’s fists were easily dodged by Seacroft. The difference in their speed was too big.

The two continued to battle in circles, exchanging positions several times over a few seconds. The Weeping Sword frequently let out ghost-like screeches. Along with the irritating noise, every time the sword screeched its speed and strength increased, and every time Garen would counter the attack by kicking up sand on Seacroft’s face. As the battle went on, he was getting better at using his techniques in combat; he was a lot more experienced than before. He occasionally let out a war cry to awe his opponent, and Seacroft flinched and slowed down for a moment as Garen shouted, almost getting hit by his fists. She broke into a cold sweat.

Slowly, Garen became familiar with Seacroft’s routines and used to the Weeping Sword’s screeching noises. He was having a good flow while using the Four Big Forms in his combat; all his movements seemed natural, but with a hint of the Four Big Forms.

"Step Form!" Garen suddenly charged towards Seacroft. However, she dodged out the attack, and Garen moved past her, leaving his back open to his enemy.

"That’s my chance!" Seacroft saw an opportunity and took it. She leaped forward with Weeping Sword vibrating and thrust it at Garen. Suddenly, she saw a backhand elbowing from Garen; the strike was fierce like an arrow, filled with explosiveness.

"Shit!"

Her expression changed. Because her body was still in the striking movement, it was too late to change directions. She did not expect Garen to combine his techniques together and set up a trap for her. Not that she hadn’t been careful enough, but Garen’s attacks had always been true and to her face, so she didn’t think he would use a fake move to lure her in.

In the heat of the moment, Seacroft decided to use her secret technique and the ghastly screech turned into a scream. She pulled up the rapier and blocked with it in front of her body.

Garen was expressionless. He had immersed himself into this battle, and although he felt clumsy using the Four Big Forms before, now he was becoming more and more skilled. He could easily use the most fitting form during battle, maximizing its effectiveness and lethality. This was truly a wonderful feeling.

His right elbow clashed into Seacroft’s rapier.

Pow!

Garen felt a pain in his waist. His elbow tilted and was only able to scratch the rapier by the tip, but the impact still sent Seacroft flying a few meters back. She stumbled with her face pale, barely standing still by supporting her body with the Weeping Sword.

Garen glanced at his waist, a long copper bullet was stuck inside his skin.

"There’s a sniper!!" He suddenly realized. Then, he felt something moving between his eyebrows. Someone was aiming at his forehead, so he quickly slanted his head.

Boom!

Another loud gunshot, and a blazing bullet instantly flew past Garen’s cheek.

Seacroft had caught her breath, and began another round of attacks with her sword.

Garen had to deal with her attacks while constantly watching out for the sniper’s shots, so he couldn’t use his full strength. However, his Four Big Forms were becoming more and more consistent and natural, and his moves followed one after the other marvelously.

"I have to finish this fight as soon as possible!" He knew he couldn’t waste time on this. Had he been by himself, there wouldn’t be much trouble, but he still had to take care of the younger disciples.

He used the Shot, Dash, Swing, and Step Form consecutively. It was his first time using Four Major Forms in just two seconds. He felt his Qi clogging inside his body, and his old belly injury started hurting once again.

Step Form lifted another wave of sand and rubbles onto Seacroft’s face, forcing her to step back.

"Die!" Garen reached for his foe’s throat with his hand. He was faster than ever before. He created an opportunity at the cost of deepening his injury. As long as he could finish her first, it would be easier to take care of the snipers later.

Peng!

Another bullet stroke hard onto Garen’s neck, tilting his body and knocking him off balance. Garen’s hand barely missed Seacroft’s neck, leaving only two blood trails on her face.

"Damn it!" Garen was furious, both times he was about to finish her off, the sniper interrupted him.

He inhaled deeply, instantly inflating his lungs. The skin on his chest turned blue and dark under the ragged shirt.

A thunderous war cry.

Seacroft’s ears went numb from the loud noise and she became paralyzed.

Garen took this opportunity and leaped onto her. Dodging out two bullets, he grabbed her head and smashed it against the ground.

Seacroft’s head cracked open like a watermelon. The Weeping Sword dropped out of her hand and onto the ground. Garen picked up the sword, stood up in a backflip, and started sprinting toward the sniper’s direction.

He could see him on the second floor of a red building; a bald man was packing up his sniper rifle and preparing his escape.

Garen leaped up to the second floor of the building. His hand pierced through the man’s chest, and pulled the ribs and flesh inside. In a disturbing noise, the man’s chest was torn open. He screamed like a pig.

"Boss! Help!!" He cried in terror.

Garen smacked the man’s head with his palm. The screaming abruptly stopped and his body turned limp and lifeless.

Following the direction of the sniper’s call for help, he saw another man standing at the corner of the room. He was also bald and had a sturdy body, while his eyes were red like Garen’s. The man was breathing heavily. He was obviously part of the attack earlier since he also had a sniper rifle in his hand.

Garen’s fury eased down after he killed the sniper. However, upon seeing another sniper in this room, he sneered and rushed toward him.

Shoo!

A stripe of silver light crossed in front of his body.

"Tenstar Ni!" In an indomitable rage, Garen shouted, "Don’t push my limit!!"

A long and slim sword separated Garen from the bald sniper. Tenstar Ni stood on the side with a face of mockery, staring at Garen.

"I’m sorry, you can’t touch this man either."

"You are courting death!!" Garen couldn’t hold it anymore. His muscles swelled as he grew from 1.7 to over 2 meters. The clothes on his chest burst and flew in all directions. Garen was topless. His muscles turned dark and blue as his veins stood out on his skin like coiling black snakes. His body was even bigger than back on the tournament.

Tenstar Ni’s expression changed.

Chapter 93: Tenstar Ni 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A punch!

Garen’s right arm darted forth like a slithering python, aimed at Tenstar Ni’s head.

Murderous thoughts emerged in his mind.

After he had transmigrated to this alternate reality, he had been pretending to be a teenage boy with his adult conscious. He had been under the influence of depression. Training in martial arts gave him a chance to unwind. Every time his strength grew, so did his sense of security.

However, old man Gregor’s death made him feel helpless and realize how weak he was. As soon as he achieved great improvements with the secret arts, he met Sylphalan and almost lost his life. This raised his sense of crisis once again.

He didn’t plan to provoke the Celestial Circle Gate, but he didn’t expect them to side with his enemies flagrantly. At this moment, Garen’s depressive emotions erupted like a volcano.

The blood sphere inside his chest released countless hot streams that circulated throughout his body.

Bang!

His fist smashed into the wall, sinking deeply in it.

Tenstar Ni dodged aside with a serious expression. His sword swirled to make a silver light curtain, blocking possible attacks, and he jumped back with a backflip.

Bam!

Suddenly, a cloud of rubble and sand sputtered all over his face. Several rocks smashed into his nose, slicing open a few bloody wounds.

"Go!" Tenstar Ni closed his eyes in the dust. He raised his left hand and a strand of silver light flashed out from it.

Clang!

A short dagger bounced off Garen’s chest, with no effect. Seeing that, Tenstar Ni pulled the dagger back into his hand by a thin thread tied to the hilt.

"Heh!"

Garen leaped forward. His right arm still had a fistful of gravel, so he hiked his hand to throw another wave of dust at his opponent. At the same time, his palm smashed toward Tenstar’s chest with a Shot Form.

His dark blue hand stretched out with inhumanly sharp nails. As the hand moved, a sharp howling filled the air. This howling sounded singular, yet layered, resembling the howling from a mammoth.

Tenstar Ni’s expression changed again. He raised his hand to block the dust and lifted the sword with his other hand. In this situation where he could not clearly see the attack, his sword flashed as he hacked at Garen’s hand.

Thud!

The sword cut onto Garen’s hand and made a thud noise, but it couldn’t stop Garen’s palm from advancing.

Tenstar Ni gritted his teeth, his face flashed with a blue aura, a clump of dark muscle emerged on the back of his sword hand, the clump was shaped like a cross shaped star1.

Swoosh! The sword stabbed three times in an instant, and in the fraction of a second, turned ninety degrees and stood up, slashing directly at Garen’s hand.

Zing!!

The hand and the sword came in contact. Surprisingly, the sword could not leave a single scratch on the dark blue palm, and thus was bent into a curve.

Garen’s showed a ruthless expression as he slammed his feet against the ground!

The stomp blasted sand and debris into the air.

The sword broke into two pieces with a cracking sound, while Garen’s hand pressed down the weapon pieces into Tenstar Ni’s chest.

With a heavy thud, Tenstar Ni groaned and flipped over. After rolling for about ten steps he finally jumped back up.

Three bloody marks appeared on Garen’s right palm; the skin and muscle around the marks were completely scraped off, vaguely revealing the bones underneath.

He clenched the hand and felt a sharp pain in the center of the palm. There wasn’t much bleeding though, since the blood soon clogged, forming a protective layer around the wounds, preventing the flesh from getting in contact with the air.

"This isn’t what the Mammoth Secret Technique looks like!" Tenstar Ni hatefully roared. His face flashed red as he spoke; it was a sign that he was seriously injured.

Tenstar Ni backed off quickly while taking out a small paper bag from his pockets and dumping all the medicinal containers inside his mouth.

As soon as he gulped down the medicine, he turned around and staggered away.

"Still trying to escape!"

Garen followed up closely using Dash Form. He stomped down on the ground with a Step Form, forming a small crater on the ground as his speed suddenly increased and he leaped forward at Tenstar Ni.

As soon as he started the chase, his eyes were blinded by a burst of flashing light as two daggers came flying to his face.

With the impressive speed from him dash forward and the daggers flying at him on the opposite direction, Garen had no chance to dodge. Adding up the speed of these daggers combined with his own, the lethality of the enemy’s attack was at least doubled!

A sense of danger never experienced before took over him. The reflection of silver lights grew larger and larger in his pupils.

Garen could only close his eyes and try to lower his head. At this moment, a stream flowed up to his eyebrows from the blood sphere in his chest.

He didn’t expect the injured opponent to hide his ultimate skill until now, turning the tables and putting Garen in great danger.

"Die!" He furiously threw the Weeping Sword forward.

The two daggers slashed onto Garen’s eyebrows and immediately hit the bone on his forehead. They were only able to cut two blood marks on his eyebrows.

Tenstar Ni’s face went pale when he turned around and saw his attacks were not effective.

He knew his strength wasn’t enough. His full might was only able to cause a small injury to the enemy. He tried everything and still got badly injured, and all of the damage came from a single hit.

Combining his full strength and Garen’s momentum from sprinting, he should have been able to put an end to this fight. However, he didn’t expect that…

"How do I fight him…" He whined mutely, "I shouldn’t have pissed this freak off in the first place! His Body-hardening Technique is ridiculous! I can’t hurt him. All that trouble only scraped off some skin.

As he turned around he saw Garen throwing a silver sword at him, and along with it came a screeching noise. Tenstar Ni was scared to death. The cross-shaped muscle plumped up again as his right arm turned into a shadow, smacking behind him.

He blocked the Weeping Sword and sent it flying. The sword sunk deep into the wall beside him, leaving only the hilt to be seen.

However, the huge counterforce shook his body and slowed him down. Garen saw this opportunity and quickly leaped forward, grabbing Tenstar Ni’s shoulder.

A grey powder sprinkled onto Garen’s face in a puff; it was the medicine Tenstar Ni used to heal himself.

The powder smelled spicy and pungent. Garen’s movement slowed down, as he knew it would irritate his eyes. He closed them and whipped his hand forward with Swing Form.

However, it was too slow and the Swing Form missed the target.

Tenstar Ni did a backflip and landed a few meters away, but his face was even paler than before. It seemed the use of his cross-shaped muscle technique expended a vast amount of energy, and combined with Garen’s smash to his chest, Tenstar Ni’s condition was terrible.

"Garen of White Cloud Gate! Just wait, I’ll kill everyone around you!" Tenstar Ni’s malevolent voice came from afar, he turned around and staggered away. His movement looked unnatural, but that didn’t slow him down.

Garen was rubbing his eyes, which were still blurry from the powder and tears. At that moment he couldn’t clearly see the opponent.

However, as the voice came, he sneered and smashed his hand into the ground, breaking the rocks and dirt into gravel. He grabbed a handful of small rubbles and fiercely threw them toward the direction where the voice came from.

His arm swelled in an instant, and his hand sent the rubbles flying in an instant, with the peebles screeching in the air.

Poof! Poof!

As soon as the bang was heard several bloody holes appeared on Tenstar Ni’s back and he fell on the floor.

"Retard! I really wouldn’t know what to do if you didn’t make a sound!"

Garen grinned hideously and rushed over under his blurry vision, catching Tenstar Ni by his hair.

"Senior Brother will avenge me!" Tenstar Ni knew he couldn’t escape. He roared as Garen held his hair and smashed his head down.

Bam!

To Garen’s surprise, Tenstar Ni’s head was fine. However, as he tried to pull him up he tore his scalp off by the hair. The scene looked horrific and bloody.

Tenstar Ni quickly climbed forward like an invertebrate mollusk, exhibiting his robust vitality.

Garen chased up and stomped hard onto his back.

Step Form!

Bang! Crack!

Two sounds echoed together as Tenstar Ni’s spine broke into pieces. He struggled with all his force to turn around and spit an arrow of blood onto Garen’s face.

This arrow of blood could have killed a common person, but it was completely ineffective to Garen. He closed his eyes and felt a warm liquid on his face, nothing else.

Garen wiped the blood off his face, aimed at Tenstar Ni’s head, and used another Step Form.

"Roar!!"

The neighing sound of the mammoth lingered in the air.

Boom!!

A deep crater appeared on the ground. Brains, bones, and blood mixed together, and along with some blue messy hair, they turned into a slimy blend.

Garen’s right foot and ankle were covered in this mixture. He lifted his foot and started searching on the torso. He found another pack of medicinal powder, two more silver daggers―both threaded with a thin line―, a string of keys and some money.

As he collected the loot, he opened his eyes as much as he could. The tears had washed away the medicinal powders in his eyes, and although it still felt uncomfortable, he was able to see clearly again.

He looked around and didn’t see a trace of the bald guy.

"Escaped huh?" He looked around. He was standing in an open ground behind the two-story building. The building wall was covered in fractures and holes from the fight.

It was completely silent inside.

He took a deep breath and looked around to check if there were other enemies nearby. Suddenly, a child’s weep came from inside the building, but something soon muffled the noise. He could faintly hear the horrified breathing of a woman.

Obviously, a family was still inside, but they dared not make a sound, afraid of getting silenced as witnesses. They kept quiet to pretend no one was home.

At this distance, a normal person could not have heard the noise. However, Garen’s senses were several times sharper, so of course he could hear everything.

Shaking his head, Garen looked at himself. His shirt was gone, a line of bullets were stuck at his waist, there were two wounds on his eyebrows and three on his right hand.

He gripped the bullets in his waist and pulled them out hard. Streams of blood gushed out from the wounds but stopped almost immediately. The blood clogged into a membrane and covered his wounds.

Chapter 94: Tenstar Ni (2)

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Apart from external injuries, Garen felt some internal bruising as well as a tearing pain. It was clear that he had strained some muscles and injured himself. Most importantly, the blood and Qi orb in his chest had been considerably reduced and had depleted significantly after healing and temporarily enhancing his defense.

Garen vaguely felt that the blood and Qi orb was overused, it might completely disperse with no way to restore it. This hypothetical situation would cause a drop in his level of attainment and his body strength could be greatly diminished.

Ever since he attained the Qi and blood orb, his all aspects of his ability had markedly increased. He did not have Attributes to enhance his physical qualities, but his explosive force, defense, reaction speed, comprehension, and so on had undergone significant changes. Even though there were no direct changes to his Attributes, his actual strength had increased by at least one level.

"Looks like I have to use this thing carefully…" Garen's body gradually shrunk as he reverted to his original state. He took the torn black overcoat from Tenstar Ni's body and put it on. Even though it was ripped, it was better than nothing.

Garen took a last look at the body on the ground and let out a sigh of relief. He relaxed his body completely and started to recuperate.

Tenstar Ni was undoubtedly an expert on par with Garen. The true strength of normal experts would not even hurt Garen, let alone threaten him, but Tenstar Ni managed to do it. If not for the effect of the Qi and blood orb, Garen would have been severely injured even if he managed to kill Tenstar Ni.

Tenstar Ni's Secret Martial Art was very strong: it was able to not only increase one's speed, but explosive force and strength were enhanced to a terrifying level as well. When this explosive technique was used, Tenstar Ni could even effortlessly break through Garen's defensive Explosive Fist Arts Body Hardening Technique

If not for the fact that this explosive technique could not be used continuously—it seemed that every time Tenstar Ni did, there would be some backlash damage to his body—it would have been hard to predict the winner of this battle.

"I've really fallen out with Celestial Circle Gate this time. There is still the Eldest Senior Brother of Celestial Circle Gate and number one expert of the South, Andrela. Even his junior brother Tenstar Ni was already so powerful. Andrela… I'm afraid I'm no match for him yet."

Garen estimated their true strengths and started to be more fearful of the Celestial Circle Gate.

"Celestial Circle Gate sent snipers, then sent a series of experts in defensive striking. In the end, Tenstar Ni even directly intercepted me and continuously impeded me. His intent was likely to get me agitated so that I would start the fight and give Celestial Circle Gate a reason for a direct intervention. Otherwise, they would have broken the rules if they intervened when they had already expressed a neutral stance. But if White Cloud Gate started it, then they could cover their face with another layer of fig leaf."

"How hypocritical…" Garen sneered. "Looks like you never would have expected Tenstar Ni to die by my hands. If it was not for his own stupidity and vocal provocation, I would probably not have been able to kill him in the end."

Celestial Circle Gate was different from other common sects. Even on the surface, they had many experts. Coupled with the number one expert of the South, Andrela, and countless other hidden strong powers, they were a huge force to be reckoned with. Even if Garen had a strong self-confidence from his special ability, he felt heavily pressured by having them as his opponent.

He was not sure how many more experts Celestial Circle Gate had that were the same level as Tenstar Ni, but if they sent two more, he would not be able to survive.

He was the strongest person of the Southern Twelve Gates, far and away stronger than other students and disciples. Some sect masters were also likely weaker than him. Even with such true strength, it was already so difficult for him to face a somewhat famous disciple from Celestial Circle Gate. There was obviously a gap in their level of martial arts: he had trained in the Secret Mammoth Technique to an unprecedented level, yet barely scraped a win against Tenstar Ni.

Garen had subtly peaked: he had reached the upper limit of this Secret Martial Art.

Although the outcome of combat was not purely decided by the level of the Secret Martial Art—it still depended on willpower, strategy, response, and other factors—martial arts definitely played a large part in it.

Disciples like Tenstar Ni definitely had not attained the level of Qi and blood orb, but they still vaguely managed to temporarily achieve the true strength of that level with special methods. The Secret Martial Arts and Secret Methods of Celestial Circle Gate could produce this effect. Garen was dismayed and did not know how many more experts Celestial Circle Gate had that were at that level.

"Enough thinking about this matter. I'll just head back first. There is no time to consider all these things now!"

Garen quickened his pace and went back the same way he previously came from.

Click!

As he walked out of the shadow of the building, Garen was stunned.

In front of him, dozens of black submachine guns were pointed at him. Not only that, Garen felt a dozen people focusing their gaze on him from afar: the gaze of snipers.

Not far away, there were green armored personnel carriers which were shaped like quadrilaterals. Imprinted on the sides, there was an insignia of a black and white striped flag with a black bird spreading its wings on the white stripe.

This was the national flag of the Yalu Confederation!

Garen did not dare to move a muscle mainly because of the gaze of the dozen snipers.

The bullet from the sniper earlier had proven that these powerful rifles could break his defense and cause him a certain amount of harm. If there were a dozen more submachine guns at such a close range, Garen was not sure he would survive.

In the dense hail of bullets, the wounds from his broken defense would be ripped wider and even he could not escape that reality. It was impossible for a human being to outrun a bullet.

He quickly scanned the soldiers with submachine guns in front of him. They wore dark green uniforms and round steel helmets, which were also painted green. Each of them was heavily armed from head to toe, with a bullet belt strapped diagonally across their bodies and a grenade bag at their waist.

"What should I do!?" A variety of measures flashed across Garen's mind in an instant, but being surrounded by so many guns, it was impossible even for him to successfully escape.

"Eldest Senior Brother! Run, quickly! They want to kill you!" Among the few people being held hostage in the distance, Collin suddenly shouted.

She had hardly finished her sentence before Garen suddenly felt a piercing pain between his brows. A chilling sense of danger filled his body and there were goosebumps all over his skin.

Someone wanted to kill him!

The Qi and blood orb in his chest bubbled. Nearby, Garen saw a military officer in a dark green uniform with a cruel expression on his face holding up a huge, heavy duty, jet-black sniper rifle and steadily aiming it at him. His hand was already on the trigger ready to shoot!

Without the slightest hesitation, Garen kicked up a cloud of dust and sand without warning.

Rat tat tat tat..!

The sound of submachine guns firing filled the air.

Within seconds, countless guns started firing. The intense barrage muffled all other sounds.

Garen stood squarely in place and was stunned to see that the federal soldiers had fallen in front of him.

Teams of soldiers in brown uniforms surrounded all of the soldiers in green uniforms.

Compared to the soldiers in green, these soldiers in brown uniforms were obviously better trained. Their every move was calm and precise: there were no unnecessary actions. Each of them had strong Qi and blood and their actions were sophisticated. They were heavily armed and were clearly battle-hardened veterans.

Next, Garen looked at the sniper military officer in the distance who was lying face down on the personnel carrier. His head was now bent to the side and blood was slowly flowing out from the gunshot wound at his temple.

"Commanding officer of the Sixth Brigade of the South, Caesar Leon, is alleged to have committed treason, traded in important national intelligence, sold federal arms, privately used military force for personal gains, and so on. He has now been found guilty and shall be sentenced concurrently for these multiple crimes. He was arrested in the name of the highest command in the South, but the commanding officer and his guards did not show repentance and have now been executed by firing squad. All Sixth Brigade soldiers, put down your weapons and await further instructions."

Calm and collected, the clear voice of a man came from the distance.

Garen looked toward the direction where the voice was coming from.

"Yo, Garen! Long time no see." The flaming red hair of Golden Hoop Number 6 fluttered as he smiled cheekily. He was wearing the neat brown uniform of a military officer and black leather gloves. On his right shoulder, a silver patch clearly indicated his rank.

Silver on black with four stripes and a dot: it was the rank of a colonel.

Garen let out a long sigh of relief.

The soldiers around him started to clean up the bodies and opened up a path.

Garen walked straight towards Golden Hoop Number 6 until the two stood one meter apart.

"I haven't even repaid you for the time you helped me out with my sister's matter. Now I owe you one more," Garen said while somewhat embarrassed.

"What a coincidence then. I have something I need to trouble you with. If you help me out, I'll count it as one favor repaid. How's that?" Golden Hoop Number 6 asked jokingly.

"What trouble? However, I will have to recuperate for a while first."

Golden Hoop Number 6 took a look at Garen's sorry state and injuries. "Of course I will wait until you have recovered. I'm in no hurry either."

"Then no problem!" Garen agreed.

"Come on, I'll arrange a car to send you all back. It's unwise to stay here for too long. Celestial Circle Gate has a huge influence here. I can only remove one of their assistants."

"Sir, we discovered the body of Tenstar Ni from Celestial Circle Gate out back," a military officer reported after walking to Golden Hoop Number 6.

"Oh?" Golden Hoop Number 6 widened his eyes in shock, then looked at Garen with a half-smile. "You're good, you!"

Garen smiled wryly and said, "Please stop saying that. I almost died. Did I give you more trouble?"

For some reason, he vaguely felt that the brown uniformed soldiers around him were looking at him in awe.

Golden Hoop Number 6 realized it too, and smiled.

"We practitioners of martial arts, regardless of our characters and personalities, will easily become impulsive due to the continually abundant and strong Qi and blood within our bodies. You have no idea how a military unit with stronger physicality and true strength will cause more trouble. Constantly having a strong power in the body without being able to use it developes into a mentally repressive grievance, so they will easily become impulsive. Since you've killed him, that's that. Celestial Circle Gate won't fall out with me for such a small character anyway. You have been too inhibited, so this release is also a good conditioning."

"Stronger people will have problems after being mentally repressed for too long?" Garen had a weird expression. He vaguely recalled Eldest Senior Sister's insane look.

"Indeed so. Of course, there are those with strong spiritual attainment who are able to disregard such situations, but they are a rare minority." Golden Hoop Number 6 turned around and said, "Come on, let's talk on the move."

Garen nodded. "Let me explain to my Junior Brothers and Sisters first."

"Very well."

Chapter 95: The Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a small building by the road, an old man and a girl stood by the window inside a dark room and looked down through the opening in the curtains.

"They are people from the Special Forces. Why are they here?" the white-haired old man asked confusedly. "Who is that military officer?"

"I've seen him once at a banquet. I think he is Colonel Su Lin of the Special Forces. Rumor has it that he's a useless playboy who only got a firm standing in the army because of his parents. Why is he here instead of in Hotel Pleasant fooling around with women?" the pale girl asked, equally confused. "Looks like he's a friend of that Garen. Does he intend to buy a hatchet man?"

"A playboy giving up pleasure activities to lead a troop to this suburb for a rescue mission? Looks like they have a close relationship," the old man said in a low voice.

"I know about Su Lin's situation. His parents spoiled him. Whatever he wanted, they would find it for him by whatever means necessary. He has an elder brother managing the family business who is also very fond of him. He is considered the darling of the Mobius family, but he did not live up to expectations. He didn't apply himself to anything and only knew how to indulge in pleasure-seeking activities," the girl said sarcastically in a hushed tone. "I didn't expect White Cloud Gate to be involved with this guy. They should consider themselves lucky."

"It's great that the power of Celestial Circle Gate has been curtailed slightly. We put in so much effort, but they only want to contribute a little. It's so unfair." The old man started smiling.

"But this Garen has concealed himself well. Su Lin's character has always been arrogant, so spoiled that he doesn't allow anyone to disobey him. He's very difficult to get along with. It's unexpected that he would be able to hit it off with this Garen. Su Lin is famous for being imperious and domineering." The girl looked at Garen and Su Lin downstairs as they chatted happily then boarded a black car under the protection of bodyguards and left. The other White Cloud Gate disciples, along with the disciples from two other sects behind them, boarded other cars and left together.

"Come on. White Cloud Gate is temporarily safe and it's even protected two other sects. It's impossible for us to act here." The old man turned to move away from the window.

"Wait! What's that?" the girl suddenly shouted in a muted tone. Her gaze was fixed on a body being carried out from behind the distant building. "Is…is that Tenstar Ni? It can't be!"

"What?!" The old man raced back to the window and looked down. The body of Tenstar Ni was being carried into a car by a few soldiers.

In that instant, a chill went down their spines and they exchanged a look.

Tenstar Ni was dead!

"It seems that we have underestimated this Garen from White Cloud Gate…" the old man spoke slowly in his baritone voice. "Fortunately, we didn't go down there. Otherwise, we might not have been able to come back alive."

"The strongest man from the Southern Twelve Gates… is indeed extraordinary! He is already eligible to be ranked as a Grandmaster of Combat," the pale girl murmured. She pulled out a rolled up map from her front pocket and gently opened it. "I'll make a note of it now!"

On the white map was an enlarged image of all of the nearby provinces. There were already a few red dots marked at different spots on the map. The pale girl bit her index finger until it bled and forcefully imprinted a blood mark on Galantia Province, which contained Huaishan City.

"I can't believe that we managed to witness the entire process of a Grandmaster of Combat breaking though the limits of the human body during this trip. The time spent can now be considered worthwhile," the old man said as he started to get slightly emotional.

*****************

On the yellow-green plains, a winding pale yellow road stretched into the distance like a long, thin piece of yellow ribbon.

A black motorcade rolled along on the road. The motorcade consisted entirely of black luxury sedans. Delicate patterns decorated the car bodies while some protracted sections even had extensions of elegant hollowed floral ornaments.

There was even a hook-like dark golden ornament erected on the hood of the second black car: it represented the number "6."

There was ample space inside the car and two youths sat in the rear passenger seats. The youth on the left had flaming-red hair and a handsome face. He wore a brown military uniform with a colonel-rank insignia, was fiddling with a lighter in his hand, and had the temperament of a frivolous playboy. The aloof and serious military uniform seemed mismatched on him.

The other person had purple hair and dark red eyes. He wore a loose white shirt, his face was calm, and he exuded an aura of peace and serenity. His eyebrows were a strange reddish-black since his original black eyebrows had been replaced by two scars. This added a sense of mystery to him.

These two fellows were Golden Hoop Number 6 and Garen traveling on their way back.

Garen turned to look out the window at the yellow-green plains that flashed past. A breeze was blowing and the grass rippled like creased waves. "How should I address you?" he suddenly asked.

Golden Hoop Number 6 snapped the lighter shut. "Just call me Su Lin. To be honest, you and I, we really… uhm, what's that Eastern phrase? Have serendipity! Yes, serendipity. Actually, I didn't intentionally help you the last time. It was by chance that I encountered that incident and it just so happened that I was in a temper, so I dealt with it straightaway. This time, I was busy with another matter when I heard about your situation, so I decided to help you out while I was at it. What's this, if not serendipity?"

"I thought you would say you rushed over deliberately to help me." Garen shook his head and smiled. "You're really honest."

"Honesty is my virtue." Golden Hoop Number 6, Su Lin, chuckled. "This time, White Cloud Gate should be in big trouble right? Need my help?"

"We're indeed in big trouble, but it's a relatively small matter. The main problem is my Senior Sister…" Garen's expression turned grim at the thought of it. Eldest Senior Sister had always been kind to him. Although she had a strange temper, he didn't expect her to betray the sect.

"Regarding your Eldest Senior Sister, I do have some news. She has gone to Behemoth Gate." Su Lin stopped smiling and whispered, "Behemoth Gate… that's a really vexing organization. Even though both your Methods and Secret Martial Arts share the same namesake, their strength is unimaginably powerful."

"Behemoth Gate?" Garen pondered. "Are they as powerful as Celestial Circle Gate?"

"Roughly the same." Su Lin frowned. "The background of Celestial Circle Gate is too strong. They have many alumni disciples in the upper ranks of the federal army and the government. As the strongest sect in the South, there is even a special full brigade in the Confederation specifically trained and led by them."

"An entire brigade…" Garen's head throbbed. He knew the meaning of "brigade." A complete brigade had at least tens of thousands of well-trained soldiers. This was a relatively strong force even in the context of the entire Confederation. Let alone a "special" brigade.

Su Lin took a look at him and continued, "Additionally, many alumni of Celestial Circle Gate have joined the National Security Division. They have plenty of experts like Tenstar Ni."

Garen narrowed his eyes, carefully masking the shock he felt.

Su Lin continued regardless, "But fortunately you have finally reached a new level." He suddenly smiled. "Not everyone can attain the level of Grandmaster of Combat. Congratulations, Garen."

"The level of Grandmaster of Combat?" It was the first time Garen had ever heard of it.

"Yes." Su Lin glanced at the female soldier driving. "This is now an open secret. Your master was probably worried that you would be distracted by this status. That's why he didn't want to tell you."

He paused, then continued, "A so-called Grandmaster of Combat is a martial arts practitioner who is able to train their physical body to the extent of the human limit. Everyone who has become a Grandmaster of Combat possesses tempered skills, a strong body, and represents the extreme pinnacle of humankind. Every Grandmaster of Combat has a quality that they excel at, just like how you are exceptional in your Strength and Defense."

Garen was silent for a while. "If what you say is true—that I have entered the level of Grandmaster of Combat—why is it that against experts at the level of Tenstar Ni, I can only handle one at a time at best?"

"That is because you haven't properly solidified. In the examples of Grandmasters of Combat that I know of, each and every one of them has a tough physical quality and vitality. Their ability to recover is shocking and the true strength that they wield is far beyond the limit that a normal human being can achieve. Simply put, Grandmasters of Combat are top experts who are one league ahead of average martial arts practitioners and represent the extreme limit of the human body’s advancement," Su Lin answered formally. "If my estimation is correct, once you return, you will enter an explosive growth phase in the enhancement of your true strength."

Garen slowly nodded. What he did not say, however, was that he was already experiencing this enhancement. During the process of fighting his way over here, he had sensed his body become easier to control and using his skills felt more natural. Occasionally, a flood of combat experience would instinctively surface and he would land a phenomenal strike.

"In that case, you should know a few experts at this level?" Garen asked in a low voice.

"Indeed I do. There are 42 people who can be considered Grandmasters of Combat and these are only the ones on-record. There are probably more off the record, but there should be about 80 people in total. They are the strongest group of people in the entire Confederation! Normal firearms have no effect on them and only especially powerful firearms can harm them."

"80 people… How many people are there in the Confederation?" Garen didn't expect there to be so many more peak experts.

"The result of last year's population census was 160 million people. In other words, combined with the older generation of Grandmasters of Combat, you are one in two million. But don't fret, among these 80 people, more than 50 are senior people from the previous generation. They are advanced in age, most of them have retreated to a life of seclusion, and no one knows how many of them are still alive. The active individuals are the Grandmasters of Combat who have emerged in the past 50 years, which total to approximately 30 people. And that's the amount when you count everyone on- and off-record."

Su Lin held the lighter, then repeatedly lit it and put it out again. "Based on the information we have gathered, there are probably 10 Grandmasters of Combat scattered throughout the 13 provinces of the Confederation. Five are from Celestial Circle Gate representing the Southern Alliance and five from the Northern Alliance. It's evenly matched, but I have a feeling that this has been deliberately decided by both parties in conference. It's too much of a coincidence that both sides have the exact same total of five people."

"Five people huh?" Garen started contemplating. "By my count, these five people should be from Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword. What about Andrela?"

Chapter 96: The Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I don’t know. I haven’t seen him in full force, so no one knows his exact ability. But, compared to Tenstar Ni, he should be at the Grandmaster of Combat level. You have to be careful. He is still a novice, so he isn’t considered a Grandmaster of Combat yet. Also, there are at least two or three Grandmasters of Combat within the older generations of Celestial Circle Gate and they are a force to be reckoned with. With Tenstar Ni’s age, he was one of the hopefuls to become a Grandmaster of Combat. Unfortunately, you killed him." Su Lin sympathized

"If he didn’t die, I would have died." Garen was speechless as he remembered the last fight with Tenstar Ni. If Tenstar Ni had not been so foolish and had ignored his big mouth, Garen would not have had to kill him. Fighters at this level were not ordinary people that would be severely hurt after one punch. The resilience they possessed meant that they were well trained to take hits. Their stamina was also incredible. If they were to advance another level…

A slight tension gripped Garen’s head, but it was more of an odd blood boiling passion. It was the expectation of facing a worthy opponent. Martial artists, especially novice practitioners, all possessed a fervent passion for combat.

Although Garen had a lot less training time compared to regular martial artists, he was no different. His passion for the arts was as feverish as anyone else.

From the first moment that he chose the path of martial arts, he did not want to use his special ability to expand his social presence. Instead, he chose to push himself to the limit and become a true martial artist. He wanted to witness the peak that the human body could achieve and challenge to those limits. Fortunately, he had the aid of his special ability.

He knew his capabilities better than anyone else. He was neither gifted nor talented. Without his special ability, it would have been difficult to enter the martial arts world in the first place. Since he was a normal and ordinary person without any talents, he had to stay dedicated. It was impossible for an individual to achieve excellence in everything and separated effort would only result in overall mediocrity. For example, take two geniuses at the starting point. If one only focused on science while the other studied everything and anything on a whim, the difference would be obvious after a short amount of time.

As for the one in a century type of genius that could master anything, if that kind of talent only focused on one subject, the heights that could be achieved would be unimaginable. The truth was that with the waves of scientific advancement around the world, subjects were being separated into finer areas of study and it would be nearly impossible to master everything. From the start, Garen knew the type of path he wanted to take.

"Are there any Grandmaster of Combat level fighters near me?" Garen recollected his thoughts and asked with his voice lowered.

Su Lin retracted his lighter and gave it a thought. "There is one. Beside Galantia in the Eliza Province, there is a Grandmaster of Combat called the White Eagle Holy Fist, also known as Palosa. He lives in seclusion at the Skylark Mountain Waterfall. If my father didn’t mention it once, I would not have known that an older generation Grandmaster of Combat lived there. The toxic gas and miasma are so thick that normal people would not be able to enter Skylark Mountain. Even the herb gatherers are not willing to venture to this vast and sparsely populated location.

"There are no others?" When Garen heard this name, he knew that this person was an older generation Grandmaster of Combat that was indifferent to worldly fame and fortune. The chance of conflict with him would be minuscule.

"There are none. The majority of the Grandmasters of Combat are concentrated within Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword. The heads of Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword are both older generation Grandmasters of Combat, but I don’t know about the others."

"Do you know the background of Behemoth Gate?" Garen changed the topic to ask.

"Behemoth Gate is a nefarious organization that secretly recruits and trains young talents. They are mysterious in nature and I don’t really know too much either, but they are certainly not weak by any means. You have to be careful." Su Lin turned serious. "After you go back this time, you’ll have to reorganize the internal structure of White Cloud Gate and take control of the situation. Although Master Fei did not suffer a serious injury, this injury will impact his martial arts due to his old age. White Cloud Gate will be dependent on you."

"I know." Garen nodded.

**********************

Galantia Province Huaishan City.

Among the forests in the rural areas, the dense and green trees had already recovered from the misery of winter. The morning sunshine pierced through the leaves and illuminated the ground. With the moist air and tiny drops of dew, the forest emitted a refreshing vibe.

Deep within the forest.

A square and dark looking courtyard rested quietly within a circle of trees. Green colored vines covered the black stone tiles.

The courtyard was enclosed by a few two story buildings and slanted stone stairs led up to an entrance on the side. The stairs were a shade of black with moss slightly peeking out from the top corner. The passage of time was evident.

A bald man with a beer belly stood on top of the stairs. Fat protruded out of his face. He wore a black suit with a white shirt hanging on his shoulder and his hands were on his waist as he took deep breaths. It looked like he was performing a morning routine.

It was evident that he did not cleanly shave as stubble covered his face and neck. The hair from his sideburns connected to his beard and it was impossible to differentiate which was which. While the man was doing this morning routine, a short-haired man slowly strolled up from the stairs.

"Mr. Bouvini." The man walked beside the bald guy and greeted him with a lowered voice.

"Mhmm, do you have any news?" The bald guy shook his upper body and seemed like he was exercising his waist.

"All the other shareholders support your attempt to take command. It’s just that a few key assets are only known by Dojo Master Fei. The dojo’s relationship with the governor would make this difficult to handle," the man reported in an undertone.

"I heard that the White Cloud Gate lot safely escaped from Celestial Circle’s territory? They are on their way back?" the bald Bouvini asked.

"Yes. I don’t have the exact intel as no information has leaked. It is believed that the military has intervened and suspended any information. It’s believed that Dojo Fei was unconscious during the competition and will not recover within a short period of time. Even if he manages to recover, his power will drop by a few levels because of his age," the man hastily explained. "Mr. Bouvini, this is the perfect opportunity. If this opportunity slips away, it will become impossible to control White Cloud Gate’s assets."

"The other three shareholders have the same intention?" Bouvini asked in an undertone.

"Yes."

A thoughtful expression appeared on Bouvini’s face. "Then go prepare first. We have to welcome the dojo’s triumphant return."

"Understood, I’ll get right on it." The man thought about it before reaching a sudden realization. He nodded and left.

********************

Three days later. In the morning.

In front of the gate of Huaishan City’s White Cloud Dojo, a fleet of black silver wave cars came to a gradual stop beside the road. The scene caught the attention of pedestrians and they occasionally peeked over. This kind of luxurious sedan was difficult to come by in Huaishan City. Now there suddenly was a fleet of five such cars, which garnered even more attention.

The car doors opened one by one. A simple stretcher transporting the comatose Fei Baiyun was carried out from the back. Collin and Simon carefully guarded the stretcher as it traveled toward the gate. Garen and Golden Loop Number 6 Su Lin exited their car. They raised their heads to look at the overhanging banner that named the dojo.

"We are finally back." Garen let out a long sigh of relief.

"Senior Brother Garen."

Rampas’s voice sounded from the other side.

Rampas and delicate girl walked over.

"We are finally back in Huaishan. It’s also time for Seven Moon Gate and Circling Dance Gate to depart. We are grateful for Senior Brother’s help this time, so here is our contact information and address. If there is anything in need of us, we will do everything we can!" He passed over a slip of paper.

"Wait a moment. How are the two masters doing?" Garen took the paper and looked behind the pair of disciples. On two other stretchers, the two unconscious gate masters rested.

"The military doctors have examined them and it’s not a big problem. The unconsciousness seems to be the result of a special technique, so they just need some time before they naturally wake up," Rampas explained. "Also, we have a contact in Huaishan City and we can arrange our own transportation. There is no need to worry about us."

"That’s good. In that case, so long." Garen nodded.

"Goodbye Senior Brother Garen." Rampas gestured before he left with his disciples.

"Senior brother Garen, if you encounter any issues, don’t forget about the Circling Dance Gate. I am Marianne!" The delicate looking girl smiled sincerely before also carrying her master away and departing in the other direction with her fellow disciples. This group met up with a few other female disciples that had heard the news ahead of time and had already been waiting.

Garen retracted his gaze. As he was about to head into the dojo, Su Lin suddenly whispered to him, "We just received intel that the strongest gate out of the Southern Twelve Gates, Murry Iron Chain Gate, was destroyed by Andrela." With a serious expression, Su Lin said in a lowered voice, "The Celestial Circle Gate heard that Tenstar Ni was killed, which angered their management. So they immediately retaliated and Murry Iron Chain Gate became the victim. Andrela took the lead and officially intervened in the incident where the Southern Twelve Gates were challenged. They eliminated Murry Iron Chain Gate from top to bottom."

Slightly shocked by the news, Garen responded, "No wonder. Celestial Circle Gate has had the intent to take over the Southern Twelve Gates for a long time and this incident was only an excuse. What about the Crimson Sand Sword?"

"Crimson Sand Sword is not reacting right now. It looks like they made a pact with Celestial Circle Gate." With a frown, Su Lin said, "This is going to problematic, very problematic. I haven’t managed to come up with a conclusion, so the hidden killer might be someone else."

"Who is it?"

"An emerging organization called the Black Mark Association. It’s rumored that they are in an alliance with Crimson Sand Sword and Celestial Circle Gate to end the separated situation in the southern area. They want to form three leading gates to focus their forces against the northern area."

Garen was silent for a moment before he spoke, "You can go back now. I’ll take care of this on my own. I already owe you a lot, so I’ll handle it this time."

"On your own? Can you handle it?!" Su Lin asked petulantly.

"You don’t have to be involved in this situation," Garen said emotionlessly. "There are no other solutions right now. Since Andrela will be here eventually, there is no way I can avoid this. My master is here and so is my family."

Su Lin stared at Garen fervently, as if meeting Garen for the first time, and it took him a while to open his mouth.

"You are afraid that you are going to cause me trouble? With just these words, I am your friend! Don’t worry, my troubles are far greater and bigger than yours. If I am by your side, not only would you have to be afraid of the Grandmasters of Combat that can strike at any time, but the assassination organization might also cause you trouble. Are you afraid!?"

"You really want me to answer with the arrogance that I am not afraid?" Garen was flabbergasted. "That with a background as fearsome as yours, my problem were bigger than yours? No one would believe me if I said something like that!"

Su Lin shook his head and led the way. He opened the dojo’s door and walked in. "Let’s talk inside. My problems are far greater than yours."

A bitter smile appeared on his face.

Garen immediately followed.

Chapter 97: Crisis and Secret Methods 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the next ten minutes, Garen arranged for the doctor and nurse to take care of his master, calmed down the slightly frantic disciples and trainees, and finally let the juniors go to rest. He then asked one of the disciples to find a quiet room to discuss everything with Su Lin in detail.

The place they were led to was decorated with wooden furniture which gave it a classical vibe. Redwood walls and floor, a wooden table and chair, even the tea cups were made of redwood.

The two of them sat down across from each other. Two wooden cups, with steam rising slowly from them, were placed in the middle of the redwood table.

Garen gently touched the missing edge of the wooden table.

"This time, a lot of the disciples have left. Plenty of places look torn down which are obvious signs of the time when senior sister left. Now the elder senior brother is gone, too, and senior brother is prohibited from leaving. The entire gate feels empty and deserted… But that’s fine, let’s not talk about it. Tell me about what is troubling you."

Su Lin grabbed the tea cup with a bitter smile. "This is why I need your help. To be honest, when I found you in the first place, I had the intention of looking for a bodyguard."

"I don’t care about your intentions. The fact that you helped me out twice cannot be understated." Garen interrupted him to stop him from talking. "Tell me about your troubles. I can’t believe that with the force of the organization they can’t protect you?"

"Golden Loop possesses force only on paper. I’ve gotten into a conflict with an assassin organization, and one of the strongest ones in the world, Duskdune Shura." Su Lin’s face was distressed. "As to how I got into a conflict with them, I don’t even know myself. All I know is that starting from next summer, they will officially take action."

"Duskdune Shura? Are they powerful?" Garen asked in an undertone. "I’m not familiar with these things, you know."

"Let me make a comparison for you. Imagine them as disciples from the Celestial Circle Gate with mastery in weapons, special techniques, combat mastery, assassination, plus they never fight in the open and always look for an opportunity to deceive. I’m not afraid of them myself, but I’m worried about my family. They don’t have the ability to defend themselves and can only rely on the protection of others," Su Lin said with impotence clear in his voice. "I’ve used all kinds of excuses to find impeccable protection for my parents, but it’s just not enough for my sister."

"Does this Duskdune Shura have any Grandmasters of Combat?" Garen took a sip of the tea, not feeling frightened by the information.

"Yes." Su Lin looked at him. "It’s an elite Grandmaster of Combat that has successfully assassinated ten other Grandmasters of Combat. The organization’s leader is called Duskdune Shura. One of the top two elite fighters in the most recent documentation. Based on it, he is also part of the Immortal Palace Alliance."

Garen’s hand shook slighlty, and the tea almost spilled out of the cup.

"It’s the Immortal Palace Alliance again." He originally thought that this organization was strong but secretive, yet they reappeared again.

"Let’s not worry about Duskdune Shura for now. That can all be taken care of in the future. The most crucial task is to be ready for the Celestial Circle Gate, or else I would not be able to survive this year, let alone the next one."

"You are right." Su Lin tasted the tea, and his eyebrows furrowed into a frown. "The tea is quite nice, but whoever made it definitely didn’t possess skill."

He raised his head to look at Garen.

"The Celestial Circle Gate is indeed powerful. However, everything must follow the same rule. Their force is not powerful enough to break it."

"You are implying?" Garen locked his vision on Su lin as he asked with uncertainty.

"I’ll use the name of the military to let my dad announce that you’ll be my sister’s Wushu teacher," Su Lin answered calmly.

"Wushu teacher. That’s two birds with one stone." Garen’s expression turned peaceful as well. "My guess was also similar. Not only does it preserve the White Cloud Gate, but it also achieves what you wish for."

"However, before this, my father would need to personally pressure the Celestial Circle Gate. This cannot be done in an instant and will take around ten days. You’ll have to stay strong during this period."

"Ten days?" His head lowered, Garen stared at the teacup on the table.

Within it, the slightly red tea gradually spread out in waves to the edges of the cup. "Good, I also want to know how powerful the renowned top fighter from the south is."

"Confidence is good." Su Lin smiled.

The two of them sat quietly on their seats without speaking a word. They silently thought about their next steps.

Knock! Knock! Knock!

Someone was tapping on the door.

"Come in."

Garen looked in the direction of the door.

It gently opened. Collin, who had changed into a white outfit, came in and stood beside Garen.

"Senior Brother, Bouvini, who controls the assets, is here."

"Bouvini?" Garen quickly recalled this person’s identity. "Tell him that I suffered a severe injury and will require healing in peace. Please ask him to take care of master’s assets."

"Ok, Senior Brother." Collin nodded as he curiously peaked at Su Lin who sat across from him.

"In this case, I’ll leave as well. I need to head back to take care of the problem with your identity and convince my father as early as possible. It would help in alleviating the severity of this incident. However, this will only be a temporary solution to your conflict with the Celestial Circle Gate. You killed the talent of their younger generation. With how those older guys act as if they’re on top of the world, they will not let you go unscathed."

"I know, even if they want to resolve the problem, this incident was a detrimental hit to their reputation. It cannot be easily concluded for that alone." Garen was fully aware of the situation he was in.

"I’ll head back as soon as possible."

"I owe you for this." Garen bowed at Su Lin.

"Don’t worry." Su Lin smiled and gently stood up, leaving quietly.

"Lead Mr. Su Lin on his way out," Garen notified the disciple at the door.

"Yes."

Kacha.

The door gradually closed.

Garen let out a long sigh. He sat on the chair when all of a sudden a mixture of emotions overwhelmed him.

"I originally thought that I was just leading an exchange gathering. After it, I would come back and continue searching for the old man’s cause of death. But to my surprise, the Immortal Palace Alliance and the Celestial Circle Gate are connected somehow. There is no way that this is all a coincidence that the moment I was attacked, my master was also injured. The Southern Twelve Gates are in a dangerous situation right now.

"The Celestial Circle Gate… The Immortal Palace Alliance… An organization of psychokinetics… An organization of martial adepts... How is everything connected?"

He felt like he was about to be drawn into a whirlpool of complexities and troubles.

The Celestial Palace Gate was creating a force to eliminate the smaller gates. The Southern Twelve Gates were the first victims, and soon the other gates would be in dire danger as well.

Garen slowly stood up. He walked to the empty part of the room and gently made a standard White Cloud Combat Arts move.

Time passed minute by minute.

Gradually, his furrowed eyebrows began to relax. His spirit echoed the blood flow within his body as it cycled around. He felt calm.

"All the time, I’ve been reactive in dealing with the unexpected incidents that kept occurring. I’ve been flowing with the tide, uanble to do what I want."

His whole body began to shake as if he was a tumbler. Left and right, front and back, as he kept on swaying.

"I have a genuine interest in martial arts, so I’ll have to put all my effort into it. The Celestial Gates, Andrela, Sylphalan."

Garen didn’t know how everything came falling down to where it was now. All of the incidents weren’t caused by him, but he was a casualty caught in the middle of a landslide.

Sylphalan from the Immortal Palace Alliance was because of the old man, while the Celestial Circle Gate was because of his master at the White Cloud Gate. Without realizing it, he was suddenly surrounded by powerful enemies.

"The Celestial Circle Gate won’t allow the Southern Twelve Gates to have any force of resistance left." Garen knew it well. "The crusade on the Southern Twelve Gates is inevitable now. I just don’t know how involved Andrela is in all of this."

His body came to a sudden halt as if everything paused.

Peng!

A crisp but deafening sound.

Garen’s right fist thrust forward, and a white trail appeared in the air. It was the mark left by the screeching streams of air.

He remembered the combat techniques he used. The wrong and ineffective moves were being gradually eliminated, and only the practical combo moves remained.

He suddenly recalled the explosive move he performed at the beginning in the Celestial Circle Gate’s ring.

One single move to defeat the challenger, and also injure the Grandmaster of Combat and himself. Though, the opponent’s injury was much more critical.

At that moment he only thought about unleashing all of his power. The blood qi ball in the middle of his body automatically flowed out and formed all his power into one. It then exploded into an unbelievable amount of power.

He was in a state where instinct and anger mixed together and using his body, in an instance, they gave birth to a new move.

He tried to relive that moment.

"If I could master this power so it would be at my command, my sudden explosiveness would increase to another level."

Garen closed his eyes and stood in the middle of the room. His hands continuously moved to mimic that explosive move.

The screeching sound of wind breaking echoed through the air. His speed continued to increase. So did his power.

Suddenly, his right arm pushed forward.

Clap!

It made a sound similar to hands clapping.

In the direction his palm pushed toward, the curtains flew back as if a gust of wind had just passed by.

Garen stopped with a look of disappointment.

"Still feels like something is missing compared to last time. Unfortunate. I wish there were more Antiques of Tragedy."

The Antiques of Tragedy were still his best assurance of improvement.

Within a year and a half, he successfully trained from a novice martial adept to the level of a Grandmaster of Combat. His power couldn't be undermined.

He had mastered the White Cloud Fundamental Secret Method to perfection. In other words, with his explosive fists’ level, it was the highest level anyone had ever achieved. There was nowhere to advance further.

The White Cloud Gate wasn’t like other powerful gates that possessed more Wushu moves. Mammoth Secret Techniques could only be considered as third tier at best.

"With my current ability, I’m no match for Andrela. The difference was obvious. Even if both of us are Grandmasters of Combat, the secret methods we use are drastically different."

Garen pondered as he chugged the tea.

"There are only two ways: the Antiques of Tragedy or a stronger secret technique. With my special ability, as long as I meet the criteria, I could learn it easily."

His eyes brightened as he thought of something.

"Learn easily. Since the White Cloud Gate’s Fundamental Secret Method cannot meet my needs, I’ll find an even lower tier secret method. Perhaps below the third tier, the even worse fourth tier, the lowest tier secret method. With my physical condition and experience, I could easily meet its requirements! Within a short amount of time, those fourth tier secret methods could improve my combat techniques significantly!"

Chapter 98: Crisis and Secret Martial Arts 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen made up his mind. He remembered seeing low-level Secret Martial Arts in the library of the White Cloud Dojo. Although he didn’t see too many of those, it would be enough for him.

No matter how weak a secret technique was, there had to be something special about it.

Garen opened the door and walked towards the library. He did not see many people around in the Dojo; the place was no longer busy. There were only about seven or eight people wandering around, and he could still see the blood stains on the floor.

Garen didn’t really care, and he headed straight to the library. It took him several minutes to reach the entrance and notice that the old bald man, who guarded the gate, was already gone. He could see the signs of the fight from the walls, and he knew the Elder was fraught with grim possibilities.

Garen was a bit relieved after he found the method to improve, but he became depressed again after seeing the scene before him.

He entered the library, and everything inside was still well organized. Although Senior Sister betrayed the White Cloud Gate, she did not touch any of the low-level Secret Martial Arts since she probably had already read everything in the library.

He closed the door, lit an oil lamp, and started to check the books on the shelves. It only took him several minutes to find all the low-level Secret Martial Arts. Garen put them down on a desk that was used for making copies and sat down. He kept the oil lamp on the side for light.

There were four books on the desk:

Iron Body, Dark Iron Palm, Lark Blade and Flame Fist.

Those Secret Martial Arts were common and almost all the Dojos had them. They were usually taught to the normal disciples, but the White Cloud Gate had the Explosive Fist Arts as the basic and the four low-level Secret Martial Arts were just kept in the library as part of the collection.

The four Secret Martial Arts were very similar to the Red Hand Fist Garen encountered before. They could not be put into skill combos, and it would take him a very long time to master them, so the benefit wouldn’t justify the cost.

Although they were put in the library, disciples read them just for fun. Secret Martial Arts like the four could be found anywhere, and they were just like the Iron Tunic that was in almost all the martial arts novels.

Garen grabbed the Iron Body and opened it:

‘Iron Body can increase one’s body defense. It is an average Secret Martial Arts that can be learnt by taking hits while maintaining a special way of breathing. It is easy to learn, but it takes a long time to master. Five years to complete the Level One Mastery, 10 years to complete the Level Two Mastery, and 15 years to master it. If one could master the Iron body, his body would become as hard as iron, and he would be able to resist small caliber pistols.’

Garen read through the instructions, but did not find them important and quickly finished the book. It was short, and the training method did not need to be paired with drugs. There were no complex techniques involved, and the person did not need to be talented. The only requirement was the will to handle all the pain during the long training years.

The most important thing in this whole book was the special breathing technique.

Garen remembered everything quickly and put the book down. "That’s why it’s called low-level Secret Martial Arts…"

He then finished the other three books, and all of them required a lot of time for one to master. Disciples needed to spend at least five to seven years on the Level One Mastery of those arts. Even more so, Flame Fist required eight years for the Level One Mastery. It had four levels in total, and the required time doubled for each level, which meant it would take 64 years for one to finish the last one.

"One won’t become any stronger if he can’t master one Secret Martial Art before the age of 25. No one is going to spend 120 years to master the Flame Fist. No wonder no one touches these low-level Secret Martial Arts…" Garen wasn’t too happy with what he found, but he still finished all four books.

He did not realize it was already afternoon.

Garen closed his eyes, and he could clearly see the skill bar of the light red statuses. He thought for a second, and slowly the four low-level Secret Martial Arts’ names appeared on the skill bar:

Iron Body: Not Started.

Dark Iron Palm: Not Started.

Lark Blade: Not Started.

Flame Fist: Not Started.

Various signs appeared behind the four Secret Martial Arts, and those signs told Garen about the requirements for each of them. Only Lark Blade required relatively high Agility, but it was still within the range that a normal person could reach. Garen could easily meet the requirements of all four.

"The Lark Blade is an Agility Secret Martial Art and requires external support. It doesn’t fit my style. I guess I will start with Iron Body."

He wanted to use his special ability to see if he could speed up the training process.

Garen’s special ability could boost up his learning speed significantly. He tried studying history the last time he applied potential points to Intelligence, and he could easily memorize everything he saw. As long as his Intelligence was high enough, and there were no external restrictions to it, he could learn the subject at an incredible speed.

He wanted to try it on the Martial Arts. It would be very helpful for him if it worked the same as when he was studying.

The Level One Mastery of the Iron Body required the special breathing technique from the book. Garen needed to imagine himself as an inflated balloon, and once his skin turned grey, he would be able to start the Level One Mastery.

Huff.

Garen slowly inhaled as the book said. He needed to inhale once and exhale nine times in a specific rhythm.

It would take him 20 minutes to finish one set of inhaling and exhaling.

He stood up and started practicing the special breathing technique beside the desk.

The first time he could feel his muscles and skin tighten, and they also became denser. Garen was excited about the change and decided to start the second try right away. His muscles and skin tightened again.

His skin turned red on the third try, and he felt like it was extremely tight.

He tried the breathing technique six times in a row and felt relaxed after the last try. His skin’s temperature was very high, and he felt like he’d just left a hot bath.

He closed his eyes and looked at the Iron Body skill:

Iron Body: Level One (Two Levels).

"I knew it! It changed!"

Garen opened his eyes and tore off his collar. He could see his skin turning darker. Although its hardness hadn’t reached the level of metal, he believed he would finish the Level One Mastery after a bit more training.

"It’s valid!" Garen hit his chest with his fist.

Bam!

Besides the normal sound of flesh, there was the sound like hitting a piece of metal.

"It’s definitely working. I wonder if I can reach the next level."

Garen tried to use the special breathing method again. However, nothing happened after more than ten tries. He knew he needed to do the hit training and that the breathing technique alone would not do much, but he just wanted to give it a try.

"I easily learned the fundamentals after I fulfilled all the requirements, but why can’t I apply the method to the basic combat techniques and the basic sword skills… Wait! I already knew the basics of the skills when I was trying to level them up, which means this ability only works when I try to learn the Level One Mastery of the skills or fundamentals. Maybe it only works with the theories that only need to be memorized?"

Garen recalled the days when he was learning the identification skill with the old man. He had studied it step by step, and his ability had only worked with the first book he read. His identification skill did not level up after finishing the other books.

His identification skill never leveled up after that. Although he studied a lot and acquired a good amount of knowledge, that skill was still at the first level.

"I’m probably correct about this."

Garen was now sure about his guess. His special ability could only help him quickly learn the basics after the requirements were met, which was still extremely helpful when he used it on Secret Martial Arts.

No matter how weak a Secret Martial Art was, it would still be much stronger than any regular martial art. He could easily finish the Level One Mastery of any of the Secret Martial Arts, and those skills would definitely be useful to him.

Garen decided to use his ability to learn more Secret Martial Arts since he wanted to know what would happen after.

"I‘m not sure if Iron Body will help me become stronger, but I can try it later," Garen thought and started to prepare for the Dark Iron Palm.

He did not need any external support to learn the Dark Iron Palm. All he required was to learn a special stance and support it with his consciousness. It was a skill that gathered all the venom in his body into his palms, and then allowed him to use it to poison opponents.

It would take Garen some time, but he started the Level One Mastery with ease. He used the special stance he learned from the book and supported it with his consciousness.

After about two hours, he felt like his hands were paralyzed, and it meant that the venom in his body had gathered into his fingers.

Apparently, the Level One Mastery of the Dark Iron Palm would not do too much for him. He only needed to gather all the venoms from his body into his palms. The more Garen practiced the skill the more venom he would be able to handle.

The technique only had two levels just like the Mammoth Secret Techniques.

The next one he decided to learn was the Flame Fist, which was different from the other ones. Garen could feel the actual effect of the skill, but the feeling was weak, and Iron Body progressed much faster.

It was dark outside when Garen practiced several more times, and most of the disciples had already gone back home. Garen did not eat anything besides breakfast and just stayed in the library the whole day.

"Andrela will be here in ten days. I hope I’ll be able to finish the Level One Mastery during that time," Garen said in a light tone.

He had three different Secret Martial Arts.

He needed to do the strike-resistant training for the Iron Body, and he would be able to finish the entry level after that. The other two needed time and he wasn’t sure if he could finish all the Level One Masteries before Andrela came.

But he was still satisfied with the results. Compared to normal people, his learning speed was already extraordinary.

Chapter 99: Seven Moon Gate

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Since the inception of martial arts, I must be the first one that has trained multiple secret methods at once. A secret method would at least take a couple of years to train and master. The secret method is also martial arts which means that without practice its power would deteriorate due to loss of familiarity. It’s similar to going against the tide. Without a day of practice, three days of effort may go to waste. Without my special ability that can consolidate and reinforce the training results, it would be impossible to train other secret methods.

"The body’s adaptability is like this."

He raised his head and scanned the roof’s edge and the starry night. A bright crest hung in the night’s sky as the moon cast a veil with its light.

"It would be better if I don’t go home now, in case something happens in the near future, and my family will be worried." Garen made up his mind to stay at the dojo.

The news of his return didn’t leak out as only a few select individuals knew about it.

He gently let out a sigh.

The hallway in front of the Dojo’s library was pitch black and silent.

He strolled along the hallway. He had only taken a few steps when he saw a shadow sitting by the right wall.

He walked closer to take a better look.

"Grace?" Garen was surprised by her presence.

The shadow was Grace in a professional office assistant attire. Her graceful legs were covered by a thick layer of stockings and closed together. She was curled into a ball as if she was in a chilling weather.

She subconsciously opened her eyes when she heard the voice and looked at Garen in front of her.

"Garen you are done." Weakness transmitted through her voice. She tried to stand up, but her legs were sore. She lost balance and almost fell.

Garen caught her still in the air, feeling the fragility of her body. It was burning.

Grace grasped onto his body with force.

"Why are you waiting here?" Garen asked gently. "Manuyllton Corporation’s intelligence gathering is impressive. I just got back, and you already know. When did you come here?"

"Afternoon…" Grace’s voice dimmed, and she sounded frailer.

Garen reached a hand to touch her forehead. It was burning.

"You have a fever. There are doctors and nurses with the master. I’ll take you there for a checkup. It shouldn’t be a big problem."

He lifted her by the waist and strode to the room where his master rested.

The dojo was silent. There was no indication of any light, either. The massive dojo appeared hollow and void.

It was a short walk before they reached the room at the corner. A nurse was carrying a bucket of water from the room.

The dim yellow light slipped out past the edge of the door. Simon’s silhouette was dozing off beside the bed.

Garen carried Grace and with a lowered voice asked,"Ms. Nurse, could you please find some cold and fever medicine for my friend?"

"No problem." The nurse was an ordinary girl with small freckles on her face, and she agreed without hesitation. "But don’t bring her into the room. The patient in there has not yet recovered, and he may catch a cold."

"Okay."

"Put me down!" Grace began to resist Garen's hand. Her legs kicked, and her face had a vivid redness to it from the fever, which confused her senses.

Garen shook his head speechlessly as he waited for a while at the door. The nurse he spoke to found another one to arrange a room for Grace. Only then, could Garen find some time and walk into his master’s room.

Simon drooled as he had fallen asleep with his head slanted to the side against the back of the chair.

Garen gently closed the door, but the sound was low enough that it didn’t even wake him up. He walked over and tapped on his shoulder.

"Wooo." Simon slurped up the drool in a hurry. "Se… Senior brother!" When he saw Garen walk in, he was shocked and hastily stood up.

"Your arm is still in a cast, why are you not getting any rest? Go back to your room and sleep!" Garen told him with a stern face while trying to keep his voice steady.

"But the dojo master…" Simon wavered.

"I’ll be here," Garen said. "Master hasn't woken up yet?"

Simon’s face dimmed. "No, not even once. He has been like this since we returned from the Celestial Circle Gate."

"He wasn’t injuried that seriously, what’s going on?" Garen frowned with his eyerbows raised.

"I don’t know, the doctor said that the dojo master’s body is fine. They just don’t know why he is unconscious," Simon replied with an undertone. "The dojo master is going to be okay, right? Senior Brother?" A worrisome expression appeared on his face.

"It’s going to be okay, I am here, right?" Garen patted his shoulder. "Go rest now, I’ll take care of him."

"I have only been here for a bit, Collin was here before." Simon laughed feeling a little embarrassed.

"To be fair, you don’t have to stay here with me," Garen suddenly said. "You are just regular trainees."

"You don’t have to say that! Senior Brother, we have already made up our minds, and we are going to stay at the dojo. Regardless of the results, the dojo has given us too much. This is Collin and I's choice. Carrie is different from us because she still has her parents and brother, so we convinced her to go back. Senior Brother, you won’t blame us for this decision, right?" Simon calmed as he expressed his thoughts.

"Of course not." Garen didn’t know what was the best thing to say at such a moment. "You guys don’t have to do this much."

"Don’t worry, Senior Brother." Simon smiled. "Collin and I are free from worry. It’s the dojo master that has taught us everything. I’ll go back and rest now, the master will depend on you now."

"Mhmm, you can go back." Garen nodded.

He watched Simon slowly left the room and closed the door.

Garen was deep in thought.

Compared to Senior Sister Rosetta, the normal core students were more like master Fei Baiyun’s disciples. During the dojo’s crisis, they didn't choose to leave but instead stayed with the dojo to fight together.

It was in critical times like this, when the dojo had almost fallen apart, that trust could be garnered.

Garen silently sat on the chair Simon had used and looked at the master lying in bed.

"Master, although the dojo is facing the most difficult situation since its inception, there are still some disciples that are worth fighting for and protecting. This is your luck, and our luck."

Despite being here for only one year, he felt a blood connection with Fei Baiyun who had taught him everything he knew. Fei Baiyun spent all his effort to provide him with the best route for growth. Even with Manuyllton Corporation’s incident, he personally stepped in to solve the issue for him.

This time only Grace came. The bodyguards and Cynthia were all gone without a trace. The Corporation had clearly seen that the tide had turned and recalled them. When a ship is sinking, this is the obvious choice.

"If we can go through this crisis together, you shouldn’t disagree with Collin and Simon becoming real disciples, right?" This was his last sentence before letting out a long sigh and closing his eyes to rest.

Fei Baiyun was still sleeping in bed with faint hints breathing. Maybe he had heard what Garen had said, maybe not.

********************

Due to the secret methods’ teaching rules, only disciples could learn.

Fei Baiyun had already announced that he would not teach any disciples. So Garen decided to teach himself. The best candidate was second senior brother Farak, but he was out there trying to assassinate senior sister Rosetta without any information.

Although he was confident in second senior brother’s abilities, Garen was afraid that external forces would be involved.

For the longest time, the difference between the second senior brother and senior sister was minuscule at best. But he had been going easy on her as his force was too explosive without constraint. Thus, he would often lose against Rosetta. It would be different in a life and death situation.

Fights between martial adepts of the same level were also dependent on the feeling that day.

He sat in the master’s room almost until the next morning. Only when a new nurse was about to come in to switch in, did Garen finally leave to train the secret methods.

He walked around the dojo and gained a better understanding of the situation.

Due to the riots in the gate, the majority of the core disciples had left. The lower level students were sent home on vacation. The sub-gates only had people to look after the door. Collin and Simon were the only ones left in the gate.

Only the core disciples knew the crisis the gate was facing. The majority of other students were not aware of the situation. Based on dojo master Fei Baiyun’s reputation, most of them thought that everything would be normal after some time passed. They didn’t know how severe the situation was.

The dojo that had been once filled with over a thousand people now only had less than ten remaining.

Not including Garen, Collin and Simon, only a few workers that had been here for years stayed.

Garen strolled into the dojo while the passing rooms and hallways spoke of the emptiness of the once prosperous White Cloud Gate. Only desolate air and marks of prosperity remained.

Garen left the dojo and ate breakfast at a store nearby. He then ordered some food for the people remaining and asked for it to be delivered to the dojo. He then returned to the Martial Coliseum on the second floor, where he started to train The Iron Body secret method. It only required one more level which needed an external force to aid the training.

The Martial Coliseum had a small room with heavy iron balls hanging from the ceiling. They were meant to train against hard hits.

This was because the White Cloud Gate’s basic Explosive Fist required this condition.

He stood without any robes in the middle of tens of iron balls. They were the size of a human head, and Garen even added spikes on top of them.

The dense iron balls were like urchins that surrounded Garen in the middle.

He inhaled and exhaled before starting to follow the Iron Body’s breathing method.

After a complete cycle, he began furiously pushing the iron balls around him.

Dang! Dang! Dang!

The sound of collision echoed within the room.

Following immediately after, were the sounds of spikes hitting against Garen. The clanking noise rang like metal impacting another piece of metal.

Garen’s skin began to darken to a black color, at the same time as it gained a metallic sheen.

The countless metal balls swung in the room and collided with his body. They would then get pushed back from the force of his body and come back even stronger.

Every metal ball weighed more than ten pounds. With the added force, the force of the collision was at least over 100 pounds. The spikes made the area of collision decrease, which meant that the force Garen’s body received drastically increased.

He only felt a tingling sensation that made him want to scratch the place hit. But he knew this was normal.

He practiced until noon before taking a break to eat. Eat, rest, train. Eat, rest, train. He repeated the same routine again, and again, and again.

Chapter 100: Seven Moon Gate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two days passed by in a glimpse.

Finally.

Dang!

An iron ball with a spike smashed against the side of Garen’s face. However, the crisp metal clanking noise made it sound like the ball collided against a piece of indestructible metal.

Joy flashed across Garen’s eyes as he forced his way out through the waves of iron balls.

"I’ll have to trouble you for a bit."

Collin stood courteously at the corner of the room with a black metal spear in his hand. The spear was as thick as a person’s arm and as long as three metal spears, its tip piercingly sharp.

"Let Grace go first," Collin said, nodding.

"That works too." Garen didn’t seem to be bothered.

The two of them walked out of the practice room and into the empty Martial Coliseum.

Grace was waiting in the middle of the room. She had an assault rifle in her hand. After Garen came out, she looked worried. "Garen, are you sure this is okay?"

"Don’t worry, let’s start." Garen nodded. "Remember to wear a bulletproof vest."

He had asked Grace to find an assault rifle to test his body’s defense. His originally strong body’s condition would require testing to determine its strength after training the Iron Body Technique.

Although Grace had seen Garen’s impeccable physical defense, it was an assault rifle she was holding. The bullets shot from this type of weapon were powerful, piercing and in no way comparable to pistol bullets. She still had her doubts in her mind, but it was for helping Garen to train, so she listened to him.

She wore a full set of bulletproof clothing, with helmet and gloves, while Collin was asked to hide in a small room nearby.

She raised the assault rifle and aimed directly at Garen.

"Should I start?"

"Begin firing."

Garen took a deep breath, and his muscles began to tighten. His entire upper body expanded by a full size as if he was a barbarian with a giant’s blood from the legends. He towered over the 170 centimeter tall Grace.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

The rapid firing echoed through the Martial Coliseum.

Garen’s body exploded with tiny sparks, but they faded in a blink of an eye. The bullet impacts made the sound of metal striking metal.

"Puuuuushhhh!" Garen thrust his palm forward.

He swiped his palm in front of him. The clanking sound was fiercest there.

The noise of bullets colliding came to an abrupt stop.

Grace stared hysterically at Garen, standing not far from her. He calmly extended his hand and faced the ground. A couple bullets dropped down, bouncing lightly up and down.

**************

In the White Gate Martial Coliseum.

Garen stood naked in the middle of the Martial Coliseum.

Collin and a group of hired men held onto the black spear with the tip pointed directly at his abs.

Ahhhhh!

They thrust the spear at Garen at full strength.

They marched forward with the same rhythm as they used all of their strength to push the black metal spear forward. Their speed increased as they got closer and closer.

Dang!

The spear’s tip collided directly with Garen’s abs in a manner of striking a metal block.

Garen’s entire body shook as he retreated two steps backward before quickly regaining his balance. He pushed back against the group of eight people.

The vibration he created forced the men to drop the spear. It almost hit their feet as it fell down.

It was fortunate that Collin managed to grab the spear and slowly put it down.

The men stepped back. They looked at Garen with eyes full of terror, as if he were an alien.

"Congratulations, Senior Brother!" Collin exclaimed, seeing that Garen’s abs were perfectly fine.

"Senior brother’s strength is impeccable! He can definitely beat Andrela’s ass to the ground." Simon laughed hysterically.

Garen shook his head speechlessly. Simon’s arm had not yet to recovered, but his audacity and cocky attitude had already returned.

Grace calmly walked over to wipe away the sweat off of him before giving him some salt water to replenish his body.

Garen took the cup of water and downed it clean. He saw what had happened to him and felt something odd.

"Ok, rest for a little, and then find more people in the afternoon. You guys will attack from all directions."

"Understood."

After seeing everyone’s pressure alleviate, Garen was certain he’d achieved his goal. Everyone was under high duress and fear when they heard the Celestial Circle Gate was invading. But now that he displayed the unbelievable amount of force, it would ease the enormous amount of pressure everyone was holding and calm their minds.

Although he had officially mastered the entry level of the Iron Body secret method, he didn’t know how much his defence had actually increased. Weapon damage differed, and even between assault rifles, there were significant variances in damage among the different models.

The assault rifle Grace managed to get was obtained through a network of connections, hence its power was limited. Since those people weren’t part of the military, the assault rifle would be different from ones they encountered on the way back.

"It’s disappointing that the progress in Dark Iron Palm and Firestream Fist is limited. Looks like it’ll be impossible to master them in a short amount of time. Dark Iron Palm requires the build up of toxins, whereas Firestream Fist’s progress is simply too slow. I must think of other ways."

He pondered, standing in the same spot.

"It would be ideal if there are secret methods similar to Iron Body."

He placed his thoughts someplace else as he approached Collin on the side. With his voice lowered, he said, "Oh, the Twelve Southern Gates are closest to the Circle Dance Gate and Seven Mood Gate. The Celestial Circle Gate is going to be an uphill battle, you guys have to train hard. If you have any questions, just ask me. In the afternoon I plan to visit one of the two Gates and see if I can find something useful from their Wushu collections. Do you know which one of these two Gates has a wider collection?"

The group quieted down after hearing that the subject took a serious turn. Grace led the men away, so they wouldn’t interrupt the conversation, and used the time to pay them for the services.

When they heard the question, both Collin and Simon looked troubled.

"Senior Brother, we are only disciples, and thus, do not have a lot of encounters with these Gates," Collin replied with her voice lowered. "I only know that the Circle Dance Gate is farther away. The Seven Moon Gate is located in the Skylark Mountain at Dinah City, which is near us. The Seven Moon Gate is also renowned as the Seven Moon Corporation. They are a conglomerate that’s known for real estate, heavy metal, crafts and multiple other areas. I am not too sure about the other things."

Garen’s eyebrows rose slightly when he heard the response. "Do you know something more, Simon?"

"I… hehe." Simon touched his nose and didn’t respond, only laughing awkwardly.

"I know something about the Seven Moon Corporation," Grace, who just came over, said. "It has always looked for books to add to their collection. When I was at Manleyton Corporation, I’ve been notified several times about their purchases of related books. They won’t disappoint you."

Garen nodded. "I will make a trip to Dinah City in the afternoon with the address they provided. Perhaps I will find something useful. Also, the White Cloud Gate’s base is basically non-existent. We better move until second senior brother comes back. If there is any danger after I leave, you guys flee in different directions, so it’ll be difficult to trace you."

Although he knew that if the White Cloud Gate base was captured, it would be detrimental to the reputation of the Southern Twelve Gates, for the safety of everyone, Garen carefully told everyone to abandon it.

"Understood, Senior brother, you don’t have to worry," Simon responded. The sentence sounded odd as Collin pinched him.

"This is a conflict between the martially adept. You guys are in a different situation compared to me. I killed Celestial Circle Gate’s Ni Tenstar, so there is no way it’ll be easily resolved. But the rule is that conflicts stop at the family level, but they will only bother me with the rule. As long as I don’t hide, my family will be okay. If you guys hide, they will not make trouble with your families. If you must run, do so immediately. After I leave, you guys go hide somewhere with the master. Is that okay?"

"No problem! I can take care of this, I have a mansion in the rural area that’s vacant. I can move everyone there." Grace nodded as she responded. Everyone agreed.

Garen carefully explained to Collin and the group what was the safest way to handle certain situations. He then answered some questions they had in the Martial Coliseum, and only after that put on some clothes and left the dojo. Even Grace, who wanted to follow was refused. He would have more flexibility going alone.

The truth was that White Cloud Gate’s true power consisted of only six people, the four brothers along with Master and an elder. All the others were considered mercenaries and had no loyalty, and were a negligible force.

Now, Master was unconscious, the senior sister had betrayed the Gate, the second senior brother’s presence was unknown, and the third senior brother was prevented from leaving the house to join the conflict in the Wushu world. The elder had also disappeared without leaving any trace behind. The entire White Cloud Gate was left for Garen alone to defend.

Master’s friends were all people from the Southern Twelve Gates. All of them were in deep water themselves,so none could have the freedom to lend a helping hand.

The Celestial Circle Gate had clearly indicated they would target White Cloud Gate. Andrela along with his companions were already on their way. Perhaps the Sixth Golden Loop’s Su Lin would waste some of their time, dealying them for a few days, but Andrela would arrive at Huaishan City in a matter of a couple days’ time regardless.

Garen adjusted his body’s condition, recoverering to full power. The first thing he had to do was ensure that everyone else had settled to avoid the problem in his backyard. Then he would head to the remaining Twelve Southern Gates to assist them.

He would have greater flexibility if he traveled alone as he would be able to assist other Gates in a hurry. They would concentrate all their forces to defend against the Celestial Circle Gate.

Of course, searching for lower tier secret methods was also one of his intentions.

Seven Moon Gate. Skylark Mountain’s Peak, where Seven Moon corporations headquarters were located. There was the address left by Rampas when he left, and it was the destination of Garen’s trip.

The fortunate thing was that the Seven Moon Gate was only a two hour drive away from Huaishan City. Although close, without this incident, the Seven Moon Gate might not have established a connection with the White Cloud Gate.

This ancient Gate was far more powerful compared to the White Cloud Gate. The former master in charge was not the strongest within the Gate. In contrast to White Cloud Gate, within the Seven Moon Gate, there were three people at the level of Fei Baiyun! They had a countless amount of disciples, and were far stronger. They were at the top of the pyramid in the entire Galantia province, and ranked second among the Southern Twelve Gates.

Garen guessed that the reason Andrela came was to target the Seven Moon Gate. He alone would be enough to deal with their conflict. Compared to a behemoth like the Seven Moon Gate, the White Cloud Gate was simply too weak.

All of the Southern Twelve Gates received a detrimental blow.

Even before reaching Dinah City, Garen spotted powerful martial adepts rushing to the mountain peak.

It was likely that the weaker Gates in the Southern Twelve Gates were seeing Seven Moon Gate as the last battleground and concentrated all their forces there. They wanted to use the Seven Moon Gate to preserve themselves.

Chapter 101: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the middle of a vast lush grassland, a white train was moving forward slowly along the tracks; it looked like a white thread in the middle of a green handkerchief.

In a carriage in the middle section of the train, light was almost nonexistent; only traces of white light shone in through both sides.

A one-eyed man with long hair down to the waist was silently standing in the dark.

"Silvard once told me: give up your eyes for a broader world," the man said in a low voice as if he was talking to himself. He had a black eye patch over his left eye, while a sparkling glow faintly reflected on the dark golden eyelashes of his right eye.

"My heart will tell me what higher realm I intend to pursue…" he inexplicably muttered.

"Andrela." With a bang, the carriage door opened. An old man with green eyes and white hair stood at the door. "Still contemplating? You have reached the level of Grandmaster of Combat for more than a year now. Dealing with an average guy doesn't require such extensive preparation."

"It's alright. I don't underestimate any single opponent, that's my principle." Andrela gave a warm smile.

"Your characteristic is having the fastest speed and strongest penetrating power, which by chance neutralizes the strengths of that Garen. No matter how you see it, you have much better odds of winning." The old man shook his head and continued, "Fine, it's up to you. Oh yeah, the fine metal blocks for testing that you requested have arrived." He turned around and left without closing the door behind him.

Soon, more than a dozen people gradually carried in five black metal blocks and laid them out one by one in front of Andrela to form a straight line.

Each metal block was cast from fine iron and extremely tough, all half the height of a person.

After laying down the metal blocks, they silently exited the carriage of their own accord and gently closed the door.

Andrela slowly unsheathed a fine sword from his waist.

Shiiing!

A silver strand flashed in the dark then instantly vanished.

The five metal blocks were punctured in the middle with round holes. The round holes pierced straight through all five fine metal blocks. The edges of the holes were rounded and smooth, and still had a faint redness on them.

Heat waves gradually dispersed in the air: it was the residual heat created from piercing through the metal blocks at high-speed.

Andrela looked at the metal blocks calmly. No one knew what he was thinking, but he seemed to be deep in thought.

Outside the door, the green-eyed elder stood by the carriage window. He quietly watched the grassland scenery passing by rapidly outside. A girl in a crimson dress silently stood behind him.

"Even though we have confidence in Andrela, but for the sake of precaution, we still have to be well prepared. Are the people from Manleyton Corporation ready?"

"Yes. According to the report that came back to us, they are ready and have probably gained the trust of the kid from White Cloud Gate," the crimson-dressed girl replied in a hushed tone.

"That's good. Prepare them to take action and administer the drug in batches. This drug can lie dormant for three days, that's when we'll arrive. Moreover, there will be no signs of the drug after the fact. We can't lose this time. Defeating White Cloud Gate is beside the point. The main issue is that old geezer from Seven Moon Gate. Andrela needs to conserve his energy. Unfortunately, I'm too old, I can't personally participate. Otherwise, I could have cleared the path to make it easier for him." The old man sighed with regret.

"You've done enough," the girl said softly.

************************

"Grace? Why are you here?"

They were in the train station in Dinah City by a busy platform with the crowd coming and going.

Garen frowned as he looked at Grace in front of him. She hung her head low and was carrying a black handbag with both of her hands; the way she dressed made her seem like a traveling college student. Her white sweater and white jeans accentuated her high breasts and slender legs. Long light blonde hair casually draped over her shoulder, tied with a black hair band in the middle. This was a change from her cool and alluring style; it was now replaced with an air of innocence with a hint of sexiness.

"I just wanted to follow you…" Grace calmly replied. "After all, you'll need someone to help you deal with sundry matters."

"Have you arranged with the others?" Garen helplessly massaged his temples.

"Yes, all done."

"Let's go then."

Garen was speechless. Since she had already come over, he couldn't possibly send her back.

Based on the address that Rampas gave them, they hailed a horse carriage, negotiated a price, then stepped into the carriage and rushed straight towards the headquarters of the Seven Moon Group.

When they arrived at the headquarters building, there were already people stationed in front of the entrance. Apparently, as a local, Seven Moon Gate was very good at obtaining intelligence: Garen was discovered as soon as he had arrived.

The people stationed at the entrance escorted them into the building without wasting any time and led them straight to Rampas, who was training hard in Secret Martial Arts.

"I thought, Senior Brother Garen, that you would have come sooner. I didn't expect you to be late." A white towel draped over Rampas' shoulder; his body radiated heat as he walked out of the room. He sat across from Garen. The attendant on the side served some aromatic milk coffee.

"Miss, why aren't you sitting?" Rampas looked at Grace; he didn't know what her relationship with Garen was.

"It's fine. I'll just stand," Grace declined respectfully. She silently stood behind Garen and insisted on not sitting down.

After dismissing the attendant, Rampas sat up straight, picked up the coffee and took a swig. Compared to when he was fleeing danger, now he seemed more confident and had the relaxed and calm manner of a master.

"Apologies, Senior Brother Garen. All the other elders of the Gate are busy entertaining the masters and representatives from other sects. Now, most of the strength of the whole Southern Twelve Gates is gathered here at Seven Moon Gate, so they're a little preoccupied to receive you. And since you saved my life, and we're both familiar with each other, it has fallen to me to entertain you. I hope you don't mind," Rampas explained apologetically.

"Not at all. Receiving guests is merely a formality. In these pressing times, I don't really mind." Garen smiled. "Just that this time I'm here, I'd like to take a look at some low-level Secret Martial Art collections from Seven Moon Gate. We've been fighting all the way back. I want to see if I can read more on other Secret Martial Arts to broaden my martial arts perspective."

"This Secret Martial Art…" Rampas seemed to be put in a tough spot. "Senior Brother Garen, you should be clear that Secret Martial Arts, albeit at low levels, are the foundations on which sects are established. On this matter… I'm afraid I can't make the decision."

"Just tell me outright what conditions you have," Garen said calmly.

"I need to consult the Elder Deputy Sect Master. Please wait for a moment." Rampas didn't want Garen to go home empty handed either. After all, he had witnessed Garen's powerful true strength along the journey. A Secret Martial Art practitioner with such great potential, the only option was to stay on his good side, particularly in such critical times.

"I'll wait for you here then," Garen took a sip of his coffee.

"Alright. I'll be back in a moment." Rampas stood up and left from the side door.

******************

"He's just a junior. For the fact that he escorted the Sect Master back, we'll give him some money and have him on his way. These small sects keep coming to us for refuge and support. What support? It's just money they want. Do they think money falls from the sky for the Seven Moon Group? Just a few words, open their mouth and they can get a few million? What a joke!"

"But Elder, Senior Brother Garen isn't here for money…" Rampas frowned as he tried to draw a distinction. He found Great Elder Cayman resting in the conference room. It was obvious that the Great Elder had been angered by someone; he was furiously chugging his tea.

"Not money? What then?" the Great Elder was curious, and immediately stopped what he was doing.

"Senior Brother wants to have a look at low-level Secret Martial Art…"

"What? Secret Martial Art! Ask him to get lost right now!" the Senior Elder stood up at once, infuriated. "Have him leave immediately! Secret Martial Art? Is that something to be requested by a small sect like White Cloud Gate?! Forget about having a look, they don't even have the right to think about it! What does White Cloud Gate think it is anyway? Nothing but a puny third-grade sect. How dare they threaten us at this hour? They think we can't fend off Celestial Circle Gate without them? What a joke! Any random Secret Martial Art from Seven Moon Gate would be far more powerful than their Secret Mammoth Technique!" The Great Elder trembled with fury.

"Great Elder—" Rampas wanted to keep arguing but was cut off by the Great Elder.

"Say no more. In this incident, the Sect Master was heavily injured and is now unconscious, but I see that you're safe and sound. Good for you! Very well done! I still haven't disciplined all of you for that. Now you're asking for a favor on behalf of someone else?" The Great Elder stood up and furiously walked out the door. He passed through the corridors and was soon out of sight.

Rampas hastily got up and gave chase, persuading him all the way.

In a corridor connected to this corridor, Garen walked out of the room with Grace, a terrible expression on his face.

The conference room that the Great Elder was in was not far from the previous room. With his current physical fitness, having attained the powerful hearing of a Grandmaster of Combat, he could naturally hear every word being said.

"Let's go. I thought Seven Moon Gate needed my help, and we could join forces to defeat Celestial Circle Gate, but it seems that they couldn't care less about a mediocre sect like ours. " Garen said in a calm tone, then turned to leave from the way he came.

Grace followed closely behind him.

Not long after Rampas gave chase, he got wind about Garen and Grace's departure. He instantly knew that this spelled trouble. Apart from overhearing what they had said, there was no other reason that Garen would have left abruptly without saying goodbye.

He guessed it immediately: Garen must have been impatient when he didn't return, so he walked out of his room and overheard the conversation in the conference room.

"Great Elder!" he roared as he couldn't hold it in any longer.

The Great Elder walking in front turned around in shock.

"You're… shouting at me?"

The more Rampas thought about it, the more he got angry and felt offended. His face was red with anger as he stood panting in the corridor.

"Great Elder! Senior Brother Garen has left. Are you happy now?"

"What gives you the right to shout at me?" The Great Elder's expression turned somber. "What does it have to do with me, whether he's left or not?"

"Senior Brother Garen saved the Sect Master and all of our lives! Is that the way Seven Moon Gate should treat him? Very well! That's amazing!" Rampas had always thought that the Great Elder had a hot temper but was still good-natured. He didn't expect him to not know right from wrong in this matter and act out impulsively like this.

"No one needs his saving! Who begged him to save anyone? What a joke! Saved the Sect Master? Saved all of you?" the Great Elder sniggered. "I'm telling you Rampas, Celestial Circle Gate is powerful, but Seven Moon Gate is no lightweight either. Even without that Garen, would they dare touch any of our people? Even if the Sect Master is unconscious from the challenge, would Celestial Circle Gate dare touch him even once? You know nothing, and yet you dare shout at me?! Do you even know what the true assets of Seven Moon Gate are?!"

Chapter 102: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Rampas was trembling in fury. He didn't want to argue with the Great Elder anymore, so he turned around and stormed off. His father was the Second Elder; his authority within the sect was only one rank below the Great Elder. He wanted to see his own father.

Unfortunately, regardless of whether it was his father or the other elders he was close with, they were of the same attitude: to ignore without exception. They felt that this was only a minor issue. Garen of White Cloud Gate threatened to obtain the Secret Martial Art collection but failed, then left in anger. Such display was not rare among the many small sects.

Representatives or Sect Master of these small sects often come over and take advantage of the times when Seven Moon Gate was in need of strength. Money, Secret Martial Art, precious herbs, power and resources, and so on; they've requested all manner of favors.

Initially, Seven Moon Gate received them with the intention of making more friends, but their demands became more and more outrageous as time passed. The whole sect gradually became more indignant and agitated about it.

Garen and Grace walked out of the Seven Moon Gate building with somber expressions. It was then that they saw a few other people walk out of the building furiously, obviously suffering the same fate as them.

"Seven Moon Gate, they're too much!" A fit old man was panting in anger as he walked out of the building accompanied by his two disciples.

"They are financially sound and have substantial power and true strength. They don't need common Secret Martial Art practitioners like us. Let's just pack and leave. The whole Southern Twelve Gates only needs Seven Moon Gate, the other sects are redundant," a group of brawny men said in an off-tone. "It's not just our two sects that have been driven away these few days. Of the Southern Twelve Gates, only Red Obsidian Gate has been shown meticulous hospitality, whereas the rest… hehe…"

Garen shook his head, speechless. He led Grace to the side of the road, ready to hail a ride.

"Senior Brother Garen?!"

Suddenly, the cute voice of a girl sounding surprised came from his left.

"Is it really you, Senior Brother Garen?"

Garen and Grace turned around. They saw a pretty girl dressed like a high school student carrying a small white satchel rushing towards them.

The girl was one of the members of Circling Dance Gate they met on their way back. Even though Garen didn't have any recollection of her, it was apparent that she viewed the strong and striking Garen with great admiration.

The girl ran to them. When she saw their somber expressions, she instantly guessed the situation.

"They are too much! They've even rejected Senior Brother Garen! Seven Moon Gate is really…" The girl was indignant.

"You're from Circling Dance Gate. You're…" Garen hesitated. "Sorry, I have a poor memory…" He smiled in embarrassment. On that journey back, everyone from Circling Dance Gate—from ordinary disciples to the Eldest Senior Sister leading the group—completely didn't register with him.

I am Imogen Lilliette from Bodia. I'm a fifth generation disciple at Circling Dance Gate, ranked second! I'm twenty-one this year," the girl patted her chest as she introduced herself with pride. Only when she approached did he realize, her height was only up to Garen's chest; she looked like a young teenage Lolita, only about 120cm tall.

Seemingly aware of Garen and Grace's strange look in their eyes, Imogen Lilliette anxiously emphasized at once, "Twenty-one years old!"

"Yes, we know you're twenty-one years old…" Garen was speechless.

"Fine. I'm used to it anyway," Imogen Lilliette said helplessly. Her expression returned to normal and said, "Senior Brother Garen, you're here for…? Anything we can help you with, Circling Dance Gate will be behind you in full force!"

"Initially, I wanted to take a look at the low-level Secret Martial Art collections of Seven Moon Gate, as reference material. I didn't expect them to refuse me, so I just left," Garen shrugged.

"If you don't mind, you are free to refer to the Secret Martial Art of Circling Dance Gate, including the hereditary Secret Martial Art of our sect," Imogen Lilliette said solemnly. "We've heard about the situation at White Cloud Gate. If you need funds, we've just raised two million on our end. You can have it to tide you over."

"You have the authority?"

"I do! Because this is my mother's intention," Imogen Lilliette chuckled.

"This is our first meeting. Thank you so much, Mr. Garen, for escorting my daughter safely home," a calm female voice came from behind them.

Garen was stunned. He didn't notice anyone approaching him from behind. He frantically turned his body sideways to look behind him.

Suddenly, he saw a beautiful blonde with a calm temperament standing behind him. Her smooth blonde hair draped over her shoulders. She had delicate skin and features, and blue eyes as clear as the sea. She was a beauty who constantly radiated a cool temperament.

Garen was considered calm compared to Grace. She jumped in shock and almost twisted her ankle.

"Apologies." The blonde lady smiled apologetically at both of them, but it seemed as if she was not used to smiling; her smile gave an odd and awkward impression. "I am Imogen Lilliette's mother, Jaimea Lilliette, also the current Great Elder of Circling Dance Gate."

"Why are you all here at Seven Moon Gate…" Garen was confused. His nose caught a hint of fragrance, and out of courtesy, he distanced himself away slightly.

"The headquarters of Circling Dance Gate and Seven Moon Gate are both in Dinah City," Jaimea Lilliette explained. "My daughter and I were just out to buy some sundries and coincidentally passed by. We didn't expect to meet the two of you from White Cloud Gate. Even though we're insignificant compared to Seven Moon Gate, but if you don't mind, why not come over to Circling Dance Gate for a while?"

Garen quickly thought about it, then accepted the invitation.

"Yes, that sounds lovely. Just as well we could pay a visit to the headquarters of Circling Dance Gate."

Jaimea Lilliette had a cool temperament and was somewhat blunt in the manner she spoke, but the way she looked at Garen and Grace was indeed sincere.

Even though the influence of Circling Dance Gate wasn't as strong compared to Seven Moon Gate, they didn't seem weak either. Soon, two slightly old black cars drove over and stopped next to where they stood.

Garen and Grace stepped into the car at the back, while Jaimea Lilliette and her daughter sat in the car in front. Both cars slowly drove towards the other end of Dinah City.

Half an hour later, Garen was sitting face to face with Jaimea Lilliette and Eldest Senior Sister Vicard in the middle of a wooden dojo.

The dojo was a rectangular structure, made entirely of wood. It was slightly dilapidated. The entrance was to the left. On the walls at both ends hung two white paper banners with the words "Martial Arts" and "Dance" written in black ink separately.

The reddish-brown wooden floor boards were neatly arranged and well-polished, but defects could be seen in some parts of the floor, giving the sense that it was timeworn. Despite being slightly dilapidated, the entire dojo was filled with a faint scent of incense, and there wasn't a trace of sweaty odor; it was clearly well maintained.

In front of Garen was a glass teacup filled with Rainflower tea. The reddish-pink tea in the cup looked exquisite. Bits of flower petals were floating in the tea like watery red crystals and the tea had a delicate floral aroma: it was an exceptionally pleasant aesthetic experience altogether.

"Senior Brother Garen, thank you for your care before." Vicard was the Circling Dance Gate leader that Garen escorted. She looked dainty and adorable now.

The hosts were both clad in black robes and long black socks. Apparently, it was the standard attire here.

Jaimea Lilliette motioned to Garen to drink his tea. "Mr. Garen, you saved our Sect Master and several of our disciples, including my daughter. Even though we are a small establishment, we are clear that gratitude should be repaid as much as revenge should be exacted. Secret Martial Art and funds are not a problem. Whatever else you need, feel free to ask for it. I will fulfill your request to the best of my abilities on behalf of Circling Dance Gate."

Garen was undoubtedly touched.

"How did you know I needed Secret Martial Art?"

Jaimea Lilliette calmly explained, "Most people who have visited Seven Moon Gate of late are primarily after these two things. I apologize if I have offended you, but I am only telling it as it is."

"It's fine."

Garen could tell that Circling Dance Gate was not doing very well itself. Despite the fact that the dojo was huge, it was dilapidated to the extent that they didn't even have the funds to properly maintain and repair it. Even White Cloud Gate was much better off. When he thought about how the headquarters of Circling Dance Gate and Seven Moon Gate were both located within Dinah City, the answer was obvious: the former must have been harshly oppressed by the latter.

In a case where they were not well-off but displayed generosity out of gratitude, such an attitude was in stark contrast to what Garen experienced at Seven Moon Gate.

Garen actually felt somewhat ashamed. He didn't pay much attention to Circling Dance Gate at the time, but just helped them out incidentally. He didn't expect that it would be this humble female sect that could help him out right now.

"Actually, we have no need for funds," Garen carefully thought about how to phrase it. "We at White Cloud Gate are not facing a huge problem with funding." This was the truth. The dojo account had tens of millions in funds. These were the sect funds voluntarily passed on to Collin and Simon by the stout Bouvini in charge of finances. Garen wasn't short of money.

Upon hearing that they didn't lack funds, the two from Circling Dance Gate were immediately relieved and felt even more grateful to Garen. It was apparent that they were extremely tight on funds. They haven't been able to cover their cost in recent years, with the dojo income decreasing rapidly. If it was money that Garen requested, they would have given it to him, but that would have put them in a tougher situation.

"I'm here not for money or whatever else. I'm here for Secret Martial Art," Garen said formally.

"No problem. Including our hereditary Secret Martial Art, you are free to study and record all the Secret Martial Art within our library," Jaimea Lilliette nodded in agreement.

"Hereditary Secret Martial Art is the foundation of a sect, I don't want it, and I have no need for it. I am merely looking for some low-level Secret Martial Art to broaden my martial arts perspective, for reference," Garen promptly explained.

"Regardless, I'll take you to the library at once. How does that sound?" Jaimea Lilliette resolutely stood up and asked.

"Uhh…" Garen didn't expect her to be so eager. "No hurry. Let's have a chat and rest for now."

"Very well." Jaimea Lilliette felt that she was slightly overeager, and slowly sat down again. "Excuse my manners."

And then it became a question and answer session between the three.

Garen asked, and they answered.

They were the type who wouldn't speak when not questioned and seemed as though they didn't interact much with people; their tone was somewhat blunt.

By casually asking a few questions, Garen gathered a general idea of Circling Dance Gate and understood the types of characters within it.

There was a total of twelve people in the sect, external disciples included. The modest and austere style of the dojo business made it unattractive. Coupled with the fact that they were oppressed by Seven Moon Gate, the entire operation was bleak, and they could barely make ends meet.

The dojo master in charge of the day-to-day was Jaimea Lilliette's father, a headstrong man advanced in years. He was adamant in preserving the estate inherited from their ancestors, unwilling to sell the current headquarters and dojo. This didn't help their poor financial situation.

Everyone in the dojo, including Jaimea Lilliette—regardless of their external personality— were tough and headstrong characters, all bent on preserving the dojo.

Originally, as a Secret Martial Art sect and one of the Southern Twelve Gates, they were entitled to a fixed income and certain benefits. This was the key reason Circling Dance Gate joined, and it was this fixed income that kept the dojo in business. But now Lucene Brotherhood, the strongest of the Southern Twelve Gates, has been obliterated. This sect was the leader and organizer of the Southern Twelve Gates. They were in charge of distributing the annual benefits and funds. Without that income, it had become more difficult for them to keep the dojo running.

Chapter 103: Variation in Secret Martial Arts 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

While the three of them were chatting, Grace, Imogen Lilliette, and another girl were preparing sweets and lunch in another clean white room.

"Grace, you go get some rest. We can handle it here, so it's fine!" Imogen Lilliette persuaded multiple times, but to no avail.

"It's alright. This is part of my duty anyway." Grace gave a weak smile. "But it does seem that there's nothing for me to do to contribute here. I'll just go out and buy some daily necessities for the next few days."

"Don't worry, just go. But don't forget the way back. Or should I accompany you?" Imogen Lilliette offered as she peeled a small potato.

"No, it's fine," Grace declined.

"You be careful then."

As she flicked away the water on her hands, Grace walked out of the kitchen. A trace of gloom flashed across her face.

She quickly walked out of the corridor into the courtyard, heading straight for the entrance.

She had barely walked out of the door when a small blue shadow dashed into her arms. She was surprised to find that it was a little blue bird with a white paper bag tied to its foot.

Grace quietly removed the paper bag, looked around, and gently let the little bird fly away.

The blue bird was swift and silent in flight, disappearing into the sky in the blink of an eye.

Grace opened the paper bag. There was a packet of white powder inside, with some inscriptions on the packaging paper. Her face went ice-cold after reading it.

*********************

In the afternoon, the sky gradually darkened. With only dense gray clouds and no sunshine, it felt heavily depressing.

Garen quietly sat in a bedroom at Circling Dance Gate. In front of him was a low square table with five thin manuals laid out on the white surface. There were no names on the manuals. A faint fragrance of ink emanated from them.

"I can't believe they've gifted me with their entire treasured collection. This is really…" Garen didn't know what to make of it, but he felt appreciative.

These five Secret Martial Arts manuals were the secret books that he just got from Circling Dance Gate’s underground library. Initially, he had picked out a few to carefully study, but he didn't expect them to simply hand over all the secret books to him. He further selected a few from the timeworn library and, without discovering anything more, he finally brought all the Secret Martial Arts manuals back to carefully study them in the room that they had arranged for him.

The entire process took him just over an hour.

"Of these five Secret Martial Arts manuals, three are Secret Martial Arts tailored to women. I'll give up on those, but I might still be able to derive something in terms of technical attacks. The remaining two…" Garen's gaze fell to the two books on the right.

Boulder Martial Arts and Augustus's Two-Handed Ancient Sword Technique.

"Boulder Martial Arts…" Garen felt that this name was similar to the names of Eastern martial arts. He picked up the secret book and started reading meticulously.

The image of a white lotus was printed on the pale yellow cover and the words "Boulder Martial Arts" was handwritten in Confederation text on the edge.

He turned over to the first page.

‘

"Boulder Martial Arts originates from the East and is a common, highly popular Body Hardening Technique. Upon mastery, it will inflict the powerful effect of anti-Vibration on opponents."

Garen continued turning the pages. What followed was a concise and direct description of the specific postures for the technique as well as preparation and practicing times. There were no external drugs needed as supplements, but it was very strict regarding practicing times. It started from one o'clock midnight and ended at three in the morning.

There were three specific levels: they were merely three strange poses. However, the method and route of blood and Qi circulation, as well as the breathing technique, were enlightening.

On the other hand, the two-handed ancient sword technique book was a martial art that relied on vocalized practice. It had typical domestic characteristics.

"Too bad I left the Weeping Sword in the main dojo and didn't bring it here. Otherwise, I could carefully study the features of a martial art involving vocalized practices." Garen gently put down the two books.

Knock knock knock.

Light knocks on the door were heard.

"Please come in." Garen slowly closed his eyes and put his hand on the two secret books, deep in thought.

The room door gradually opened. Grace came in with two cups of coffee.

"Garen, I've brought you some hot coffee."

She wore a short white dress. The thin black stockings under her short dress vaguely revealed the white underwear between her legs and her high breasts exposed a wide area of fair skin.

She gently laid down the saucers on the table by the secret books and sat across from Garen. When she saw that Garen's eyes were closed, she could not help but show a trace of disappointment on her face.

She reached to pull her dress down a little to cover her underwear, then put the coffee in front of both of them.

"Please drink."

"Leave it there for now," Garen said casually.

The atmosphere in the room settled down. Garen was pondering a problem, but Grace started to feel restless and uneasy.

"Grace," Garen suddenly spoke. "Back then, what was the reason that made you decide to follow me?"

Grace was silent for a while. "Because of the corporation, and also probably because you spared my life."

"And mostly because my master was the Sect Master of White Cloud Gate?" Garen asked bluntly.

Grace paused. "Yes."

Garen opened his eyes and calmly looked at the seductively dressed girl in front of him. There wasn't a hint of desire in his eyes.

"Your family is one of the major families in Huaishan City with great influence. Was it what your corporation wanted or what your family requested of you?"

Grace widened her eyes in shock. Her expression couldn't help but finally change and her breathing started to become heavier as well.

"How did you notice?"

Garen smiled. "When you found me at the station, I noticed that your heartbeat was very fast. You didn't do any strenuous exercise and you were calm on the surface, but still your heart raced faster in front of me. If it were ordinary girls, I would probably guess that they fancied me, but not you."

He watched as Grace sat there stone-faced, then continued, "Also, when you came in with coffee, the two coffees had different smells. My cup is obviously impure."

Grace felt a chill in her heart.

She looked at Garen smiling kindly in front of her and suddenly felt that everyone had probably underestimated this ordinary 17 year old youth.

This drug powder was clearly declared by Celestial Circle Gate to have an undetectable scent that could not be sensed Secret Martial Arts practitioners, but it was easily identified by Garen.

"His true strength… what level has it actually reached…" Grace was in a panic all of a sudden. She looked into Garen's clear, deep, red eyes and bit her lower lip. "How… how do you plan to deal with me?"

"Your heart rate is fast again." Garen took a sip of the coffee without the drug powder. "You're afraid? What are you afraid of?"

When Grace recalled the information that her family had obtained, she suddenly felt that she had been too naïve. Originally, she had thought that the information about Garen was exaggerated and she had not witnessed it personally, so she did not take it to heart. However, from the looks of it now… Killing dozens of people along the way—all of them elite fighters—it must have been true!

Garen let out a sigh of disappointment.

"Actually, if not for the fact that I never fully trust anyone, the chances that your plan would succeed were great. But unfortunately…" He shut his eyes as a trace of fatigue showed on his face. "Leave."

Grace's eyes opened wide as she looked at him in disbelief. She seemingly could not believe what he just said.

"You're… not going to do anything?" Suddenly she recalled the manner in which Garen usually handled things: even though it was not cruel, it was not peaceful either. She did not expect him to let her off on this.

"Just leave. This marks the end of our relationship. Don't appear in front of me again. I won't be so merciful the next time we meet," Garen said calmly.

Grace's pale face regained some color. She slowly stood up. When she saw that Garen remained seated, she was delighted.

"What an idiot! Who lets an enemy who tried to poison them go? No wonder you've come back in this sorry state after just one trip! Obviously your stupidity is the cause." She started to relax. Although she did not care for Garen's compassionate gesture, she only dared to think of some ideas in her head and did not dare to make any wrong moves. Her life depended on it, after all.

"Celestial Circle Gate is very powerful! You be careful," she said, faking some guilt before leaving.

She did not wait for a reply. Gently closing the door behind her, she hurried towards the courtyard. It was only after she exited the entrance of the Circling Dance Gate dojo that she let out a quiet sigh of relief.

"Even though the plan failed, at least I managed to keep my life. I need to report back immediately. There is a great discrepancy in the information we have on Garen!"

She quickly hailed a horse carriage taxi and stepped on.

Departing from the main dojo of Circling Dance Gate, she reached a remote corner in the suburbs a dozen minutes later.

After paying for her ride, Grace stepped off and walked into an alley filled with filthy and smelly homeless men.

"Get out of the way!" She kicked aside the thigh of a homeless man blocking her path and walked onward with a look of disgust. "Who sets such a place as a contact point anyway?"

Under the greedy gaze of this group of homeless men, she flashed the silver handgun on her waist and succeeded in frightening the ones with malicious intentions.

She was muttering as she walked into the depths of the alley. She retrieved an engraving dagger from the corner of the wall and forcefully carved an inverted "V," then stood up and turned around.

"You!" Blood instantly drained from her face as she backed up a few steps and hit the wall.

It was unclear when Garen had appeared behind her. He had looked at her with mild interest as she carved the mark.

"This is your secret contact code?" He walked over and touched the wall. Suddenly a layer of white stone powder showered down. The mark was easily erased.

"Grace, I treated you as a friend. What a pity…"

"I thought you said you'd let me go…" Grace's heart was beating fast and her entire body was sweating slightly.

Wham!

Garen grasped her neck tightly with one arm and held her to the wall. He applied a light pressure.

Crack.

With her neck broken, the glow in Grace's eyes slowly faded away. Her initial violent struggle gradually weakened, before finally ceasing.

Without a sound and without alarming anyone, she died straightaway in silence.

"Indeed, I did not intend to kill you earlier," Garen said calmly. "It would be inappropriate if you were killed in the Circling Dance Gate dojo. After all, it's someone else's place."

Unconsciously, after killing so many people along the way, his heart had become oddly calm.

Chapter 104: Variation in Secret Martial Arts 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I've caused danger to my master and the other disciples by letting them stay at the secret villa that Grace prepared. Someone needs to take responsibility for everything."

For a while, Garen still had slightly complicated feelings. After all, Grace was someone who had followed him for so long. The feeling of killing someone he was familiar with was different from killing a complete stranger.

Using his empty hand to search Grace's body for a while, he found a set of keys, a black leather wallet, a silver handgun and some documents.

Grace's figure was so curvaceous that even Garen could not help but grope her large breasts a few times, just to feel even more disappointed. He thought it was a waste that he had to kill such a capable and beautiful woman.

Fortunately, he was not some sort of perverted noble. Otherwise, he might first rape Grace before killing her, or even keep and train Grace as a sex slave after capturing her.

He carried her corpse to the dumpster on the opposite side and stuffed it inside. Taking out a lighter from his pants, he lit it up and threw it into a huge bag of shredded paper that was inside the dumpster.

The dumpster quickly caught on fire that slowly grew larger as white smoke gradually drifted into the air. Then the red flames lit up Grace's clothes and completely enveloped her corpse within the fire. The fair and delicate skin of her corpse started to turn yellow as oil seeped out from her skin, then her corpse turned black and completely turned into coke.

The air was filled with a strong smell of burnt meat.

Garen silently watched as Grace's beautiful face was completely burned beyond recognition before he slowly walked out of the alleyway.

There were several vagrants lying in the alleyway and were all knocked out using small stones. With the current strength of Garen's Vibration that came along with the Mammoth Secret Technique, it was an easy matter to completely knock all of them unconscious.

The smoke in the alleyway was getting bigger as Garen left. He quickly returned to Circling Dance Gate using the same route he came from.

He only spent half an hour to go there and back.

A young girl was holding a broom and cleaning the yard when Garen returned. After politely greeting her, he went back to the room that was arranged for him and sat down at the table with the precious Secret Martial Arts manuals.

For now, he had to put aside the situation in Huaishan City. Since Grace was a traitor, Celestial Circle Gate definitely knew where he was. He had no intentions of fleeing either. With so many people from the Southern Twelve Gates gathered here, it might be the best location to confront the Celestial Circle Gate and that mysterious organization. If he were to flee to another location, he might jeopardize his master and fellow disciples in Huaishan City. This upcoming war was inevitable.

The current situation was very simple. As long as he could block Andrela and protect White Cloud Gate, everything would be fine. The other factions would not behave like rats leaving a sinking ship. However, once he—the final hope of White Cloud Gate—was defeated, then they would be a sitting duck for other factions.

Putting aside Grace's matter, he moved the cooled coffee to one side and started to carefully open the secret manual of the Boulder Martial Art.

At the same, the Boulder Martial Art selection gradually appeared within the Skill Pane in his field of vision.

"Boulder Martial Art: Uninitiated (Three levels in total), Learning Requirement: At least 1.00 in Vitality, Strength, and Agility."

This particular Secret Martial needed at least fifteen years to complete each level. It took a lot of time and the initial learning requirement was high. It was also the main reason why low grade Secret Martial Arts were disfavored.

On the other hand, the main problem for Boulder Martial Art was that the learning requirement needed Vitality, Strength, and Agility to be at least 1.00, and that was the average for an adult male.

This meant that only the body of an adult could satisfy the basic requirement for learning this Secret Martial Art.

The fact that every level needed fifteen years to complete was another important reason. If a Secret Martial Art needed fifteen years to get to the initiated stage and was only an inferior martial art, nobody would be stupid enough to practice it.

Garen took another look at the description of the result after mastering the Boulder Martial Art.

"When the Boulder Martial Art has been mastered, the body of the practitioner will be as hard as a boulder. Qi and blood will continuously circulate throughout the body, putting the body in the strongest defensive state all the time. Body speed will uniformly experience a significant growth. This Secret Martial Art was derived from the indestructibility of boulders in mountain ranges. After mastering the Boulder Martial Art, Qi and blood will blend together and become abnormally hard, while tranquilizing the mind. It will have a positive effect on irritable practitioners as well."

Garen suddenly remembered Jaimea Lilliette. Her cold appearance might have been caused by practicing this Secret Martial Art. He guessed that it might not be entirely from it but could have learned from it.

"Could this really aid growth in body speed?" Garen was feeling slightly expectant.

Garen immediately stood up and took a pose according to the first diagram. At the same time, he followed the breathing instructions and the method to adjust his Qi and blood. His mind gradually entered the calm state mentioned by the secret manual.

However, ten minutes later, Garen suddenly felt a slight itchiness in his chest and abdomen, as if his organs were itching. Soon after more than ten seconds later, his skin and muscles were starting to slightly itch as well.

It was not really itchy, but was just a slight feeling.

The situation was similar to what was described in the secret manual. The Secret Martial Art would only consider to be initiated when the itchiness appeared, grew stronger, and finally subsided.

However, the current itchiness was very weak. Garen came to conclusion that he was practicing at the wrong time. There must be a reason that the secret manual stated that the Boulder Martial Art must be practiced in the middle of the night.

************************

Dinah City railway station

In the dead of the night, a white, luxurious train gradually stopped at the empty railway station.

The middle door of the carriage opened and a series of passengers wearing various kinds of casual clothes got off the train. Some of them looked like students, while others looked like tourists and there were even workers and intellectuals among them. There were all kinds of attires, but all of them had one thing in common, and that was they were all wearing a silver cross star symbol on their chest.

After most of the passengers got off, but three men and two women slowly alighted.

Among the five of them, only one man was an elderly in his sixties, while the other four were young.

A long-haired young man was leading the other three as they quietly and slowly got off the train.

"We've finally reached Dinah City. If we didn't receive the news that Garen came over here, we wouldn't have to switch to another train halfway through." The long-haired man was slightly shaking his head in frustration. His left eye was covered by a black eyepatch while his right pupil was a rare dark golden. He had waist length hair, wore a black coat and had a mysterious aura.

"How is it? Andrela, Dinah City is the territory of Seven Moon Gate. Are you confident?" The old man raised his head and looked at the sign—that displayed the station name—hanging above them within the train station.

"I’m fine." Andrela smiled and lightly touched the slender sword hanging at his waist that was hidden by his coat.

"Speaking of which, you've been at the Grandmaster of Combat level for quite a while. This time, you might be able to find an opportunity to advance." The old man was feeling slightly emotional and expectant.

Andrela only smiled. "Grandmasters of Combat are far more superior than normal people and are no longer afraid of guns and bullets. It's even classified as a non-human realm. There are even some Grandmasters of Combat that believe that they're no longer mortal and view normal people as ants. Even though that kind of path was powerful, it is not the path I want to walk. That's why I've stopped progressing for so long."

The old man was slightly surprised. This was his first time hearing this head disciple of Celestial Circle Gate voice out his opinion. "Then what kind of a path are you trying to walk?"

"Grandmasters of Combat are classified into Righteous and Immoral, and the difference lies in the fighting styles. A Righteous style doesn't hide its moves and uses momentum to pressure opponents. An Immoral style uses endless amounts of secret techniques. They each have their own merits. I have not figured out my third path. However, I feel that it's close… Grade D… is not the end..." Andrela's eyes were flashing with an indescribable gaze. "Martial arts should be endless."

"That's our hope as well." The old man patted Andrela's shoulder with a hint of gratification in his eyes. "To be unburdened by unnecessary emotions, as expected of my disciple!"

Andrela slowly shook his head. "Master, there are some people and things that were only buried in history. I am not the first Grandmaster of Combat that has walked on this path."

"I know." The old man nodded. "Let's go, bring along the glory of Celestial Circle Gate. Nobody will be able to stop you in this war of unification!"

"That's what I thought as well." Andrela smiled as he strode out. The other three followed after him, as if they were bodyguards protecting him.

***************************

Late at night

Circling Dance Gate

Garen was sitting cross-legged in the center of the cold dojo.

The muscles in his entire body were slowly wriggling around, as if there were countless earthworms crawling all over his body.

"Even though I've become a Grandmaster of Combat, I still don't understand true meaning of it." He was constantly adjusting the Qi and blood within his body and also his condition by following the method provided by the Boulder Martial Art.

"Su Lin once said that a Grandmaster of Combat is a Martial Adept that has reached the limits of the human body in a certain aspect. Their skills have been thoroughly tempered and they no longer have any fatal flaws.

"However, is it really true that the limits of the human body were just this low? Even though I can withstand a bullet, I am helpless against bombs and artillery shells." Both of Garen's hands were slowly raised above his head.

Hah!

With a low roar, all of the muscles in his body suddenly expanded. It was not the expansion of the Mammoth Secret Technique, but a very little amount of muscle expansion instead.

"A Martial Adept that has reached the limits of the human body and is also the number one expert of the younger generation, Andrela." Garen's eyes were faintly filled with a trace of expectation. It was a kind of a true expectation toward an opponent of the same level.

Suddenly, within the Skill Pane in his field of vision, the Boulder Martial Art selection slowly changed.

"Boulder Martial Art: Rudimentary Level (Three levels in total)"

Suddenly, he thought of something.

Garen slowly stood and slowly performed the Four Major Forms of White Cloud Combat Arts. He was entirely immersed within the limit state of the Mammoth Secret Technique. However, he was not using the special breathing technique of Mammoth Secret Technique, but the breathing technique of Boulder Martial Art.

It was as if the Boulder Martial Art and Mammoth Secret Technique were reacting to each other. Garen was entirely immersed within the casual execution of the chain combination of the Four Major Forms.

The Boulder Martial Art selection, that was just displaying Rudimentary Level, immediately started to slowly disappear.

The strange part was that the Mammoth Secret Technique was slowly disappearing as well. They were replaced by an entirely new Secret Martial Art and a symbol slowly appeared behind it.

"Mammoth Variant Secret Technique: Explosive Level."

Garen looked toward the symbol behind it.

"First level of stabilization of Qi and blood: The integration of Qi and blood within the body can reflect damage back to the opponents. Originated from Boulder Martial Art. Can advance to higher levels through training Boulder Martial Art."

Reading the meaning of the symbol, he was slightly surprised. "The main effect of Boulder Martial Art is the powerful defense. I didn't think that its effects could actually stack with the Mammoth Secret Technique. However, the text behind states that it can advance to a higher level through training Boulder Martial Art. However, why isn't there any reaction from Iron Body? It should be combinable as well!"

He slowly recovered his posture and focused his attention on the Iron Body selection.

He suddenly thought of something and slowly performed the Iron Body as he executed the Four Major Forms.

After a few minutes, Iron Body slowly disappeared as well.

Then, the symbol behind Mammoth Variation Secret Technique slightly changed. It changed into two: one of them was stabilization of Qi and blood, the other was hardening of the epidermis.

"First level of stabilization of Qi and blood: The integration of Qi and blood within the body can reflect damage to opponents. Originated from Boulder Martial Art. Can advance to higher levels through training Boulder Martial Art."

"First level of hardening of the epidermis: Hardness of the skin rises and is capable of resisting injuries from highly sharp weapons. Originated from Iron Body. Can advance to higher levels through training Iron Body."

All of his Secret Martial Arts that were Body Hardening Techniques were fused together and he was only left with a variant Secret Martial Art.

Chapter 105: One Battle! 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen slowly lifted up his hand and looked at his palm. His slightly enlarged palm was faintly glimmering with a black metallic luster.

He felt that the Blood Qi Ball within his body had not release any Qi and blood to assist in the expansion of his body.

"This feeling is different from when I was using the expanded form of Mammoth Martial Art, but it is still slightly stronger than normal. Since the degree of expansion is not large, I'll consider this as the first form."

Garen forcefully waved his arm around, and felt that the hardness of his skin was around half of his defense when he was at full power. At the same time, it was around twice the hardness of his normal state. After mastering Mammoth Martial Art, his defense when using all of his power was four times that of normal situations. This sort of terrifying Body Hardening Technique allowed him to block the attacks of most martial artists using only his eyelids.

Slowly relaxing his body, Garen's gigantic body gradually shrunk like a deflated balloon from 1.9 meters to 1.7 meters. Under his normal state, he looked just like an ordinary person that was slightly muscular. It's just that his powerful physique made him seem more like an adult than a seventeen year old teenager.

Boom boom boom! Boom boom boom!

Suddenly, the sound of urgent knocking sounded out from the door of the dojo.

"Senior brother Garen! There's trouble, the people from Celestial Circle Gate are here!" Imogen Lilliette's voice came from behind the door.

"Celestial Circle Gate! Is it Andrela?" Garen walked over to the locked wooden door and opened it.

Standing at the door, Imogen Lilliette looked frantic and was still wearing black pajamas.

"Calm down, what's the situation?" Garen softly asked.

"I don't know, almost everyone from the Celestial Circle Gate is staying a hotel near the railway station. However, their leaders, Andrela and a few others, were nowhere to be found. What should we do, senior brother Garen!?" Imogen Lilliette was slightly at a loss.

"The Southern Twelve Gates are all targets of the Celestial Circle Gate. Don't forget about the Seven Moon Gate and the Red Obsidian Gate that joined them. There two sects are definitely not pushovers. Let's take a look at the result first. There's no need to hurry." Garen smiled as he comforted Imogen Lilliette, while gently rubbing her head.

Feeling Garen's unworried and relaxed mood, Imogen Lilliette began to relax as well and became less anxious.

Actually, she had no idea why she was so anxious either. When she heard that Celestial Circle Gate had arrived, she immediately panicked.

"The Celestial Circle Gate is walking the just and honorable path by fairly challenging each sect to a duel. If they want to unify the entire southern martial arts world, they need to comply with the rules or it will all be for naught. So we'll only need to face them head on and not have to worry about them playing any tricks. After all, the Celestial Circle Gate is very confident of their abilities..." Garen simply said. "If my guess is right, Andrela is currently already fighting with the Seven Moon Gate."

He was faintly looking toward the direction of the Seven Moon Gate headquarters as an inexplicable gaze flashed in his eyes.

*****************

Da da da...

A series of rapid footsteps rang out as a three-storey hotel near the railway station was completely surrounded.

The surrounding area was completely quarantined by numerous police vehicles.

Under the night sky, there was a cold-looking young man wearing black leather clothes. With shoulder length silver hair, a beautiful face, thin waist, and long legs, he expressed an androgynous beauty. If it was not for the fact that he had an adam's apple and no breasts, no one would believe that he was a man.

The man was slowly putting on a black and red gauntlet—with brutish spikes on it—with a calm gaze

"Commissioner Karanan, I am relying on you to help out in the quarantine this time," he simply said.

The middle-aged man with a potbelly standing next to him nodded while smiling. "Chairman Shia is being polite. The fact that I am able to help out the Seven Moon Group is a great honor for me. Not to mention that the governor specifically mentioned that I should fully support the Seven Moon Group in all of your activities. This is also part of our duty as the Metropolitan Police."

The beautiful man called Chairman Shia nodded. Then without saying anything else, he beckoned with his hand.

The men dressed in black outfits in the area immediately created an opening for him to pass through.

Shia walked into the encirclement and looked up the small white building toward the window on the third storey.

"Shia Ludanni from Seven Moon Gate is here to welcome senior brother Andrela from Celestial Circle Gate. Please come out to meet me."

His voice was androgynous and was a mixture of women's softness and men's rigidity, giving a strange sense of indifference and severity.

There was no noise at all. Although there were over a hundred men dressed in black surrounding the small building, there was no sound coming from the building at all. Even the policemen outside the perimeter were affected by the nervous mood and lowered their volume.

There was only silence in the small building and no one replied.

A sneer appeared on Shia's face.

"During the exchange gathering, we really owed it to Celestial Circle Gate. This time, since senior brother Andrela has come to our Dinah City, it's only natural that we, as the host, should properly take care of the guests. Could it be the fellow disciples from Celestial Circle is unwilling to give Shia this honor?"

There was still no reply from the small building.

Shia's face slightly contorted in anger.

"Since senior brother is unwilling to come out on your own, then I'll just have to personally invite you!"

A few of the men dressed in black slowly drew out black daggers as cruel sneers appeared on their faces. They were the most elite of the core teams within the Seven Moon Gate. The reason why the Seven Moon Gate was able to develop so much and obtain the best territories in the entire province was due to the efforts of teams like theirs.

As the sound of light and hurried footsteps rang out, more than a dozen men dressed in black charged toward the entrance of the small building. Before they could reach it, a silvery flash of light suddenly appeared, drawing a semicircular arc in the air.

The men all groaned at the same time and flew backward. There was a slit that was sliced open on each of them, but it was only their clothes that got cut and not their bodies.

At the entrance of the small building, a man with reddish purple hair slowly walked out. He was wearing a white outfit with a silver cross star symbol on his chest.

"If you want to see our senior brother, you need to get past us." He calmly stared at Shia who was standing at the front as a trace of severity flashed in his eyes.

"I am one of the Four Circles of Celestial Circle Gate, Xin Luo," He slowly announced his name. Immediately after, two other figures slowly walked out from behind him. One of them was a tall woman and the other was a short and thin boy.

"Xin Luo?" Shia's eyes narrowed into a straight line and his entire being was both sharp and cold. "I've long heard that the Four Circles of Celestial Circle Gate has always been four people. Why is one of you missing?"

He knew very well that the Four Circles of Celestial Circle Gate were the four strongest disciples below Andrela. They were also the most promising candidates to vie for the position of senior brother and were definitely not weak.

The moment he mentioned that matter, the faces of the three turned slightly ugly.

"Tenstar Ni getting killed was his own fault for being unskilled. Since you dare to speak that way about Celestial Circle Gate, let's see how strong you are!"

Before Xin Luo even finished speaking, he applied force to his legs and started spinning to the left—like a spinning top—into the surrounding teams of men dressed in black.

Ding ding ding!!

A series of clashing between metal sounded out as half of the men in black were injured by the black shadows of the sword. Only a few veterans were able to timely parry the thin sword.

More than a dozen of the men dressed in black did not retreat, but attacked instead. They were unafraid of getting cut by the thin sword as they stabbed toward Xin Luo with a dagger in each of their hands.

Ahh!!

One of the men dressed in black suddenly retreated while clutching his right hand and screaming in pain. His right palm was sliced off at the base of his wrist and blood was rapidly spraying out like a fountain. Two men from the back immediately arrived to take care of his wound.

"Step aside! Let me do it!" Shia's expression went cold and he suddenly rushed out. The gauntlets on his hands drew a dark red line in the air.

At the same time, the men dressed in black suddenly spread out, creating an opening in a well-trained manner that was just enough for one person to enter.

Shia punched toward Xin Luo's chest with his right hand that was clenched into a fist, while silently aiming for Xin Luo's abdomen with his left hand formed into a spear-hand while hiding it behind his right hand.

This was Seven Moon Gate's most famous Yin Interception Finger. Once it made contact with a person's body, it would cause the blood vessels to burst and create an internal hemorrhage, while the skin remained unharmed.

Shia's fingernails on his left hand were slightly purple and gleamed with a strange luster. Hidden below the gauntlets, they were like a venomous snake hiding in the shadows and were both malicious and covert.

The two of them instantly collided together.

Kacha!

The black shadow of the sword clanged as it struck between the spikes of the gauntlets and was twisted into pieces by the spikes.

Shia's Yin Interception Finger—that was aiming for Xin Luo's abdomen—missed as it was parried away by a knife hand from above.

Both of them each took a few steps backward as a fearful expression flashed across their faces.

"No wonder you dare to show up with so few people. Very well!" Shia's expression did not look well. Even though he had the upper hand, Xin Luo was only weaker than him by a tiny amount. They were both stuck at the level right before Grandmaster of Combats and there were two other exponents at the same level as well. Not to mention, there was still Andrela after them.

He was originally planning to quickly get rid of these people and directly recruit Andrela. He did not think that...

"As expected of the Celestial Circle's Four Circles! Attack them!"

He suddenly beckoned and the hundreds of men dressed in black in the surrounding immediately surged forward.

***************

Puff...

Garen heavily breathed out.

Ever since he returned to Huaishan, he had been thinking about how to perfect his martial arts system.

He had always been walking the route of focusing on strength and defense. However, this type of route lacked speed. Once he met an opponent who was much faster than him, he would be stuck in a situation of getting beaten up. Even though he had yet to meet such an exponent, it did not mean that it would not happen in the future.

A perfect martial art system should be able to deal with any kind of situation. An excessive shortcoming was just a fatal flaw.

When faced against Sylphalan's illusionary power previously, he did not have any way of dealing with it either.

This was his weakness and weaknesses needed to be overcome.

"Speed…" Garen was sitting cross-legged in the dojo. The morning sunlight was gently beaming on him, plating his topless upper body with a layer of light golden glow.

He got up early in the morning and started to adjust his condition. Since Celestial Circle Gate had already arrived, a battle could occur at any time. This was a battle in front of everyone and if he lost, it would imply that the White Cloud Gate that he was representing had lost.

Chapter 106: One Battle! 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

For a martial arts sect, reputation was extremely important. Losing signified lesser skills, and practitioners naturally gravitated toward stronger martial arts, rather than picking weak ones. In the case that the reputation of losing was to spread, White Cloud Gate would be finished.

All sects, regardless of size or strength, would not generally want to compete throughout the entire sect to conclusively determine the stronger sect. If met with such a situation, someone must be picking a fight.

The real strength rankings may be an open secret, but publicly determining it would be interfering with the livelihood of other sects. Such an action would invite lethal revenge.

So, Andrela instantly led some people over after Ni Tenstar was killed and challenged the headquarters of the Lucene Brotherhood to restore the reputation of Celestial Circle Gate. Externally, they could claim that Ni Tenstar was not fully trained in his martial arts and then prove that it was not the martial arts of Celestial Circle Gate that was weaker than the opponent's martial arts. Instead, it was due to the practitioner's own insufficiencies and inability to fully absorb his teachings.

Garen was clear about the consequences of this duel, but the other side must have learned the whereabouts of his family members and his master: it was an invisible threat. Killing a spy from the Manleyton Corporation was nothing since the whole company was merely their tool; it would not help solve the plight.

This was the power of Celestial Circle Gate: to be able to force their opponents to wait in place and accept the challenge.

"A sect which was able to survive until now must have challenged many other sects. That was probably how they obtained their collection of rare Secret Martial Art tomes. The low-grade sects which lost these challenges could not carry on locally, so their only choice was to leave their base and continue surviving somewhere else."

Garen recalled several things that his master Fei Baiyun had mentioned when he was giving him guidance in martial arts. One of them was about the reason the ancestors of White Cloud Gate moved overseas to the Confederation. After being challenged by a local expert and suffering defeat, all they could do was move away to a place where no one knew them and start from scratch. There was no way to keep the original dojo running once their poor reputation spread.

"If you want the break the reputation of White Cloud Gate, you'll have to get my permission first." Garen closed his eyes and started thinking about measures to counter a faster opponent.

"When he has attained a qualitative boost in his speed, my speed wouldn't be able to keep up. All I can do is maintain the status quo. As long as I determine the opponent's target of attack, regardless of how he changes, all I need is to protect myself. Defense is simple, but to be able to successfully attack the opponent will prove difficult. I can't keep up because he will be too fast and I can't enhance my Speed with Attribute Points anymore…"

Garen began envisioning a high-speed opponent attacking him from all angles and imagined possible counter moves and ways in which he could successfully attack his opponent.

"The shortest distance between two points is a straight line. And that aspect… Maybe I can figure out a way from these two aspects…" He moved his body slightly, then fell into deep thought again.

After a while, he got up and walked out to the yard. He stood silently still in front of the rockery pond.

****************

Seven Moon Group.

Andrela calmly stood in the pale gray ring. The fine sword in his hand gave off the crisp sound of tinkling silver bells. The tip of the sword was vibrating swiftly and this created a sound like chimes fluttering in the night wind.

He quietly looked across at the group of people holding up the old man, who was dealing with his wounds.

"Seven Moon Gate, let me face your true expert. I have no patience to waste time with you."

"You!" Pffft!

The old man spat out fresh blood as he pointed at Andrela, trembling in fury.

Shia was supported by two disciples clad in black. He had blood all over his face and his right arm dangled gingerly from his shoulder as he stared fiercely at Andrela. Around him were Rampas—his face white as ash—and a group of middle-aged men and women clad in red. This group of people came from Red Obsidian Gate, had just arrived, and looked nervous. Some of them, who wielded daggers in their hands, were trembling slightly. They rushed over after they had gotten wind that Andrela had appeared to challenge, but the scene that greeted them was of the Seven Moon Gate Great Elder being stabbed by Andrela.

Everyone heard a clear ringing, followed by a flash. The Great Elder groaned as blood spurted out from his right chest and he collapsed to the ground. They did not even see how Andrela retracted his sword.

"Our strongest expert is Great Elder Kudo Slant! You are strong Andrela, far beyond our expectations. But if you intend to humiliate us with such a crude reason, we at Seven Moon Gate would rather fight you until the end than see you prevail!" Shia, the strongest of the younger generation at Seven Moon Gate, roared in fury.

"Humiliate?" Andrela waved his sword and the ringing stopped. "The path to the Dao is so difficult. Do you think I would devote my time to humiliate garbage like you?"

His looked like his usual self, with a serene glow in his eyes. But in a moment like that, serenity merely conveyed an ice-cold impression.

"Seven Moon Gate… What a disappointment…" He leapt out of the ring. Xin Luo and the other two stepped forward to keep up. "Forget it. I have wasted too much time. Let's go straight to Circling Dance Gate."

Pffft!

The Great Elder spat more blood out from his mouth. He initially wanted to say something, but was hindered by blood flowing back into his throat. He was so enraged that he fainted straightaway.

The faces of the Second Elder and the others were livid. Some were firmly held back by their peers, who were afraid to let go lest they walked to their deaths.

Andrela and the other three walked out of the Seven Moon building. An Elder from Celestial Circle Gate was waiting for them with some men outside.

"Settled?"

"Settled." Andrela grinned.

"They were not comparable. Eldest Senior Brother settled it in minutes. Such garbage is only a waste of space," the girl beside Xin Luo said in contempt.

"Weren't you injured earlier, Iona? If Eldest Senior Brother hadn't interfered… Heh," a short boy snickered.

"At least I held my ground for a bit. What about you? A midget is indeed a midget. One blow and you were out of the ring."

"Let's go. Off to Circling Dance Gate." Andrela did not say more. He turned around and went into the car.

He held more and more sway now. One sentence and both of them were silenced. They separately got into the black car.

The onlookers from other sects waited until the car from Celestial Circle Gate drove off into the distance before starting frenzied discussions in clusters.

At the same time, a large group of people poured out from the entrance of the Seven Moon building. Shia, Rampas, and the rest were carrying the Great Elder who had just regained consciousness. There was also the group from Red Obsidian Gate led by their Sect Master.

"Come, let's go to Circling Dance Gate!" Shia snarled as he watched the black motorcade drive away.

Seven Moon Gate was different from other sects because they had a solid foundation as a group and would not be annihilated merely by a fall in reputation.

A white motorcade arrived and they boarded.

Rampas sat with his father, the Second Elder.

"Rampas, you were one of the disciples at the exchange gathering. What did you think of Garen from White Cloud Gate?" The Second Elder was a stern-looking middle-aged man with short black hair and white sideburns. He looked deeply troubled.

"Senior Brother Garen, he's a very powerful person," Rampas candidly recollected. "He has a strong Physique! He's the type that uses Strength as an advantage."

"The type that uses Strength as an advantage?" a trace of regret flashed across the Second Elder's eyes. "Unfortunately, I didn't take it seriously when you came to me, but Seven Moon Gate is not a plain martial arts sect. This defeat would cost us some loss at most, yet it wouldn't affect us too much. We don't rely on martial arts to support the entire group. Forget it. Since we've offended him, even though it's our fault, let's just put the matter to bed."

"But…!" Rampas seemed to want to continue, but was halted by his father.

"We at Seven Moon Group can't possibly humble ourselves and apologize to a plain martial arts practitioner. You do not understand the Great Elder. If it were up to me, I would be willing to do it. But the Great Elder has the authority now. Even if he knew that he was wrong, he wouldn't apologize," the Second Elder sighed. "He is a man who would rather die than admit fault."

Rampas was speechless. A surge of indignation pent up inside him without release.

Horse carriages from other sects trailed the Seven Moon Group motorcade. Everyone knew that the decisive battle between Celestial Circle Gate and the Southern Twelve Gates was at Circling Dance Gate. This decisive battle was a golden opportunity to openly witness Andrela's true strength. Celestial Circle Gate had no intention of stopping them either: this was a golden opportunity for them to showcase their true strength.

Andrela had defeated Seven Moon Gate effortlessly. Red Obsidian Gate was too scared to even make a move. Celestial Circle Gate's foundation of power was firmly established.

The final step was to settle the score with Garen from White Cloud Gate.

The mighty motorcade formed a long chain and stopped in succession in the open spaces and streets around Circling Dance Gate.

The locals in Dinah City thought that some official had come for an inspection and a crowd of onlookers formed in the periphery. The city police sent a large number of officers for security. They put a cordon around the area and refused to allow non-martial arts practitioners within 500 meters of the Circling Dance Gate premises.

Only residents within the cordoned zone who were already at home had the opportunity to witness what happened inside.

The black motorcade of Celestial Circle Gate slowed to a stop at the entrance of the Circling Dance Gate courtyard.

The reddish-brown wooden door was shut tight.

With the sound of car doors closing, Andrela and the rest stepped out of their cars.

He looked up at the black plaque above the courtyard door. The words "Circling Dance Dojo" was clearly visible on it, but some black paint around the edges had come off, exposing the brown wooden material underneath.

Andrela had changed into a new set of clothing, wearing a black shirt and long trousers. His long hair reached his waist and he had a grin on his face. If not for the fine silver sword at his waist, he did not appear like he was here to challenge anyone and looked more like a visiting friend.

He gently pressed the eye patch over his left eye. With a creak, the courtyard door opened.

Beyond the open door, he instantly saw Garen standing in the courtyard, with his back to him.

Garen shut his eyes tightly, mildly conditioning the muscles of his entire body. He was in a peculiar subtle state and in the best form he had ever been in his life.

"Andrela of Celestial Circle Gate?" he asked softly.

"Garen of the Southern Twelve Gates?" Andrela asked in soft tone too.

Without the slightest hesitation, he unsheathed his sword and transformed into a black shadow rushing towards Garen.

Garen turned around and opened his eyes. His stature rapidly expanded.

Both approached each other at breakneck pace. Suddenly the sounds of wind bells chiming and a mammoth bellowing could be heard.

In that moment, both their faces lit up with a smile. It was anticipation!

Chapter 107: Victory! 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A huge crowd gathered around the courtyard of the Circling Dance Gate; some martial artists had even jumped onto the walls for a good spot to watch the fight from. Others who were watching the fight were the inhabitants of the tall residential buildings in the vicinity.

The members of the Celestial Circle Gate stood in front of the courtyard, and following behind were the Seven Moon Gate and the Red Obsidian Gate.

The few girls of Circling Dance Gate stood at the entrance of the wooden door of the dojo.

Everyone’s sights were nervously pinned on the two people in the middle of the field.

Andrela rushed towards Garen, his figure creating black lines. He plunged his sword in.

Ding ding ding! A series of metallic clashes rang out violently. In a flash, numerous sparks erupted from the rapier on Garen.

Hu!!

Andrela did a backflip and jumped away, narrowly missing Garen’s hand chop. The green and black arm, as thick as a concrete pillar, crashed onto the earth on the ground.

Bham!

The fine, grey dirt exploded violently, as though a bomb had gone off. The huge amount of grey dirt, under the intense force, turned into countless of shrapnels which flew ruthlessly towards Andrela.

With another rain of little tinkling sounds, a big mound of earth and mud had all come before Andrela and defended him...

A silver mirror seemed to have materialized in the air before him in that instant. Blocking all the finely crushed dregs.

Chik!

The silver mirror disappeared, turning into a rapier pointing towards the ground.

Having had their first turn against each other, they resumed their positions, a few meters away from each other.

Garen lowered his sight to look at where he had been stabbed. Dabs of blood had appeared indistinctly on the skin there. Clearly, some tiny blood vessels had been cut.

"You are able to hurt me, surprisingly... Not bad... You are indeed the opponent I have been waiting for!" The corners of his lips curled into a deeper grin unconsciously. A surge of turbulent emotions shook in his chest, ready to erupt at any time, like boiling hot lava.

Andrela held his sword, as though he had yet to make a move, standing in his original position, his long hair flowing.

"One who can receive a full-strength blow from my sword in my normal state. You are definitely the person who killed my brother." He spoke slowly, in a low voice, but his tone did not weaken and was heard by everyone clearly.

"Tenstar Ni is your brother?" Garen was stunned but he immediately recovered. "No wonder you have come in person, I see that this is the reason. As for killing Tenstar Ni, I do not regret it. It is difficult to avoid getting hurt or dying in a contest of combat. If you wish to avenge him, I stand here. Come and kill me yourself, if you can."

There was a flash in Andrela’s eyes.

"Life and death are inevitable on the path to the truth. What a pity. If we had not met under such circumstances, we could have been really good friends... Although now, I still do not wish to kill you..."

He lifted his rapier; a greenish black piece of muscle, shaped like a cross, protruded suddenly from the back of his hand, exactly the same as had happened with Tenstar Ni.

*****************

"Big brother is using his secret weapon already?" At the Celestial Circle Gate, Xin Luo exclaimed, somewhat astonished, "He should not be needing to use this against Garen, right? Even if he can’t pierce through the other parts of the body, but he should be able to pierce through the ears and the eyes, no?"

"What do you still not understand?" The Elder, standing on the side, said in a deep voice, "Take a closer look at Garen’s stance."

Xin Lo and the other two took a moment to look over, with fixed concentration.

Garen’s entire body had formed a strange V shape; at the same time, both his arms were slowly moving, continuously in a gentle motion. His entire body had blended into one harmonious figure.

Wisps of white vapor were released from his nostrils, surrounding his body in vague, blue forms, flowing slowly. From afar, he looked as though he was shrouded in the body of a huge, white elephant. Every slight movement he made came with the faint sound of a mammoth’s neigh.

The expressions on the three people shifted slightly.

"Such powerful bravery!"

The Elder nodded, looking grave and solemn.

"His secret weapon is to unite his body into one; the blood qi of his entire body becomes incomparably sensitive. No matter which point you attack him at, it will be deflected easily by his excellent combat skills. After all, however fast you are, can you be faster than that slight move of the shaking of his head?"

He watched the strong and ferocious Garen from afar: "Looks like everyone underestimated this young lad from White Cloud Gate!"

On the other side of Circular Dance Gate, a few people, including Jaimae Lilliette and Imogen Lilliette, had become solemn after seeing this scene.

"These two people have such strong bravery!" There was an uncontainable shock on Jaimae Lilliette’s face. "Indeed! Garen has indeed become an Ultimate Adept of the Grandmaster of Combat!"

"Mummy, what is bravery? Senior Brother Garen looks so powerful, but that Andrela does not look weak either. Will Senior Brother Garen be alright?" Imogen Lilliette asked in a small, anxious voice.

The other disciples also looked to the dojo master doubtfully.

"Bravery is the combination of a martial artist’s physique, technique, spirit, released as a single aura. Or, it can also be called a sort of threat! A sense of danger! You should know, every living being has natural responses to danger. As for elite martial artists, they have a method to blend everything in and of themselves together, giving off a fierce, threatening feeling. This method is called bravery. When you see a venomous snake, would you feel that it is dangerous, highly toxic? Your entire body would then be nervous. This is a similar principle."

Jaimae Lilliette watched the two people in the field, with mixed emotions reflected in her eyes.

"As for excellent martial artists, having such an ability lets them display their strength, and can even achieve an exaggerated effect without having to resort to battle, making their opponents desist from having thoughts of retaliating! This is to achieve victory without having to fight. Look closely at that Andrela."

Imogen Lilliette and the rest paid close attention to Andrela for a moment, and indeed, vaguely discovered that his long black hair was flying all around his body; there was a delicate sound of windchimes echoing slowly around his entire body. At the same time, both his arms were raised up before him, making a strange hand gesture. It gave them a very weird feeling.

"It looks a bit like a black cross!" Imogen Lilliette blurted out.

The two people in the courtyard, one a giant, white elephant, and the other a black cross, were facing each other; a huge horrifying and threatening aura was spreading out, unrestrained. Some martial adepts nearby had a momentary misconception, as though even with the great distance between them, they were still in danger at any given time. They automatically retreated, one after another, only relaxing when they had backed off quite a bit.

The members of the Seven Moon Gate, furthest in the back, were the ones watching the confrontation between the two people in the field with unusually mixed feelings right then.

The Second Elder, leading the team, stood at the forefront. Next to him were Shia and Rampas.

"This is bravery…!" His voice was dry, "Bravery that only an elite martial artist can have."

It was not only him; all the other higher-ups of the Seven Moon Gate had complicated looks in their eyes; they were all the higher-ups whom Rampas had pleaded for mercy before. Now, looking at Garen’s terrifying and humongous bravery, they were momentarily rendered speechless by an indescribable, mysterious feeling.

"That’s Senior Brother Garen! No wonder the news from the exchange gathering states that he is the most powerful one amongst all of us in the Southern Twelve Gates!"

"With him, we the Southern Twelve Gates will not sink!"

"Senior brother Garen!" A disciple shouted.

"If only I can be as strong as Senior Brother Garen!"

Most of the disciples of the Seven Moon Gate were ignorant, and were still exceptionally excited, all looking proud of Garen.

"Elder, why didn’t Senior Brother Garen rest with us at Seven Moon Gate when he came to Dinah City? After this contest is done, how about you invited him over to give us some tips on martial arts?"

"Oh yes, Elder, it’s not every day that we Southern Twelve Gates has a master who can fight the number one of Celestial Circle Gate. We must invite him to be our guest at the Seven Moon Group!"

The emotions of the disciples, who had been shamed by Andrela, had burst out all at once; now seeing that Garen could face off directly against the Andrela who had defeated even their Elder, their excitement was on fire, as though it was a senior brother from their own Gate who was in battle with Andrela.

Seeing the excited disciples, the Second Elder and a few of the higher-ups were temporarily speechless, unable to voice out their concerns.

Were they supposed to tell these disciples directly that, this Senior Brother Garen of yours had actually come over to the Seven Moon Group before, only that we had completely disregarded him and chased him out the door as though he had been a beggar?

If this got out, not only would their reputation crumble in an instant, but even the image of the entire Seven Moon Gate would receive a great negative impact.

Rampas watched the excited looks of the fellow junior brothers and sisters around her with an emotional heart; even the strongest Junior Brother Shia was gritting his teeth and staring at Andrela, and at the same time, giving Garen encouragement.

There was an unspeakable surge of emotion in his heart, for a moment; it caused his eyes to tear up a little.

"Shut up!!"

There was a sudden roar.

The entire Seven Moon Gate immediately fell silent; everyone’s sights were set on the Great Elder on the stretcher at the back.

The Great Elder had changed into a set of clean, white clothing, and at the moment he was so angry that his face was completely red, and his beard was shaking.

Shiang!!!

With a loud crash, a terrifying, great howl sounded out from the Circling Dance Gate courtyard.

It was like the howling of a mammoth into the skies.

The Great Elder was shocked by the sound; he had initially wanted to speak, but instantly, a gulp of air got stuck in his throat as his eyes rolled over and he fainted.

Every martial artist in the area had their eyes focused on the two people in the courtyard.

The crazy howl of the mammoth was still erupting and had not stopped. Those were the fierce noises made by Garen’s arms and entire body piercing through the air.

Garen stood, unmoving, his white, strong upper body surrounded by a black flow of air which was swirling around him wildly. That was the optical effect caused by Andrela being too fast.

The two of them, one unmoving and one striking, were in a crazy tangle.

Every stab of Andrela’s sword landed clearly on Garen’s body, but at most had drawn only a bit of white mark. The attacks occasionally went to his eyes and ears but were easily deflected or blocked.

Furthermore, Garen’s body now was slowly swelling up; although it had not reached its full strength, it had reached a point where the Boulder Martial Art was about to burst out. His height, which had originally been 1.7 meters, was now almost 1.9 meters. His entire person had become stocky and imposing, like a beast; just moving simply about was enough to move the airflow and disturb his opponent, and at the same time, he could even hit out a noise not unlike the roar of a mammoth.

But he was completely unable to catch up with his opponent’s speed, and could only tightly cover up his vital points. As for the other parts of his body, he depended on the hardening of his skin and the stabilizing his blood qi to harden himself up. It was all he could do to forcefully maintain this condition, undefeated but also unvictorious.

The clear sound of the wind chimes rang faintly in the midst of the roar.

This deadlock was not maintained for long; the black lines drawn by Andrela instantly pounced off, and landed on the rockery of the courtyard, crouching down. His long black hair fell gently onto the greyish white rock, like a satin cloak. The silver rapier was pulled to his side.

The calm fire in his eyes had increased, which was unusually conflicting.

"Looks like ordinary swordsmanship has no effect on your body’s defense now. Be careful, this next sword is one of my three great secret swords. I hope you do not die to this..."

Garen moved both his arms, and once again, subtle airflow roars began to permeate around his body. "Three great secret swords? You are indeed the number one of the young southern generation! Definitely much stronger than the typical garbage!"

The corners of Andrela’s lips curved up gently again. His long rapier moved steadily, seemingly slow but actually rather quick, and drew the silver outline of a fan.

"Celestial Secret Weapon..."

He jumped up lightly and flew towards Garen.

"Bright Moon!"

Clang!!!

Immediately, silver moonlight shone in between him and Garen.

The silver moonlight was so bright and glaring, that all light in the area seemed to be sucked in, condensed together before erupting in a flash.

All the spectating martial artists were speechless; they dared not even breathe heavy, afraid of breaking the beautiful, silver-white crescent moon in the courtyard.

Two crescent moons flashed in both of Garen’s eyes momentarily; the silver light pierced his sight. He was completely unable to see.

Instinctively, he raised up both arms before his head.

An extremely sharp, icy cold breath hit him outside of his arms. In that instant, Garen felt a sharp pain in his arms. He did not even think.

A roar erupted from his throat.

Roar!!!

A violent howl exploded instantly.

The courtyard was shaking, the ground was also shaking! Every martial artist was shaking, and even the dojo house began to make a creaking sound, huge clouds of dust fell with a swish.

Chapter 108: Victory! 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Everyone at the place, including the people from Celestial Circle Gate, Red Obsidian Gate, and other Martial Artists around, felt the ringing in their ears. They were suddenly paralyzed and lost all their strength.

Waves rose in the pond, and several red goldfish jumped out of the water.

BOOM!

The two in the courtyard separated.

One man was blown away toward the wall at a high speed, but he quickly shifted his position mid-air, landing on his feet against the wall to reduce the impact. He reached the top of the wall and stood on it firmly.

It was Andrela, a sword held in his right hand, which was trembling. Blood was dripping down its sleeve, and it fell to the ground quietly.

"They don’t call you the strongest Martial Artist of the Southern Twelve Gate for nothing." Andrela’s voice was low, and he sounded excited.

"You are pretty good too." Garen stretched his arms. There were two narrow sword cuts on the outer side of his arms, and blood was spurting out of them in two red lines.

"Secret Sword Art Bright Moon, huh? Impressive." Garen licked the blood off his arms with a ferocious expression on his face. "I am surprised… However, it’s not enough."

"True." Andrela smiled. "You are a worthy opponent, and I will show you the second skill of my Secret Sword Arts."

The people watching the fight were still in shock. The fight between the two were on a different level, a level that human beings could not even imagine. Garen’s body was incredibly strong, while Andrela’s Secrect Sword Arts were terrifying. In addition, the two’s speed was so fast that the crowd could barely see their actions.

Everything happening in the fight was new to the Martial Artists here.

They heard the two’s conversation and realized that they hadn’t yet shown their true power. Even though, the skills the two displayed made most of the strong Martial Artists here speechless.

"They are… so strong!"

"I thought I was strong, but I never knew there were Martial Arts with such power!" Seven Moon Gate’s Shia looked at the two, and the passion in his eyes could almost melt iron.

"Those are the Grandmasters of Combat." The Second Elder spoke in a light tone.

"Shia, Rampas, you two are the hope of the Seven Moon Gate. Watch how they fight carefully, and I am sure it will help you a lot in the future."

In the courtyard.

Andrela slightly swung his blade.

It suddenly started to vibrate, many silver light dots appearing at the point of the blade, and they were bouncing in the air. Andrela jumped off the high wall and charged toward Garen. He was slower than before but still much faster than Garen.

There were many silver light dots floating around Andrela, and as he charged forward, those silver light dots started to gather together. They converged at the point of the blade and became three large silver dots.

"Three Star Convergence!"

The three dots at the point of the blade became one, and the final dot was flashing. Andrela stopped charging when he was two meters away from Garen. Strangely, the silver light did not stop and went straight toward Garen.

A silver tiny light dot appeared on Garen’s chest and disappeared in a second. Andrela’s attack penetrated his skin and muscle, a drop of blood appeared on Garen’s chest, but started to flood with red right after. Garen held the wound with his hand, feeling a severe pain coming from his chest.

"What a strike…" Garen looked surprised. "I didn’t even have time to defend. The burst of speed at the last second was unbelievable."

"Unfortunately… It is still not enough…" Garen inhaled deeply and a great amount of heat started to come out of his body.

His body was getting larger, and taller!

His height increased from 1.9 meters to about 2.3, and he was much taller than Andrela after the transformation. Some of his muscles changed to black, while the rest became green. He turned into a giant within seconds, and his arm had the size of a normal person’s leg.

Veins twisted in his body, and they looked like numerous venomous green snakes.

After seeing Garen’s transformation, everyone’s expression changed.

The Martial Artists, girls from the Circling Dance Gate, and people from the Red Obsidian Gate, the Celestial Circle Gate, the Seven Moon Gate, were all staring at the horrifying black-green giant, Garen.

"This is the Master level of Body Hardening Techniques… I only heard about it from the tales…" One of the Martial Artists in the crowd said in a shaky tone since not many people in the world could recognize the changes happening to Garen.

"Changes like this will only happen to people that master Body Hardening Techniques!"

"Garen from the Southern Twelve Gates! This battle will become his masterpiece!"

The crowd got noisy and excited.

The Three Circles and Elders of the Celestial Circle Gate looked nervous. They thought that the one from the Seven Moon Gate was strong and Garen was just an average Martial Artist, but they did not expect him to be so strong.

"Master level in Body Hardening Techniques! We are in trouble!" The Elder said and stared at Andrela. "Andrela… How are you going to deal with his legendary Body Hardening Techniques?"

"Senior Brother will never lose!" A tall girl of the Three Circles said in a serious tone.

"Fight! Senior Brother!" Xin Luo yelled.

The Second Elder of the Seven Moon Gate was surprised, but he looked full of excitement.

"Master level in Body Hardening Techniques. I didn’t expect that…"

"Let’s see what Andrela is going to do! Garen is invincible!" The Junior Brothers, Senior Brothers, and the Elders were all surprised. Rampas finally felt elated.

At the entrance of the Circling Dance Gate, several girls just recovered from the shock and saw Garen’s changes.

"Get him! Garen is the best!"

Imogen Lillette yelled excitedly.

"What are you going to do now? Andrela." Jaimea Lilliette was looking forward to seeing Andrela’s next action, so she stared at him.

Everyone at the place was staring at Andrela, wanting to know what he was going to do next.

Andrela was wearing black, and he looked like a kid in front of Garen. It was like a kid trying to fight an adult: weak.

Although the sword in Andrela’s hand was about 1.5 meters long, but it looked like a toothpick when compared to Garen’s body, about to break at any moment.

Bam!

Garen clapped, creating a loud sound. He was also staring at Andrela, looking forward to his opponent’s next skill.

"This is my true form, Andrela! Come get me, for your brother, for the fame of the Celestial Gate, and for the Extreme Martial Arts you’re always pursuing!"

Andrela had a surprised look on his face, but unlike the others, he did not fear Garen, not at all! He was just surprised and excited to see something he had never seen before.

"The Master level in Body Hardening Techniques… Garen... Your name will be heard in the whole Southern Martial Artist World!

"You are right. Even though it’s a pity, but one of us has to die today. It’s either you or me." Andrela calmed down. "I thought I’d never meet a worthy opponent, and then I met you…"

Andrela raised his sword in the air.

"I will show you the strongest Sword Art created by myself!"

"Secret Sword Art!"

"Blink!"

Chi!

After hearing the light noise, Garen felt pain coming from his back, and Andrela had disappeared from in front of him.

He turned back immediately and saw Andrela standing there firmly. Andrela lowered his sword slowly, and there was blood on the point of his blade.

"Such speed…" Garen’s pupils constricted. "My eyes can’t catch movements like that… but I don’t think you can use that skill with ease."

Garen could still feel the pain coming from the centre of his back, but it was not a big deal.

"If you’d used it on someone else, he would be dead for sure. Unfortunately..."

"... it’s you." There was a bitter smile on Andrela’s face.

Garen nodded. "When I’m in this form, any damage I take will be partially reflected. Your Blink was done at full speed and strength, so the reflected damage must be high. I guess your wrist bones have already fractured a bit, right?"

Andrela’s bitter smile disappeared. "I can still try one more time."

"Your last attack was at full speed and strength, but it barely hurt me, and you want to try again?" Garen looked at Andrela calmly. "Also, I can’t promise you will survive my next attack when I’m in this form. Each of my attacks come with vibration, and it is the essence of my Mammoth Secret Technique."

Garen shook his head. "Stop. I don’t want to kill you."

"It’s fine. I’m willing to give up my life as long as it’s worth it. The Extreme Martial Arts are the purpose of my life." Andrela raised his sword again, and Garen could see the passion in his eyes.

"I will respect your choice." It was the first time Garen had met someone who would give up his life to pursue the Extreme Martial Arts.

Garen closed his eyes, and his body started to tremble. It looked like he could move to any angle he wanted, and he was trying to prevent Andrela from attacking his weaknesses, such as ears and eyes. He focused his defense on those parts.

"Secret Sword Arts… Blink!" Andrela disappeared with the last word.

Garen’s muscles suddenly retracted and became very dense. He also raised his arms.

"Consecutive Swing Form!"

His body started turning, and his arms were swinging like a wheel. He was chopping at all the angles with his hands.

Chi!

Andrea’s sword appeared in front of Garen’s eyes and ears, but he did not find any chance. He then aimed at Garen’s right armpit, trying to stab his sword into it.

Boom!

At that moment, Garen hit Andrela’s left shoulder with his hand, and Andrela was blown away by the impact.

"Celestial Circle Gate lost!"

Everyone had that one thought in their mind after seeing what had just happened.

Chapter 109: Farce 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wham!

Andrela's body hit the half-open door hard, and with a 'crack' he broke the wooden door and skidded far across the floor. He finally stopped after almost hitting the martial arts practitioners watching the fight.

Garen stood silently in place; his scarlet eyes seemed to emit a fluorescent glow. He silently looked at Andrela who was lying on the ground in a distance.

He had already tried to restrain himself as best he could. Unfortunately, he was completely out of form and his strength was too violent. Even if he only struck a shoulder, the force would be enough to cause turbulent shocks.

This was the essence of the Secret Mammoth Technique: explosiveness.

He looked around him. The whole room was quiet. Any martial arts practitioner who met his gaze would subconsciously look away.

His gaze swept from the martial arts practitioners on the fence, to Circling Dance Gate, then to Red Obsidian Gate, and finally fell on the group from Celestial Circle Gate.

Those from Celestial Circle Gate fell into a dead silence. They had a blank look on their face, as if they hadn't managed to process their Eldest Senior Brother's defeat. Only Xin Luo and the other two disciples rushed to support Andrela up from the ground.

The Elder who led the group stared fixedly at Garen without avoiding his gaze. There was no hatred or anger in his eyes, just slight disappointment.

"Do you know the real purpose of our trip, Garen of White Cloud Gate?" he suddenly said aloud. His voice seemed to stand out distinctly in the sea of silence.

"Our trip here was to…"

"Master!" Andrela's voice cut him short.

He stood up with the support of his Brothers, and maintained his balance by using his sword as a crutch. Even though he looked pale, apart from the wound on his shoulder, he didn't seem to be too severely injured.

But everyone knew that he was merely putting up a strong front. After being struck by Garen who had transformed into such a terrifying size, no one would have been able to withstand it.

"A victory is a victory, and a defeat is a defeat. There is nothing more to say." Andrela clutched his shoulder with his other hand, and was prodding around the circumference of the injury with his fingers in a compact and swift manner; it looked like a type of healing Secret Martial Art. It was apparent that after his continued prodding, the injury and pain on his shoulder seemed to gradually reduce. Even the way he spoke seemed more relaxed.

"I can't believe you actually showed mercy, Garen." He calmly looked at Garen in the courtyard. "About my brother's death, I won't pursue it further. I owe you a life. You've killed Tenstar Ni, so we're now even. Next…" He turned around slowly—unexpectedly with his back to Garen—to face the crowd behind him.

"We should carry out the real purpose of our trip."

Members of Seven Moon Gate blended in the dense crowd. The Second Elder, Rampas and the others were surprised to discover at this point that Andrela was facing in their direction!

"Young man, you've got some nerve."

A thin and short figure gradually emerged from the crowd of members from Seven Moon Gate. The strange thing was, before he walked out, no one actually noticed him standing in the crowd.

He was a skinny old man in dark green robes, a bamboo hat covering his face. His height merely reached the chest-level of everyone around him, but he exuded an air of violence and danger.

When he walked out, everyone around him instantly crowded backwards, as if they had encountered a poisonous snake. Some who had weaker willpower even looked terrified and were screaming in fright.

Just as the old man emerged, the Great Elder from Seven Moon Gate followed closely behind. His injuries seemed to have been alleviated; he looked healthier.

"Since you made a formal challenge based on the rules of the martial arts world, I'm following the rules too. Hmph! You've injured so many of our people, do you think you can leave Dinah City just like that?" Sarcasm was written all over his face.

"Regardless of whether it's the Secret Martial Art world, or the sway that Celestial Circle Gate holds in the military, this is Galantia Province, not your own neighborhood. You think you can be as rampant as when you were at the exchange gathering?"

Everyone was baffled; they had no clue where this old man came from. Even the people around Seven Moon Gate were confused, but based on the look of the Great Elder, obviously this old man was a secret force within Seven Moon Gate.

And from his Bravery, it was apparent that he was a Grandmaster of Combat from the previous generation.

But everyone understood the motive of the Great Elder of Seven Moon Gate now: he brought a group here to stir up trouble. And they purposely waited for the moment when Garen and Andrela were both injured to take advantage of the situation.

"Mr Mallone, I'll trouble you to handle these people from Celestial Circle Gate," the Great Elder calmly said to the old man in a hushed tone.

"You're too modest, General Bert," the old man replied the Great Elder in an oddly polite manner. "You helped me out a great deal the last time. This is just a small matter in comparison. As Grandmasters of Combat, I'm interested to see what experts have emerged from the next generation."

His gazed shifted to Andrela who was barely standing.

"Kid, seen as you've just dueled with someone and lack strength, I'll make the first move. I'm telling you in advance, this move is a simple move I created by casually observing the cosmos; I'll just be using ten percent of force. If you can't even withstand it, I'll have to take your title of 'Top Youth Expert in the South'."

Upon those words, without waiting for Andrela to respond, the old man Mallone took a deep breath, dug out a red pill from his pocket and put it in his mouth. He chewed a few times and swallowed it. At the same time, the violent Bravery on his entire body became stronger, and everyone could faintly hear the hissing of a poisonous snake.

He bent his knees slightly. His face was pale then red intermittently; his hands were swollen to a larger size and were a bloody red. There was a faint revolting stench in the air.

"Red Python Fist! Poisonous Bite!" His figure approached Andrela at a moderate pace. At every step forward, the stench from his fist became noticeably stronger. His face was reddening too; apparently it was the embodiment of an extreme flow of Qi and blood.

Shameless!

This was the thought that crossed everyone's minds at that moment.

Putting aside the fact that he took advantage of Andrela when he was heavily injured, he found an excuse to make the first move as a pre-emptive strike, and even increased the power of his fists. And yet he claimed that it was merely a simple move, and that he's using ten percent of force!

Also, youth, it's YOUTH! How could you claim to be a youth? Look in the mirror, you're way past 50!

"Fuck! This is his idea of a simple move? Only someone retarded would believe that!" a crude martial arts practitioner couldn't help but curse out loud.

"Could you be anymore shameless? Ten percent of force? Red in the neck and face and you claim it's ten percent of force? Who are you trying to fool? Fuck, I can't believe there’s a freak like you at Seven Moon Gate!"

"I know that pill! It's Blood Surge Pill, a high-grade secret medicine that can increase the strength of the fists and speed within an hour!"

"Shameless!"

"Scum of the martial arts world!"

Everyone around couldn't stand it any longer, and started berating him.

Even members of Seven Moon Gate bowed their heads and gave way, their faces feverishly red.

Rampas and the Second Elder were traditional martial artists. When they saw how shameless the man that the Great Elder had invited out was, they were humiliated; it was a complete disgrace to Seven Moon Gate.

The old man Mallone was unfazed, and kept walking towards Andrela menacingly.

Of the Celestial Circle Gate members, three slowly stepped forward and shielded Andrela. They looked at the old man Mallone, expressionless.

"Move aside. You can't shield him." Andrela had figured out his opponent's true strength; he was equally a Grandmaster of Combat, and not a low level one at that. This person was one of the true hidden strengths of Seven Moon Gate, and also one of the targets of his trip. It's just that he didn't expect himself to be injured to this extent from his fight with Garen.

"It’s alright! Eldest Senior Brother, you have a rest," Xin Luo whispered. "We'll handle him for you." He had always been the leader among the few of them, and this time he was the first to reply too.

In that moment, on the grounds:

"Does Seven Moon Gate only know such despicable tactics?" the Great Elder of Celestial Circle Gate sneered.

"At least it's better that Celestial Circle Gate drugging opponents." The old man Mallone chuckled a couple of times, then didn't speak anymore.

"Drug?" the Great Elder of Celestial Circle Gate was surprised. But before he could react, the old man Mallone accelerated instantly—leaping every few steps—and dashed towards Andrela.

Wham wham wham!

Three consecutive 'whams' and the three members of Celestial Circle Gate were struck aside. They rolled over sideways, their faces red. It was a sickly purplish-red; obviously they had been poisoned.

The old man started sniggering, and motioned his palm to strike Andrela's chest. The poisonous snake hissing which surrounded him became louder, and brought with it a gust of revolting stench.

Chhh!

A dart flew towards his neck.

"Nuisance!"

A murderous gleam flashed in Mallone's eyes. He hit the dart mid-flight and sent it propelling back towards where it came from.

One of the three members of Celestial Circle Gate—the short youth—let out a dull cry. His left arm was pinned to the ground by the dart.

Andrela looked on calmly as Mallone's scarlet palm approached. He raised his sword. Although he was weak, he strenuously traced three specks of silver light with the tip of his sword then made them converge.

Crack.

He heard his own shoulder fracture; that was the side effect of forcefully using a secret sword.

"Three Star…Convergence!"

He thrust the sword forwards and directly stabbed Mallone's red palm.

With a 'creak', the sword was instantly bent.

"You can't even withstand a random move of mine, what 'Top Expert of the South' are you?! Looks like today is the day that I, Red Python Fist Mallone, make a name for myself! Hahahaha!" Mallone was finally unable to restrain himself and started laughing maniacally.

Suddenly his expression changed. He sensed something from his front left flying towards him at a high speed. The force of it brought about a sharp whizzing sound. Hastily, he shifted his palm to block in that direction.

Wham!

A dull thud.

"What the..! What was that?!"

Mallone's body flew backwards diagonally, his scarlet palm blocking a small white pebble.

The pebble was rotating at a high speed in the middle of his palm. The violent friction gave off a burnt smell. The immense force caused his body to skid backwards for a dozen steps before stopping.

His feet had created two visible black skid marks on the ground.

"A pe…pebble?!"

Mallone was stunned. He clutched the pebble in his hand, incredulous, and quickly looked towards the direction where it came from.

In the courtyard, Garen's eyes were shut, and a wisp of green smoke was rising from his right hand. It was obvious that the pebble was thrown by him.

"You're a Grandmaster of Combat too, right?" Garen put down his hand, "Just happens that the last duel didn't cure my itch for a good fight. Come, fight me."

"Kid! Do you know who I am?!" Mallone threw away the pebble in his hand, and a sneer showed on his face. "I am the legendary unbeaten Red Python Fist Mallone!"

"I was merely out of form earlier. Forget it. For Celestial Circle Gate Master Lourdannon's sake, I'll spare you this time. Don't let me see you again! The next time we meet, don't blame me for being merciless!"

He scoffed twice, then leaped into the crowd and disappeared.

Garen's face twitched; he wanted to say something, but couldn't manage a word.

"Mallone…So that's him!" the Great Elder of Celestial Circle Gate was speechless. "His nickname had always been Dwarf Red Rat, since when did he become Red Python Fist? No wonder he looked familiar."

Chapter 110: Farce 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

All the martial arts practitioners were in a bustle.

After witnessing Seven Moon Gate's hidden force being a despicable Grandmaster of Combat like Mallone, they started to look at members of Seven Moon Gate strangely.

Disciples and students of Seven Moon Gate wanted to hide their faces in shame; they were red in the face and ears and hung their heads low.

Even the Second Elder and several senior officials from the corporate group couldn't stand the shame, and turned to leave with their people.

The Great Elder had green veins popping out on his pale face. He was a retired confederal general—not one of those casual officers—but a real military commander with widespread influence and immense power. When he came into contact with Mallone and other martial art practitioners, hearing how Mallone toots his own horn, he didn't think much of the other so-called "Grandmasters of Combat". He had a Grandmaster of Combat by his side too, who was the strongest of them all, the unbeaten Red Python Fist Mallone.

Just from his title you could tell he was powerful. Coupled with witnessing Mallone easily defeat competing martial arts practitioners, including two famous ones, the Great Elder who initially had doubts became more confident, and didn't doubt the veracity of Mallone's title.

Now, he couldn't believe that Mallone actually fled on his debut!

Suddenly gazes of disdain were directed at him from all around; the din of chatter sounded like buzzing bees.

Puff!

The Great Elder spit out a mouthful of blood, and fell over backwards.

"Spitting blood again… This old man only knows how to spit blood!" the elder from Celestial Circle Gate was speechless. "If not for my martial arts being abolished, I wouldn't be able to help myself in giving him two good slaps!"

"Elder, I think he won't make it this time…" Xin Luo, who had just gotten up, whispered beside the elder.

Sure enough, the disciples from Seven Moon Gate all rushed over in panic.

"The Great Elder has passed out in shock! Quick, get him to the hospital!"

"Send him to the military zone general hospital! Who has any acute medicine? Quick, someone perform CPR!"

"Apply pressure to the heart, quickly!"

In the commotion, members of Seven Moon Gate finally carried the Great Elder—who had temporarily regained consciousness—and made a swift exit.

Rampas anxiously stayed by the Great Elder's side. Even though he had an altercation with the Great Elder because of Garen, the Great Elder had always taken good care of him.

Before he left, he turned around to look at Garen who was standing silently in the courtyard; there was a complexity in his gaze.

The Seven Moon Gate who had arrived aggressively suddenly became a farce.

Everyone's gaze quickly fell back onto Andrela and Garen.

"I owe you my life," Andrela took a deep breath, swiftly took a pill handed to him by the girl from the group of three Celestial Circle Gate members, and swallowed it.

"Rest assured, in my honor, my faction in Celestial Circle Gate won't find trouble with you from here on out. Also, I will give you a full explanation. You have to be careful, the Black Mark Association and the Gate Master won't let this go peacefully. Finally, this defeat, I will claim it back."

Garen didn't say anything. His body relaxed, and he gradually shrunk to his normal state.

He looked on as members of Celestial Circle Gate gradually left carrying their injured. He walked to the pond in the courtyard; the goldfish in the pond were swimming about without a care in the world.

Jaimea Lilliette and the others from Circling Dance Gate walked over. Taking in the messy courtyard, they didn't say anything, but merely looked at Garen.

Phew…

Garen let out a long sigh. Suddenly he felt an immense sense of relief.

The spectators gradually dispersed. The Master of Red Obsidian Gate begrudgingly led his disciples back.

The unification plan of Celestial Circle Gate and Black Mark Association had been completely halted by Garen.

As long as Garen was at Southern Twelve Gates, it wouldn't be so easy for Celestial Circle Gate and Black Mark Association to unify all the forces. After this battle, Garen had become the emblem of Southern Twelve Gates. The leaders of the sects that left had a clear idea of the situation now; they had only two choices.

One was to maintain the existence of their sect and align with Garen for refuge. The second was to dissolve their sect and merge with the Black Mark Association.

No one wanted to dissolve their sect and merge with Black Mark Association to be managed by someone else. After all, these were martial arts inherited through the years. Each sect had their own beliefs and ideals, which was not something they would simply give up over some benefits.

Now, as long as Garen didn't fall, Southern Twelve Gates would not completely fail as the obstructive force against unification.

As time passed, the crowd dispersed from Circling Dance Gate. Even the police maintaining security had left in their police cars. The lockdown on the area had been lifted and traffic resumed.

The girls at Circling Dance Gate bolted the broken door in the courtyard. Garen retrieved a checkbook from his room, wrote a number on it and handed it to Jaimea Lilliette.

"This is for the damage caused to the site during the fight. Take it."

Jaimea Lilliette wasn't sanctimonious. She really needed the money now. She received the check and looked at the number on it: one million!

"How generous."

Garen smiled. "This matter with Celestial Circle Gate is temporarily resolved, I should return." He had slowly been removed from the sphere of an ordinary high school student. Coupled with the fact that his mental age was far beyond the seventeen years of a high school student, there was no point in going back to school anymore.

Moreover, there were loose ends that needed tying up. Celestial Circle Gate and Black Mark Association had merely retreated temporarily. The matter with Sylphalan remained unresolved. Members of the Immortal Palace were unusually mysterious; they were untraceable.

Garen was sure that Sylphalan didn't intend to kill him, but he seemed to have taken something from him in their previous encounter. He checked for a long time, but didn't discover what was missing. All he could do was keep wondering.

He didn't know why Sylphalan wanted to draw him out. It could be part of Black Mark Association's plan; it could be something that he had on him; it could be some other reason.

What he could sense, was the complex and inexplicable attitude Sylphalan had towards him.

Then there was the issue of supporting Southern Twelve Gates, and Su Lin's matter.

Apart from those two things, there was still the matter of relying on Detective Dale to track down the Antiques of Tragedy. Dale Quicksilver and the others were still in Blue Gulf City, Evenia Province investigating this case.

These three aspects of matters seemed independent, but had a common thread.

That is, Immortal Palace seemed to be involved behind the scenes in all of them.

What Garen needed to do was investigate each matter thoroughly, and in the process, continually search for Antiques of Tragedy to enhance his true strength.

That was his current purpose.

"Are you going back?" asked Imogen Lilliette, a hint of disappointment in her voice. "Can't you stay for a while longer to give us guidance?"

"Next time, hehe," Garen detached from the mode of Grandmaster of Combat, and replied with a grin.

"So when are you leaving?" Jaimea Lilliette, in contrast, asked casually.

"I'll need to trouble you to help me buy some clothes." Garen awkwardly pointed at his bare upper body; even his white pants were soiled. "Walking out like this doesn't seem too appropriate."

"Yes, indeed." Although Jaimea Lilliette still maintained an unusually cold attitude, but the way she looked at Garen had very much softened.

**********************

The battle at Circling Dance Gate shocked the entire martial arts world in the South.

The principal person at Celestial Circle Gate, Eldest Senior Brother Andrela, had been defeated by Garen of White Cloud Gate in a direct confrontation. This meant that the momentum in unifying the Southern martial arts world had been halted.

There were currently seven major sects within the Southern Twelve Gates. Apart from Seven Moon Gate which had suffered a drastic decline in power due to the plunge in their reputation, the other five major sects combined with the rest from Southern Twelve Gates had spontaneously formed a coalition organization to counter the rise of Black Mark Association. This organization held the top expert of the South, White Bird Holy Fist Palosa as their leader, and was acknowledged by Palosa. Coupled with the reputation of Garen of Southern Twelve Gates defeating Andrela of Celestial Circle Gate, the fame of both Palosa and Garen gathered a large group of people with noble aspirations who had long resented Celestial Circle Gate, Black Mark Association and Crimson Sand Sword.

Moreover, this organization had inadvertently obtained a 'no-intervention' policy from Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword. Under the situation where external forces maintained a neutral stance, the battle with Black Mark Association was extremely intense. Formal martial arts challenges between the two sides constantly emerged, but none at the level of Grandmaster of Combat. However, both sides kept urging companions to join in the fight, making the scope of the battle larger and wider, and the intensified conflicts elevated.

After a period of stalemates, the organization officially announced the establishment of a unified force named 'Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate', implying that it was the supreme fist arts sect of the South.

While Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate and Black Mark Association were battling, Garen returned to Huaishan City to handle things at school. He applied for a temporary suspension and started sorting out the affairs of White Cloud Gate. But the first person he had to face was the person in control of the assets of White Cloud Gate, Bovini.

*********************

Huaishan City

At a building downtown.

In an extravagant room.

Garen and Bovini sat across from each other, a cup of hot coffee in front of each. The strong aroma of coffee slowly filled the air.

Garen didn't speak. He was invited by Bovini to come.

Sitting on the couch, he recalled his time since transmigrating here. He had experienced an infinitely more interesting life than in his past life on earth. It was no longer dull, no longer boring, no longer repeating a mechanical, monotonous life, and was no longer submersed in the monotony of life to the state of depression, deterioration and finally, rot.

He ran his fingers on the delicate texture of the white porcelain cup; he could only feel the slight warmth of the hot coffee through the wall of the mug.

Garen snapped out of his thoughts, and looked up at the bald stout man sitting opposite him.

"Mr Bovini, you've invited me here to…?"

Bovini had a relaxed smile on his face. He took out a document which he had put to a side and placed it on the table beside Garen.

"Mr Garen, these are the various properties transferred to your name, with asset valuations by the valuation company on the side. Please have a look."

"Transferred to my name?" Garen was slightly stunned.

"Of course." Bovini slowly took a sip of coffee. "You have been through hell and back for White Cloud Gate and made such a huge contribution. Transferring some properties to your personal name is no big deal. I imagine even if Master Fei woke up, he wouldn't blame me for such a trivial thing."

Garen instantly understood what Bovini meant.

All the properties of White Cloud Dojo were under Fei Baiyun's name. It didn't mean anything to him. It was his master's assets, he couldn't utilize them, and didn't even have the right to manage or intervene. Now that White Cloud Gate was withering, he was the only one left to call the shots. Bovini's intent was to invite him to the dinner table splitting the assets of White Cloud Gate, and shut his mouth by offering him some practical benefits.

"Mr Bovini, I think you have misjudged me," Garen couldn't help but laugh, and shook his head slightly.

Bovini's expression remained unchanged; he maintained a passive smile.

"It's alright. We can discuss this slowly. We'll find a common point of exchange eventually."

He calmly took out a stack of documents from the briefcase by his side and put them in front of Garen.

"Please have a look first."

Garen picked it up and glanced at it. The documents were the asset transfer agreements for the casino, factory and antiques trading company under White Cloud Gate respectively, all effective upon his signature. Attached were the asset valuation report and a Confederal Industrial and Commercial Bank check—the amount written on it was 20 million dollars.

Chapter 111: Cleaning 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What do you mean by this? Are you trying to bribe me?" Garen put down the documents and asked calmly.

"How can you call it a bribe?" Bovini smiled. "This is just a simple exchange, where we each get what we need. What do you think?"

Garen smiled too. He felt a sense of contempt and absurdity.

"What a pity. Maybe you think that without the White Cloud Gate, you can become independent and completely control all the assets. But I'm not interested in getting involved in your business."

Bovini's expression changed a little. "So what you mean is…?"

"I'll take these." Garen stood up and collected the transfer documents. "Alright, it's settled then. I still have other matters to attend to. I'll make a move first."

As he watched Garen's figure slowly walk out the door and leave, Bovini's face showed a trace of confusion.

"Did he agree? Or…? Forget it, as long as he's taken the documents, it's fine." He gradually felt more reassured.

After exiting the building, Garen walked straight to a red horse carriage stopped by the roadside.

Inside the carriage sat a black-haired youth wearing a grey overcoat.

"It's up to you now, Jim." Garen stepped into the carriage and patted the youth's shoulder. "We have to let Bovini realize that he can't do anything without us."

"As the local manager for Golden Hoop, this is my duty. Since Mr. Six told me to obey your every order before leaving, I certainly will not reject," the youth said calmly. "Nonetheless, the procedures at school are done, what do you plan to do next? To tell you the truth, Golden Hoop's forces locally are mediocre. The most we can mobilize is thirty to forty people. The plan cannot work by relying on us alone."

"What's going on? I thought you could previously mobilize a lot of people in a short amount of time?" Garen asked, confused.

"It's all because of you," the youth complained. "Our local operations have been suppressed to the limit. My application to manage Huaishan City seems like a mistake from the start. No, I need to start applying to be transferred to other cities. Staying here around you is too problematic."

The youth Jim was the local ordinary staff manager for Golden Hoop, also known by the titles of intelligence chief, periphery administrator and so on. Apart from the ranked Golden Hoop members, the remainder periphery Golden Hoop members— technically nobodies—are assigned under him.

From an external perspective, he was considered the leader of two local groups.

"It doesn't matter. As long as the goal is achieved."

Garen smiled. The carriage began to move. The driver was from Golden Hoop too, but he completely ignored the conversation between the two people behind him.

"I've been back from Dinah City for more than twenty days. If I had waited for Su Lin to help me out of the tight spot, I would probably be long dead. Any news from Number 6?"

"Mister will arrive in Huaishan today, if the trains are on time," Jim said in a hushed tone. He stretched his wrist out to look at his watch. "It's now 11 o'clock. He should arrive at three. And plus, you can't say that. Mister was relieved when he heard that you managed to get yourself out of that tight spot, which is why he didn't go out of his way to make a trip over. Otherwise, he would have been here within ten days. The reason he's delayed his trip was merely to help you tie up the loose ends."

"So.. I should thank him?" Garen was speechless.

Half an hour later, the carriage slowly drove to a small, remote restaurant. The restaurant was desolate; barely a handful of people were dining inside. The only customers dining were youths wearing white robes. They were the branch students of the reopened White Cloud Dojo.

Garen stepped off the carriage and walked into the small restaurant.

A girl in a green dress who was bored inside immediately greeted him. The girl was slim and had large breasts. She looked quite pretty, and gave off an impression of innocence and charm.

"I've reserved the private room for you. Please follow me."

"Thank you." Garen had been dining here recently. The restaurant was small; there was only one main area and one private room. The owner who managed the place was a middle-aged man. The girl responsible for cleaning up was this thirteen-year-old girl in green dress he adopted. Additionally, there was the chef he hired. Father and daughter ran the restaurant near the dojo branch, and relied on business from students to make a meager living.

Their food wasn't very good. It was average, but more importantly it was clean. And the beautiful and adorable figure of the girl was pleasing to the eyes too.

Garen was wearing jeans and a white t-shirt, his strong muscles tight against his clothes. Below his indigo hair was a pair of clear dark red eyes. His actions and words conveyed an inexplicable authority, as though his physical stature was oppressive enough to crush opponents with weaker willpower.

When the green-dress girl first stood in front of Garen, she actually felt weak at the knees and didn't dare to look up into his calm red eyes. It was the type of strong confidence which gave him the ability to stay calm in the face of any situation.

Garen followed the girl into the only private room. Since he entered the restaurant, everyone else seemed to quieten in his oppressive presence. It wasn't until he completely entered the private room that they resumed their loud chatter. The gaze of a few youths curiously followed him into the private room, then slowly retracted.

After walking into the clean and tidy private room with red walls and sitting down on a wooden yellow chair, Garen ordered a few familiar dishes. The green-dress girl hurried out of the room to prepare them.

As the door closed, he could vaguely hear her let out a deep sigh of relief.

Garen smiled helplessly.

"Ever since that battle with Andrela, my Bravery is getting stronger. Even if I concealed all of it, it would still unconsciously affect others. How troublesome."

"Some people want it but can't have it, yet you complain that it's troublesome," Su Lin's voice came from outside the door. He pushed the door open to enter. He was wearing an ordinary black t-shirt and jeans, similar to Garen's. But his physique was slender, which gave the impression that he had a gentle temperament. The only imperfection was his eye-catching red hair which ruined the whole look.

"I saw you come in, so I followed."

"I thought you said you would only reach at three o'clock?" Garen casually asked as he watched Su Lin walk to the chair by the table to sit down.

"That was a ruse. If everyone could easily grasp my whereabouts, then there would be absolutely no security at all," Su Lin smiled as he sat down.

"Have you settled things with your parents and sister?"

"They are under my uncle's care. They shouldn't be involved in our world." Garen shook his head. "They should be allowed to just lead a quiet life. The Manleyton Corporation has retreated from Huaishan, the whole city is now under the control of our family. Covertly protecting the safety of a few people shouldn't be too much trouble, right?"

"According to the rules, they are indeed not in much danger. Even though you're getting more and more famous in the martial arts world, but you're still relatively unknown in other areas. The possibility that your family is targeted is low. After all, no one would dare break the rules. Whoever starts the fight would have to expect an opponent without scruples. With your current true strength, even if you retreated behind the scenes, Celestial Circle Gate would probably still be concerned," Su Lin chuckled. "But the stronger your true strength, the more useful it would be for me."

"How are the state of things now? The specific situation," Garen poured some cheap black tea for the both of them, took a sip and asked.

"The state of things…is a little complicated. But it's simpler after a detailed analysis," Su Lin paused, seemingly thinking about how to phrase his answer.

"Currently, three forces in play have been determined, you excluded. Celestial Circle Gate is with Crimson Sand Sword, Black Mark Association is a force on its own, and Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate another."

"Celestial Circle Gate and Crimson Sand Sword are not homogeneous with Black Mark Association. Even though they have formed a temporary union, but the pie that is the Southern martial arts world which they’ve jointly broke up, they each want a piece. So they've been expanding wildly and challenging others along the way. Members of Black Mark Association almost got into conflict with members from Crimson Sand Sword. It seems that in the process of integrating the South, they are using the opportunity to expand their own influence. All three forces seem to be competing against each other. "

Su Lin paused and glanced at Garen who was listening attentively." Celestial Circle Gate has temporarily retreated because of you. Andrela has played a big part in this. He has openly declared that he owes his life to you. Everyone understood what he meant. Even if you've killed Ni Tenstar, but anytime you are in danger and need help, the branch that he, Andrela, commands, will instantly come to your aid. All to repay the life debt that he owes you. No one doubts the authenticity of his words. Rumor has it that when he said those words, Andrela was publicly slapped by the Celestial Circle Gate Master, and was heavily injured to the extent that he vomited blood on the spot. But this did not diminish his respected status and influence in the eyes of other disciples. So to avoid internal conflict, Celestial Circle Gate won't take any action against you. But that's not the case with Black Mark Association.

"What about the other two forces?" Garen was clear about the consequences of saving Andrela. This was a man who took his promises seriously; he didn't easily offer promises, but once he had promised something it will be honored. So he had already anticipated Celestial Circle Gate's attitude from the start.

"Black Mark Association seems to be indifferent. They are of the opinion that Andrela's true strength was being exaggerated, so they are not taking it seriously. And naturally they do not think much of you, the person who defeated Andrela. They have produced three Fist Master Grade experts internally. I predict that you will face them sooner or later. Crimson Sand Sword, on the other hand, are fully aware of Andrela's true strength before he was seriously injured, so they will be more restrained in their attitude towards you. Lastly, Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. Merely established for a dozen days or so, they are simply referred to as Southern Holy Gate. Due to personal emotional involvement, three people stood up against the three Fist Master Grade Grandmasters of Combat from Black Mark Association. Initially, these three were not experts from the South, but because their acquaintances were injured by Black Mark Association, so they are now involved formally as a major force against them. They are styled as Divine Marshals by members of the Southern Holy Gate, collectively known as the Three Divine Marshals!"

"The Three Divine Marshals? What an impressive name. But how is their true strength?" Garen murmured.

"I'm sorry, you are one of them," Su Lin giggled as he said it.

"Huh?" Garen was stunned. "Me?"

"Yeap," Su Lin suppressed his laughter and nodded. "You are the strongest among the three in Southern Holy Gate, one of the Three Divine Marshals: the Mammoth."

"So I'm named after my Secret Martial Art? I thought they would give me a better nickname," Garen sounded disappointed. "But out of the blue I've become one of the so-called Three Divine Marshals, I'm really speechless. They've set a position for me without me even knowing about it."

"It can't be helped. It wasn't easy for Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate to find a Grandmaster of Combat who is able to oppose Black Mark Association in a short amount of time. You are merely filling in to make up the numbers, just like White Bird Holy Fist senior who was summoned to hoist the banner. Anyway, there is no disadvantage to you, just accept it." Su Lin shrugged.

"Now, I believe it's time for you to help me?"

Chapter 112: Cleaning 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"No problem." Garen nodded. "Before that, I need you to help me locate Senior Sister and Senior Brother. Also, I need to make sure the situation in Huaishan City is under control. There are still some things I need to take care of."

"Sure, I can help you with that. I will talk to the authorities. You don’t need to worry about anything after those mice are dealt with." Su Lin smiled, he was in a good mood.

"We need to finish Manleyton Corporation and Bouvini off. I’ll send you some people to do the management if you want. Also, what about your uncle?" he continued.

"I will handle it," Garen said with a light tone. He was much stronger than before, and with the help of Su Lin, he could easily handle all of those issues.

However, Garen had never told his sister and parents about what he was doing. They thought that he went on a trip with Master Fei Baiyun and had no idea how bad the situation was.

Su Lin knew Garen had made up his mind. "Finding Rosetta and Farak may take some time. They just disappeared without leaving a trace."

"It’s fine, just keep searching while I am away." Garen knew it was impossible to find them in a day or two.

"Sure."

The dishes finally arrived. There were several Asian style pan-fried dishes served with rice. Although the flavor was average, the food was to Garen’s taste.

Su Lin was efficient. He led his special army to Manleyton Corporation, accused them of Antique Scalping and arrested whoever was left there. Someone had passed a message earlier to several elites of the corporation, and they escaped before Su Lin’s team arrived.

**************************

Ten days later.

In a deep forest outside Huaishan City.

The last force of Manleyton Corporation was surrounded in a mansion. There were many gunshots going on at the place. Su Lin and Garen stayed behind the guards, surveying the white mansion from a distance.

"Our people are having trouble breaking in. It is probably the last force Manleyton Corporation has, and there are many elites inside it. They are doing a pretty good job of defending their position." Su Lin smiled and looked at Garen. "How about we just wait here until they decide to surrender? I don’t want to lose anyone in my team."

"I will do it myself I guess." Garen looked at the rifles sticking out of the windows and shook his head.

He did not wait for Su Lin to respond and just walked straight toward the mansion. His body kept inflating while walking, so Su Lin ordered his soldiers to stay out of Garen’s way.

"Is this guy trying to die? He’s not even wearing a bullet proof suit. Who the hell is this guy? A superhero? His body is inflating?" One of the young soldiers behind the tree said in a light tone, mocking Garen.

"Shut the hell up!" Another soldier beside him slapped the young soldier’s head. "You’re talking about Master Garen. He’s one of the three Divine Marshals from the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate. He can easily deal with those punks."

"Tsk, I don’t think he can resist bullets." The young man was not convinced, but he decided not to argue with the leader and lowered his head.

"Dumbass."

Garen did not hear their conversation. He kept on walking toward the mansion’s gate.

"It’s Divine Marshal Garen!" Someone inside the mansion yelled in a shaky tone. He sounded desperate and scared.

"Bring it on!"

"We can’t just sit here and wait!" several others yelled.

Suddenly, the place became deathly silent.

There were no gunshots going on anymore.

Garen stood in front of the white iron gate, but he could not sense anyone pointing a rifle at him. After becoming a Grandmaster of Combat, Garen’s sense was keener than before, and he could easily find the people that weren’t hiding their intention to kill. To him, it was as easy as finding a shining dot of light in the dark.

Su Lin’s soldiers stopped firing after the mansion became silent. They were confused, and some of them were trying to peek inside through the windows, but did not see anything moving. It seemed like the Manleyton Corporation’s last force had already given up.

"What’s going on? They surrendered?"

"I don’t know, they aren’t firing anymore."

"Let’s wait for orders."

Garen stood in front of the gate quietly, his body still inflating to 1.9 meters tall. Although he was still weaker than in his final form, his defense was already incredibly high.

It was quiet.

Sunlight penetrated the leaves that were falling from the tree, and the wind blew them away. After the gunshots stopped, Garen could hear birds twittering and insects chirping.

Hoo!

Several dry leaves dropped down from the tree again due to the wind. Garen slowly reached out to the handles of the gate.

Boom!

As Garen’s fingers touched the handle,Manleyton Corporation’s force started firing again.

Garen rushed forward, bullets were coming toward him from all angles. The noise of gunfire suddenly returned, and he could barely determine where all the gunshots were coming from. Garen crashed through the white iron gate with his fists. It broke into pieces and collapsed inward.

Garen was locked on by four enemies, and they kept firing toward him.

Dan!

Garen was in the line of fire, but he kept stepping forward. He travelled more than ten meters after three steps. A one-eyed man had a submachine gun in his hands right in front of Garen, and Garen hit the man in the face.

Crack!

The man’s head exploded, and he dropped his gun to the floor. Garen did not stop. He found the other three and finished them all, then looked for more targets. Although his speed was slower than the best Martial Artists’, he was still much faster than normal people.

The bullets did no damage to Garen. It was like they were hitting a steel plate.

Finally, Garen found the last elite of Manleyton Corporation. The man was choking with tears in his eyes. He saw Garen coming for him, the horrifying shadow getting bigger and bigger in his sight.

The elite had a crazed look on his face, and he was laughing.

He quickly took something black out of the pouch on his waist.

"Let’s die together… heh… together…" The man pulled the ring off the grenade and held it in his right hand. Garen stayed calm. He chopped off the man’s right wrist with his hand right after he figured out what the man was trying to do.

Pon!

The man’s right arm detached and flew to the corner, blood splashing all over the ground.

Boom!

The grenade exploded, and mud was everywhere. Garen could smell the gunpowder in the air.

Garen took the man by his throat and lifted him up. The crazed man took out a pistol and kept shooting at Garen’s chest.

"Grasping at straws." Garen broke the man’s neck without applying a lot of force. He put down the body carelessly and walked inside the patio.

There were still people shooting at him from the second floor, and some were even throwing grenades at him.

Pon!

Garen only blocked the grenades that went close to him. Although there were explosions all over the place, the further ones were of no threat to him.

Garen stood in front of the mansion and pulled the lock out of the door with his fingers. He then pushed the door open and entered the mansion. The gunfire inside stopped, and Su Lin’s soldiers started firing to suppress the enemy.

Several of Su Lin’s elite soldiers followed Garen, splitting into two groups after entering the building. Garen stood by the entrance and looked at the second floor.

Pon!

A bullet hit his eye lid, and it sparked a bit. Garen had closed his eyes right after seeing the enemy was about to fire. The scene made the soldiers around him speechless. No one had ever seen anything like this before.

"I want that one alive," Garen spoke in a light tone.

"But…" The lieutenant’s voice was shaking. It was not the fear that made him shake, his body was just naturally reacting to danger.

Garen did not wait for the lieutenant to finish his words, he just entered the first floor of the building.

He saw a large living room first. Everything was white here, and he saw several religious sculptures in the room. On the left, there was a spiral staircase that was connected to the second floor.

The soldiers that had entered the building with him were already fighting by the stairs, judging by the sound of gunshots he could hear.

Garen did not stop, he kept going upstairs.

Before he could reach the second floor, the staircase collapsed, and lime was blown into the air. Garen fell to the first floor. He raised his head and looked at the second floor.

He saw several people, Cynthia among them. The elite bodyguard captain of Manleyton Corporation was hurt, and there was blood on her face.

"I’m done… I am Assassin Bichurin… I can’t just die like this. This place is narrow, and there is no audience. There is nothing around here! I didn’t even find a worthy opponent…"

There were only four enemies guarding the stairs and the windows.

The leader was a middle-aged man with a scar on his face. He finished his sentence and drew his scimitar. He was ready to engage.

Cynthia had no expression on her face. Although she was hurt, she looked calm and was even whistling.

"I am so dead… Divine Marshal Garen of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate… I knew it! I knew I should not have stayed with you guys! Wah…" A tall handsome man was crying like a baby and trembling in fear.

"Kaiser, you weak ass bastard! Why don’t you find a way to deal with that monster if you have the time to cry!" The last woman in black yelled, holding submachine gun in her hands.

There were bodies everywhere on the second floor. The blood was dripping off the stairs, and the fishy smell in the air made people sick.

Chapter 113: Cleaning 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Cynthia looked at the strongest of the captain-rank companions around her. Three out of seven were killed, only these four were left. Last time, when she was companions with Garen, she didn't think anything of it. Now that they were opponents standing in front of each other, she felt the suffocating and terrifying pressure.

It was like facing a dozen-storey tall dark blue wave. It was the terrifying pressure of realizing that there was no way to dodge, no escape, and direct confrontation would only result in being devoured and drowned!

The dark blue wave that covered everything in sight was advancing towards her; even her breathing started to quicken, and her body temperature fell.

Clap!

Cynthia fiercely gave herself a slap, and instantly snapped out of the illusion of pressure.

"Am I breaking?" she muttered.

Only someone who was about to suffer a mental breakdown would experience such illusions. She went through death training before when she was very weak and had experienced it once, but it wasn't as terrifying as the suffocating pressure from downstairs.

Hrfff… Whooo…

She hung her head low and started taking deep breaths.

"It's going to be alright… It's going to be alright… I can do it. I will definitely be able to find a way to break through. Definitely!"

**************

Downstairs.

Garen looked up at the broken steps on the staircase leading up to the first floor and frowned. He turned around to look at the military captain awaiting his orders.

"Break through it."

He pointed at the ground floor ceiling.

Bang bang bang bang!

Dozens of submachine guns were raised and fired towards the ceiling.

This was a small building constructed with cement-bonded wood fiber. The partition between the ground and first floor was not completely concrete; it was effortlessly punctured under the powerful impact of the submachine guns.

A large number of bullets shot through the first floor flooring like rain drops and ricocheted within the small living room on the first floor.

Crash!

A large celadon vase in the corner of the room was hit by a stray bullet and shattered into countless pieces.

Cynthia and the others crouched closely together in a corner and tried as much as possible to reduce the surface area of their bodies, but two of them were still hit multiple times to the extent that they resembled hornet's nests. The space on the first floor was limited; there was no way to effectively avoid the gunfire.

Cynthia and the captain could be considered the strongest two among all of them. In haste, the method which they chose to evade the bullets was the most effective, so they didn't suffer much harm. One got hit in the face, and the other in the left shin. At least compared to the other two, they were already very lucky.

Huff… huff… huff…

Their heavy breathing was clearly audible in the quiet space.

"Cynthia."

Garen's voice came from the first floor.

"Killing you would be as simple as crushing an ant to me. Surrender, and both of you can live in this situation. I acknowledge your true strength," Garen downstairs looked up towards the first floor and said calmly. He was indeed making the offer out of appreciation of talent.

The operational model of Manleyton Corporation differed from other companies. To prevent the concentration of power at the upper tiers, all staff would transfer teams from time to time. Constantly scattering and constantly changing, the relationship between members was detached. This was the reason he dared to solicit the other party after killing so many people from Manleyton. Moreover, White Cloud Gate currently lacked elite talent that completely belonged to him.

"It seems, among the Three Divine Marshals, you are the most mediocre one." Cynthia didn't speak. Instead, it was the other old man's voice that came from above.

Garen gestured for the soldiers to spread out, and addressed the people on first floor alone.

"From the sound of it, you've met the other two Divine Marshals?"

"Of course. They are strong and cruel. Anyone confirmed as an enemy would face their full wrath," the man replied. "But you're different. You would alter your benefit analysis based on your mood or some other reason and come up with the best solution. Am I right?"

Garen unconsciously smiled.

"Not bad. You are indeed worthy of being a talent who has survived till now. If you join White Cloud Gate, I will assign you to a suitable position. Choose: join, or die."

"The alternative of refusal is death. This is your idea of a choice?" Cynthia said sarcastically.

"Death is equally a choice." Contrary to Cynthia, Garen nodded calmly. "Well, it was your corporation that betrayed me first. A force that is familiar with my details, expecting to safely escape my sphere of influence. Don't you think that's too naïve?"

The first floor remained silent. After a while, the sound of two guns being dumped on the ground could be heard.

Garen put his hands into his pockets, turned around and headed out the door. He had his answer from the way they breathed.

"Go upstairs and bring the two of them down. Give them medical treatment and a good rest."

"Yes, sir." The military captain quickly saluted Garen. Speaking to Garen at spitting distance, he recalled the outrageous scene earlier. The captain had already listed Garen as someone he would absolutely not provoke.

Su Lin walked in from the courtyard.

"It's over?"

"Yes, it's over here." Garen nodded. He removed his torn t-shirt in one swift move, and changed into a t-shirt of the same style handed over to him.

"You're not worried they'll trick you?"

"It's fine. The risk of loss is inevitable if you want to reap the rewards."

"Next, you plan to…"

"Let's check on Bovini," Garen said calmly.

"He's now half alive after being tortured by the 'triad' members," Su Lin was delighted about Bovini's misfortune.

"It can't be helped. Nobody asked him to declare leaving White Cloud Gate. Property incapable of being defended are naturally alluring pieces of meat. What a pity. If Mr Bovini was still part of White Cloud Gate, I would offer my full assistance in punishing those unruly 'triads'. But now it's none of my business." Garen smiled.

"Sometimes I wonder if you're really seventeen." Su Lin was speechless and started smiling too.

"There will always be people who are considered geniuses in this world. Unfortunately, I'm one of them." Garen boasted without blushing.

"Brag on, you!" Su Lin patted him, speechless.

The two of them walked towards the direction they came from, and soon disappeared into the woods.

********************

A few days later.

Garen was sitting cross-legged in the middle of the White Cloud Martial Colosseum, his eyes closed.

Across from him, also sitting cross-legged on the floor, were Collin and Simon. The entire Colosseum capable of accommodating 200 people was empty apart from them.

Recently, Garen had a growing feeling that his martial arts had gradually entered a stage where it couldn't be explicitly assessed. The Qi, blood and spirit of his body were completely in sync, as if all of his previously latent true strength was gradually being explored and utilized.

"The human body is a large treasure trove," he slowly spoke. The two people opposite him were instantly invigorated and listened attentively. It was a golden opportunity to be able to receive personal guidance from the current Garen.

"Even if it were an average person, as long as he is able to thoroughly tap into his potential, they can exhibit amazing power too," Garen said softly with his eyes closed.

"The method I'm teaching you is to be used in training exercises. Spend half an hour a day meditating, and consciously perceive the favorable and unfavorable factors generated in training within your entire body."

"The Secret Martial Art of White Cloud Gate is sufficiently intense, but lacks solidification. This is something that I have only recently realized. It's difficult to find a suitable Secret Martial Art to aid in solidification in such a short amount of time, so I've chosen to use this method. Focus on your meditating for half an hour. There will be students to remind you when the time is up."

"Yes, Eldest Senior Brother," they answered in tandem, and closed their eyes. They would never doubt Garen's words, because his actual personal progress was already evidence that the method was effective.

Garen slowly got up and headed to the basement of the Colosseum.

Simon and Collin were two core disciples that he had been devoting his time and efforts to coach recently. There were many core disciples at White Cloud Gate, but they were the most distinguished. If he wanted to successfully train two right-hand men in a short amount of time, they were his best hope.

Fortunately, both of them were aware that it was a critical period for White Cloud Gate—which needed the backing of powerful forces—so they have progressed rapidly. They weren't lacking in foundation skills in the first place, so now under Garen's personal tutelage, they have naturally improved by leaps and bounds. They had exceeded their peers and were now on par with adult Martial Adepts.

A few days ago Simon even went for a test; his Amateur Stage had reached Stage Six. This could be considered a qualified level even among adult Martial Adepts. After all, Second Senior Brother Farak was only at Amateur Stage Nine.

In comparison, Collin was similar. Both improved at a perceptible pace.

But Garen was able to see that Simon's limit was at Stage Seven. He had lost an arm, and any further training would be impeded by this inherent defect. If in future he didn't possess extremely strong willpower to persevere, this would be it for his entire lifetime.

Collin, on the other hand, could still improve. Since they returned, he had taken them both as disciples. Under his unreserved tutelage, coupled with Collin's immense potential, she could probably reach Eldest Senior Sister's level by 25 years old.

Of course that referred to Rosetta's true strength on the surface, after concealment. Her actual true strength was unknown, even to Garen. After all, he had never seen her fight with full strength before.

In estimation, Master, Eldest Senior Sister, and Tenstar Ni, should all be at the level on the brink of Grandmaster of Combat, that is, the peak of Grade E.

Of these so-called "grades", Grade D is the limit. Anything above that was not used to assess humans.

In other words, this alphabet grading was originally used by countries to grade firearms.

Grade E was for handguns and other small firearms, Grade D was medium-sized firearms. Going up the scale would be weapons that were even more powerful.

This was merely because martial art practitioners unwilling to be phased out by the times refused to withdraw from this stage of history, so they graded their own martial art powers with firearm gradings, all to prove that martial arts could reach a level not inferior to firearms. But alas, the highest could only be Grade D.

When he reached the staircase at the entrance, Garen turned around to look at the both of them.

"In the near future, they could both thoroughly stabilize the standing of the dojo locally," This so-called stabilization referred to the average daily challenges, teaching, training, explaining and similar tasks.

"You are planning to leave?" At the bottom of the stairs, Cynthia was leaning on a wall flipping a sharp dagger. She tossed the dagger upwards—it spiraled into a round silver wheel—then accurately caught the handle in her hand as it landed. The sound of the blade cutting through air could be heard.

"Where's Jack?"

"The car is ready. We can head over straightaway." Jack was the scar-faced captain who had surrendered together with Cynthia.

Chapter 114: Cleaning 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Alright. Let's go see that adorable chubby Bovini first. I haven't seen him for a while, I quite miss him," Garen couldn't help but laugh.

"Miss his money, you mean?"

Cynthia looked contemptuous.

Garen didn't mind. Both of them walked out of the stairwell one after the other. The students around them stared at them in awe as they exited the main dojo and stepped into a white horse carriage.

"Oh yeah, how is Master now?"

"Very well. His body is well maintained. But for some reason, he just hasn't woken up all this while." Cynthia had now become Garen's full-time secretary, replacing Grace's original role. This was the initial purpose for which the corporation sent her. Ironically, it wasn't achieved then, but achieved now after she has left the corporation.

"He hasn't woken up all this while?" Garen frowned. He suddenly thought of the illusory tactics that Sylphalan previously used. "Could it be them?"

"What did you say?"

"Nothing, let's go," Garen snapped out of his daze and said calmly.

Ever since defeating Andrela, his mind possessed a kind of fearless and strong confidence, as if there was nothing to fear in the world, and in the face of everything his body would be able to adapt seamlessly and he could confront it head on.

This was the characteristic of his strong Qi and blood, to the extent that it was at a non-human level. He wasn't sure if other Grandmasters of Combat felt this way, but it was apparent for him.

The horse carriage moved slowly, and the street on both sides gradually moved backwards.

It was now early spring. On the streets of Huaishan, some farmers carried baskets of fresh vegetables for sale.

The surface of the streets was wet; it was obvious that it had rained yesterday.

Soon, their white horse carriage stopped in front of a black marble building.

The chubby Bovini was smiling ear to ear, standing at the entrance with some people. There were bruises all over his face and body. A piece of white gauze was stuck to his forehead, and one of his eyes was so swollen it couldn’t open.

"Welcome, welcome Mr Garen. The directors and I have been waiting for you for a long time."

The rest of the people around him started guffawing. Every one of them was like him, bruised all over; they looked extremely awkward.

Garen calmly said from the carriage, "You have to understand, some things are not yours to keep. Hand it over obligingly and leave Huaishan. In view of our previous friendship, I'll decide on behalf of my master: I won't pursue this matter further."

After he finished speaking, his gaze turned to Cynthia who was sitting by his side.

The latter nodded, held her handbag and stepped out of the carriage.

"Leave it to me over here. You get going. I will properly handle all the transfer documents," Cynthia said assuredly.

"Just transfer it all back under Master's name." Garen didn't need these properties. With his current status, if he wanted to make money right now, it would be a walk in the park.

"Understood."

"I'll make a move first then. Uncle is still waiting for me."

The horse carriage slowly started moving again, taking Garen to the other side where Pennington Street was.

His uncle's family on his wife's side had already been dissatisfied about inheritance matters for quite some time now.

Now that he's heard about Garen's return, his uncle immediately sent for him to meet the elders from that side of the family.

Compared to his uncle Anjer, the likes of Bovini were simply feeble nobodies.

Anjer's company footprint spanned the whole of Galantia. Even in the province they were considered a large infamous criminal group. There were even rumors that they took over an assassin-and-bodyguard type of business.

****

It was equivalent to the magnified version of Manleyton Corporation. Smuggling, drugs, gambling, arms, Anjer's company would do whatever generated a profit. Of course, they have cleaned up a lot over the years. Technically speaking, the fact that White Cloud Gate could achieve their previous status in Huaishan was merely because Anjer didn't try to control it. It was a power he chose to give up on the consideration of cleaning up.

Compared to all these industries, selling antiques was just a negligible source of income, a way to distribute some excess wealth to other local companies.

This time even Garen's uncle knew that he was coming back. It could be said that, after Bovini and the rest were humiliated by Golden Hoop, the fact that there wasn't any revenge or life-and-death battle, was partly to his uncle's credit.

So Garen attending this gathering was also a show of gratitude on behalf of White Cloud Gate.

On the matter of the competition for the industries under the control of Anjer's company, this problem was slightly more troublesome.

The other party was not to be underestimated. Anjer's company was a group that spanned a dozen cities, more than half of the province. Their immense power and influence was comparable to that of Seven Moon Gate.

Of course, this was simply referring to low and middling strengths. The comparison would be less clear if it were higher-end martial art practitioners. But to be able to survive until now is definitely not an easy feat.

Garen analyzed his uncle Anjer's situation along the journey.

Since his childhood, Anjer Group seemed to have always been stable and unusually peaceful; there didn't seem to be any major complications in its development. This was obviously the embodiment of substantial power.

It was obvious that his uncle was not as simple as he seemed. What could be certain was that behind his uncle was a strong power belonging to him, shielding the entire group at all times.

And based on his uncle's lack of understanding and exposure towards the martial arts world, it didn't seem like the power of martial art practitioners.

Garen recalled his past. His uncle had always expressed disdain at martial arts, but he did have a martial arts expert friend over as a guest.

Inviting Garen over this time, it was apparent that he wanted him to gain recognition from his wife's side. Obviously the other party still had influence over the group. Even though it wasn't enough to affect his uncle's decisions, but if something went wrong there, there would still be a certain negative impact.

Sitting in the carriage, Garen fully considered all the factors, then slowly closed his eyes to rest.

Ten or so minutes later, the carriage slowed to a stop at the end of Pennington Street, coincidentally not far across from where Dolphin Antiques used to be.

There was a garden-style private bungalow which was uninhabited all year round. He didn't expect it to be his uncle's property.

The white bungalow was surrounded by a green garden and pink Chinese roses, fenced in by a wall with white vine motifs on it.

On both sides of the white pebble trail leading to the bungalow were large patches of green grass, where two children were playing chase.

To the left of the three-storey white main building, a black patio umbrella was erected in the garden. Below it was a round table and four chairs. The three fair ladies in long dresses sat there chatting and drinking coffee. They had on black or white round hats with different colored feathers and were chatting casually; the whole affair seemed composed and elegant.

Looking into the main building from its open main door, he could vaguely make out some men wearing elegant suits talking to each other in clusters of twos and threes. Some were holding red wine, some were smoking, and there were even some who were taking notes with pen and paper.

Garen could hear some music from afar. It was piano and violin music.

At the main door, the two bodyguards clad in black standing guard at the door stepped forward and bowed respectfully to Garen.

"Young Master Garen, the director is waiting for you inside. Please come in." Someone behind immediately led the carriage to park elsewhere. The white carriage was not dreadful, but compared to the luxury cars parked around the bungalow, it seemed shabby and insignificant.

Garen frowned. He looked at the black jeans and black t-shirt he had on, although they matched well, the workmanship and material seemed ordinary, and didn't go well with such occasions.

"It's okay. The director has prepared an attire," one of the bodyguards said in a hushed tone. Garen could tell that he wasn't someone in charge of standing guard at the entrance, but someone who had purposely came out to wait for him. "Please follow me."

"Very well."

Garen followed the bodyguard and changed into a black slim suit, with a dark red tie around his neck. His indigo short hair had been tidied up. Coupled with his beautiful cool red eyes, he exuded an indifferent and elegant charm. Only the glow that occasionally flashed across his dark red eyes—when he was watching others—would convey a vague sense of vastness.

It was a temperament created by his strong martial arts power resulting in mental and physical sublimation, a sense of standing on a higher level overlooking ordinary people.

Garen evaluated his look in the mirror. When he saw the immense Momentum in his eyes, he furrowed his brow.

Facing the mirror, he made some adjustments and restrained his inner state.

It was only then that the indifference in his eyes gradually faded away.

"No matter how powerful a martial arts practitioner is, they are vulnerable in the face of firearms. It was now the era of firearms, and the era of ordinary people. Being overly affected by this Momentum would only make one more and more arrogant. One has to be vigilant," he reminded himself. Although bullets weren't a threat to him now, but explosives and artillery shells were a different matter. Even if he could withstand the blast, the immense impact would still cause instability in his Qi and blood.

Even though he had never experienced it, he vaguely felt the danger of it.

Momentum was one of the byproducts of Bravery, generated from the absolute confidence in oneself. Different from Bravery, the existence or non-existence of Momentum wouldn't affect much. Moreover, Momentum with a poor foundation would lead to self-aggrandizement, which made one vulnerable.

Bravery was not the same; it was the basis of Momentum. Astute Grandmasters of Combat had to cultivate their Bravery, something akin in nature to a force field. It wasn't merely linked to martial arts strength; it was also related to one's spiritual cultivation. It was the amalgamation of strength, Qi and spirit.

Bravery was something all Grandmasters of Combat had. If one's Bravery was suppressed by their opponent before combat, Qi and blood wouldn't be affected, but the spirit would be affected by negative emotions like shock, hesitation, panic and so on.

Once the spirit is unstable, moves will not be as intense and reactions will be slower. In critical moments, one would fall into temporary hesitation, leading to a delay in response and entering a vicious cycle of reduced pace. Eventually, one would lose the upper hand and regret bitterly.

Whereas once one manages to crush their opponent's Bravery, they can attack their opponent in a complete state with strength, Qi and spirit as one, and completely quash their opponent physically and mentally. In the end, their opponent's defeat would be the only result. An opponent defeated in this way would not even have the intention to make a comeback: it was a complete collapse of one's soul and self-esteem.

This was the fundamental power that a strong Grandmaster of Combat with remarkable Bravery had.

A truly superior Grandmaster of Combat had to have remarkable Bravery.

Apart from the boost that his special ability and Attributes gave him, the factor that really gave Garen an edge over other talented practitioners, was that his actual age was more than 17 years old, as well as the experience from his past life.

In his past life on Earth, he had lived to more than 20 years old. Environment and level decides the experiences to which one is exposed, and ultimately determines a person's maturity. These extra 20 years of experience coincidentally made up for the shortfall in his level of spiritual accomplishment to become a Grandmaster of Combat.

Chapter 115: The Conclusion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Remembering these, Garen could not help but be reminded of Andrela.

"As for me, at that age, Andrela had already entered into the rank of Grandmaster of Combat. I don’t know how much he has had to sacrifice, how much he has experienced. No wonder his spirit feels a bit abnormal. Perhaps it’s only because of such focus and extremism that has allowed him to entered into such a high level at such a young age. Compared to me, I can be said to have cheated my way in…" He was very aware that he was not some gifted being.

Reminiscing all the young masters that he had met, only Andrela had gone into the Grandmaster of Combat level. Even the performance of Beo from the Crimson Sand Sword was only close to the Grandmaster of Combat level. It was clear that he lacked the bravery. His martial arts cultivation might have been perfected, but his soul cultivation had not yet been achieved.

Tucking away his thoughts, Garen straightened up the suit he was wearing, and walked out in great strides from the wing towards the main entrance of the great hall. Uncle Anjer had already been standing by the door, coming to greet him.

"There might be a bit of trouble later. On the surface, for my sake, they will not cause you any trouble, but as for any issues with the juniors, I have no reason to interfere, so it is up to you. I have also arranged for Venia and the others to follow you. Take care of your own safety, do not rely on the fact that you’ve trained in the martial arts to pick a fight with them. Do you understand?" His uncle exhorted in a low voice.

"I understand, uncle." Garen nodded helplessly in response.

Only then was Anjer satisfied, and he reached out to pat his head, "It’s been a while since we’ve met, you’ve become taller again. It’s only been a little over a year, and you have grown so strong. That bean sprout in the past has totally vanished. Not bad, not bad."

He caressed Garen’s hair, laughing loudly. Garen, helpless, could only let him pat as much as he pleased.

"Alright, follow me in. Make sure to be a bit more polite, everyone inside is a dignitary, much stronger than your background as a master. Establishing good connections will be beneficial for you in the future."

"Okay." Garen could only nod and agree.

Just as they walked in through the doors, he saw the local governor of Huaishan City, Boravil, in the corner, who was laughingly chatting away with two middle-aged, goateed men, completely in character as an accompaniment.

"It looks like they are really not typical people." Garen was momentarily curious about his uncle’s hidden societal influence.

The strongest force he had encountered in the martial arts world were the Celestial Circle Gate and Sun Lin’s clan. Only, he did not know which level the ten or more people in this great hall belonged to in comparison.

However, these all remained mere thoughts; he still obediently followed after his uncle, putting on the polite and demure look of a junior.

Not far away, two middle-aged people, a man and a woman, were watching Garen and Anjer walk through the doors attentively.

"That is the future heir Anjer has chosen?" The woman was wearing a red, sleeveless dress, body-fitting and had a high collar; with a neat, golden ponytail tied to the side, and long, narrow blue eyes, she gave off a sharp and noble allure.

"Anjer has been working hard for a huge chunk of his lifetime. This time, he has more or less decided to retire after all the success he has achieved. However, his industry is neither here nor there. It won’t be easy for him to retire completely." The man had his arms crossed. There was a little blonde goatee on his chin, and his short hair was combed to the right; he looked unusually mild mannered.

"Actually, after the banquet this time, all cards would be on the table, yes? Then I’m guessing that there will be news tomorrow."

"Let’s wait and see." The woman laughed lightly. "Compared to this Garen, I am more inclined towards the Delai Xima and Vaeneris there."

"With just the support of Anjer, even if this Garen is of no use, he is still a formidable contender. A bit more time can still be stalled. Oh, right. Between Delai Xima and Vaeneris, who do you support?" The man asked in a low voice.

"Depends on the situation. Both are young leaders of the next generation, with authoritative support behind them." The woman said very nonchalantly, "Are you thinking of pulling me over to support Delai Xima again? He might be very outstanding, but he is not the type that I admire. I don’t have to say much more."

"So you have noticed." The man smiled bitterly. "Cheers."

"Cheers." The woman smiled, pretending to raise up her wine glass and clink it against the man’s.

Garen followed after his uncle, politely answering the questions from the elders all the way. Various appraising eyes continuously focused on him.

As he smiled and hurried forward to the thirty-plus year old man in front of his uncle, nodding in response, he swept his gaze quickly over uncle Anjer’s face.

He did not know just how much of uncle’s help he had received as he was growing up. Even his sister and himself were enrolled into the academy simply because of his connections here. Although his uncle’s sexist opinions were rather bad, but it was really nothing for him to complain about. Only, what was causing him confusion now was this sudden desire to pass on the business to him.

This was so unexpected.

Last time, he had fought for it to the utmost of his ability, but his uncle’s attitude had remained firm. However, even if Lombarth was not trying hard enough, he still would not be so willing to pass all the assets to Garen.

And uncle was only about forty years old this year…

Thinking about uncle’s age, there was an increase of profoundness in Garen’s eyes.

"Brother..."

Suddenly, a weak voice sounded from behind him.

Garen was slightly startled, and turned his head to see his sister Ying Er standing behind him.

"Why are you alone? Where is mum and dad?"

"They did not want to come, so they rejected the invitation." Ying Er was wearing a black dress with a drawstring waist; the skirt reached her knees, and there was a black hairband tying up her long, waist-length hair. Her lips were pink, and her eyes glistened with brightness. It was obvious that she had been dolled up by professionals.

"Rejected?" Garen was stunned. Although he had known since he was young that his parents and his uncle were not on good terms, he had not imagined it to be this bad.

Ying Er walked over to Garen’s side and stood next to him, greeting uncle Anjer.

Anjer smilingly nodded in response.

"It’s been a long time since you siblings have met. Have a good chat between yourselves." He patted Garen’s shoulder. "In a while, when I ask for you, come over immediately. Don’t dawdle."

"Okay."

Garen could vaguely feel the predicament that his uncle was facing now. He nodded resolutely.

"Brother, what is going on?!" The moment their uncle left, Ying Er immediately spoke and asked; her eye were filled with doubt and a bit of concern, as well as a sliver of confusion and unfamiliarity. "How could you came back and did not even check up at home for a bit? And how is uncle able to have such great influence?"

Garen led her to a corner and found two quiet seats. The two of them sat down.

"To be honest, I am also not clear about the situation here. Uncle suddenly wants me to take over his business. I am completely unprepared." Garen himself was in doubt, "However..." He had a vague guess, but did not speak it aloud. "Forget it. Let’s hope that I can get through tonight. Don’t you bother with these things. It’ll be alright as long as I’m here."

"But why didn’t mum and dad come over? I heard that you were here, brother, that’s why I hurried over. Otherwise they wouldn’t have let me." Ying Er could not understand. She suddenly felt as though her parents and the brother who was just right in front of her had all become strangers now.

"They did not come here. Is it because they were unwilling?" Garen was thoughtful. "In a while I’ll go back and take a look. I’ve also just returned, the dojo the master was heavily ill, so I had no time." What he said was the truth; originally, before he had settled everything completely, he had not been planning to go home. He did not expect to meet his sister here.

"Then come get me in a while, don’t slip off by yourself!" Ying Er felt totally uneasy at such a banquet, and unconsciously stuck closer to her big brother.

"I know." Garen laughed, and leaned on the sofa casually.

At the cocktail party, some wealthy dignitaries were complimenting each other; there was a struggle amidst their words, both openly and covertly. They had hidden agendas. It all looked to be the same old thing, but in reality, the danger was real. Being the slightest bit careless at the cocktail party could mean offending some narrow-minded people, and getting oneself into trouble. If caught just a bit unaware, one could leak out some vital information about oneself. So everyone was extremely reserved and polite; every sentence was carefully worded.

After sitting about for a while, Garen and his sister saw their uncle waving at him, not so far off.

He hurriedly got up and walked over.

"Mr. Pand Di, this is my nephew, Garen. How is he? Easy on the eyes, yes? Garen, where is your greeting?" Anjer smiled and patted Garen’s shoulder. The other person was a huge client of his corporation, not to be taken lightly. He was also a very huge threat.

"An honour to meet you, Mr. Pang Di." Garen smiled, stretching his hand out to him.

The grey-haired man named Pang Di gave Garen a cold look.

"Hello. However, although Anjer recommends you, my impression of you is not so good. Of course, if you can satisfy me in the future, I might change this opinion of mine. Who knows."

"Mr. Pang Di." Anjer interrupted from the side in a deared voice, "What do you mean by that?" His eyes flashed as he fixed them on the man. His nephew was being accused in front of him; naturally he could not just ignore it.

"No meaning whatsoever." Pang Di smiled, "Anjer, we have worked together for so many years. To be honest, I am quite disappointed in your decision this time."

Standing at the back, listening to these callous words that made him look bad, Garen, however, did not feel strange about it at all.

The few dignitaries who had come over just now were also like this, albeit they did not express it as forwardly as he had.

Only, he had never intended to take over his uncle’s industry. Uncle was still young, and wanting to retire at such an age…..

He suddenly stepped forward, and, with a smile, politely asked Pang Di: "Then what can I do to give you that satisfaction?"

Pang Di was slightly startled, as though he had not expected Garen to suddenly step up and speak. He turned his head and looked at Garen closely. Before breaking into a sneer.

"Do you know anything about business science? How much do you know about classic case studies in the market?"

"The information in the regard is, in the end, only information. I am very confident with my ability to learn. I’m sure you have also gone through my relevant data?" Garen said calmly.

Pang Di was still sneering.

"So what? You’re only a newbie who has stood out, you are not the rightful heir, and your network is far less impressive than the other two candidates. If it weren’t for the support of your uncle, what right do you have to stand here and speak to me? You’re only a common student who can’t even get through the door."

Garen raised his eyebrow.

"Who hasn’t stood up from the basics? There is some bias in your words, sir. I don’t know what your requirements are for heirs, but believe me, if you choose me, I am confident that I can do it."

"You are very confident? You think you can definitely surpass the other two candidates?" Pang Di laughed.

"If I can, would you support me, then?" Garen said coldly.

"There’s no ‘then’. I simply don’t like you. Although I don’t know how a mere nephew you like could obtain Anjer’s approval, but it has been the custom that the industries are passed down to the rightful first born. Don’t try to use such small tricks to snatch what is not yours. No matter what you do! I will never agree to you being the heir."

This was what they really thought.

Garen finally understood.

All these people believed that he had been flattering his uncle on purpose, with the intention of obtaining the family fortune using dirty tricks.

Although he had never wanted to be a part of his uncle’s business, this man’s words were really quite irritating. However, he had only spoken to him because he had wanted to understand his passionate stand and attitude.

Only, Pang Di’s refusal to listen to anything they had to say, had caused him to feel a bit indignant.

"Actually, I really want to say this too. I don’t really like you much either." Garen retorted sarcastically. "Isn’t it a bit too early for you to interfere with my uncle’s decision?"

"Anjer’s issue..." Pang Di’s face turned cold.

"Alright, Garen. That’s enough." His uncle’s face had become solemn.

Pang Di harumped coldly, and as he brushed past Garen, there was a sliver of fear on his face. It was obvious that he knew something about Garen, and walked off immediately seemingly in respect for Anjer.

Although, amongst the gentlemen on the scene, no one was afraid of anyone, and everyone was equal, but he did not need to see Anjer’s displeased expressions at all.

"Alright. Garen, don’t you get upset as well. Pang Di’s eldest son supports Vaeneris. Delai Xima and Vaeneris are two representatives of the younger generation from my wife’s side. In a while, you shall go down and meet with them privately."

Anjer knew his nephew considerably well. The recent case with the Manuyllton Company, although he was not clear about the process, but he knew the result very well. Garen had, with connections to the special forces that he had borrowed from who knew where, single-handedly gotten rid of the entire Manuyllton Company. This had caused him to see Garen in a new light. That was why he did not wish for Garen to have hatred towards Pang Di over this matter. After all, he was still a good friend who had partnered with him for many years.

"It’ll be fine, uncle." Garen smiled. "How about I go and meet my peers now?"

"That’s good too. Let me send someone to go with you." Anjer pondered for a moment, and felt that the attitudes of the guests on top were so-so. The advantage obtainable for Garen here was too small, so he might as well let him meet the other juniors downstairs.

Very soon, under his uncle’s arrangements, a slender man wearing a dark blue suit followed Garen from behind. An attendant brought the two of them out of the banquet hall, and through a sidedoor, entered into a smaller parlour.

The small parlour could only contain about a few dozens of people. The walls and the ceiling were all light yellow, and the floor was covered with white sheepskin rugs. The lamps on the walls emitted a warm, yellow glow.

Spread around the parlour, here and there, stood and sat over twenty young men and women.

A big group of them were clustered around two people, the rest were standing in the corners in twos and threes, completely unassuming.

The moment Garen walked in, he immediately saw the two exceptionally eye-catching central figures.

On the left was a young man with thick eyebrows, looking very experienced. There was a glass of dark liquor perched in his hand, from which he occasionally took sips. He was listening to what his companion had to say, but there was a bit of a distant look in his eyes. From the conversations around him, one could vaguely hear the others calling him Delai Xima.

The man on the right had short blue hair and dark eyes; there was a faint, thin and long scar on his forehead. He was the complete opposite of Delai Xima’s quietness; he had complete control on the conversation. Although he was smiling, he still gave off a threatening, aggressive vibe.

When Garen walked in through the door, he immediately caught the attention of some of the people there.

"Garen! You finally have the balls to come out!" The mature man next to Delai Xima suddenly stood up and straightened himself, speaking casually. "Xima, wasn’t this the guy you saw back then?"

Hearing this, Garen was surprised, and took a closer look at Delai Xima’s face. He suddenly remembered the young man in the white shirt that he had met at the doors of his uncle’s house. How long had it been that he had become so matured?

Pap!

The wine glass in Delai Xima’s hand had suddenly fell to the floor, and was smashed into pieces. The calm and the nonchalant look on his face had disappeared without a trace; in a moment, his face was drained of blood. Both his eyes were locked on Garen, vacant. It was obvious that his mind was now blank.

It was only after the people around him had shook him up, that he came back to his senses.

Chapter 116: Finish 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Yea… That’s him!" His voice was shaky, but calmed down after taking a deep breath. "Brother… It was him who almost killed me last time! It was very close!"

He stepped back and hid behind the mature-looking man.

The two looked identical, but his brother had an aquiline nose and looked cunning. Garen stepped forward with a smile on his face, and Delai Xima stepped back in fear.

"No! Don’t come any closer!" Although the young man looked more mature than before, he still remembered the horrifying experience Garen had given him that day. He tried to run but he was so nervous that he tripped over himself.

"Huh? Am I scaring you?" Garen smiled and grabbed a glass of black wine from the table at his side.

The room was silent, and most of the people were staring at Garen, but he did not seem to care.

"I’m Delai Ando. I think you have heard of me before." The mature-looking man did not even look at his brother who was hiding behind him. "I‘m here to make you pay for what you did to my brother last time."

Garen glanced around. His plan was to come here and finish whatever was left on his uncle’s side, and he really did not want to waste his time on these people. However, they had great power in their hands, even his uncle had to think twice when dealing with them.

In the end, it was a good opportunity for Garen to learn of their backgrounds.

"I’m not going to take over my uncle Anjer’s business. However," Garen said, seeing the surprised looks on those men’s faces, "I hope someone will at least explain to me what is going on here?"

"I saw you talking with my father not so long ago, didn’t he tell you about it?" Delai Ando stood in front of his brother. "Didn’t uncle Pang Di mention it to you? I don’t trust you. You’re doing everything you can to try and take everything from me, and you don’t even know about it?"

Delai Ando stopped for a second and sneered. "I don’t know what you are planning to do, but uncle Pang Di won’t allow it to happen. Also, I still need to make you pay for what you did to my brother."

"Alright, what are you going to do?" Garen stared at the man in front of him curiously.

"You will know after the party." Delai Ando sneered again.

"Why wait? Show me what you got!" Garen stood up and tried to grab Delai Ando.

Garen was extremely quick, and no one had expected him to start a fight right here and now.

He was aiming at Delai Ando’s neck and made it look very easy.

Bam!

Two men kicked Garen in the back, but they did no damage to him.

Another two men blocked Garen’s path, but they fell to the ground after he touched them with his palm, and Garen grabbed Delai Ando easily.

Clack!

A black pistol appeared in Delai Ando’s hand, and he pointed it at Garen’s forehead.

"You want to fight, huh? You are dead!" There was a grim look on Delai Ando’s face, and he turned off the gun’s safety.

The situation got intense. The young men in the meeting room had no idea what they should do at the moment, and no one talked. They did not want to make Delai Ando angry. If he pulled the trigger, the people in the large meeting room would definitely hear the noise, and no one would be able to take the responsibility if that happened.

"You are as foolish as your brother," Garen said in a light tone. He startled Delai Ando with the shockwave from his hand, and the man dropped his gun to the floor.

Delai Ando felt like he had just lost all his strength, and Garen could see how shocked he was from his eyes.

"How dare you!" Delai Ando yelled.

Crack!

Garen hit Delai Ando’s right arm with his palm, and broke the man’s bone. Everyone in the room shivered after hearing the sound of bones breaking.

"Ahhh!"

Delai Ando screamed in pain.

"Let him go!"

Suddenly, someone tried to stab Garen’s right arm with a black dagger.

It was Delai Ando’s body guard. Although it was a fight between the Young Masters, Garen had went too hard on Delai Ando. The bodyguard thought if he did not act now, Garen would do something even worse to his charge, and he would be in trouble after.

Bam!

The bodyguard’s wrist was hit by Garen, and he dropped the dagger to the ground right after. He backed off immediately, but he still lost his strength and fell to the ground.

On the other side of the room, the young man named Vaeneris started to clap. He was smiling, and it looked like he was praising Garen. He and several other teenagers were protected by more than ten bodyguards in black suits. They formed a circle around the teenagers.

Garen had no idea when they had entered the small meeting room.

Delai Ando’s face was pale, and Garen just dropped him to the ground.

"Who are you? Vaeneris?" He slowly walked towards the young man.

Vaeneris’s expression changed, but he quickly calmed down and backed off a bit. The bodyguards seemed nervous when Garen moved toward them and moved even closer to the teenagers.

"Garen, Mr. Anjer’s situation is bad, and he does not have much time left in this world. Our fights here will not affect the right of inheritance."

"He is dying?" Garen scrunched his eyebrows.

The clean meeting room was in a mess after the fight. Wine, broken glasses, chairs, tables, bodyguards and Delai Ando were all on the floor.

Delai Xima hid himself in a corner, his face pale as he looked at Garen in fear. Delai Ando had passed out due to pain, and several other teenagers were staying as far from Garen as they could, not wanting to get involved in this.

"I will inform father about what just happened here. He broke his relative’s bone! Let’s see how he can get the inheritance after the rumor spreads!" a young man with grey hair said in anger. He stood right beside Vaeneris, staring at Delai Ando’s broke arm with fear in his eyes.

"Westin! Are you alright?" The door of the meeting room was pushed open, and several people rushed in. One of them was Pang Di. He rushed toward the young man with grey hair and started to check on him.

Garen did not really care. He glanced around and saw that none of the bodyguards that followed the people into the room were strong. Most of them were just amateur gunmen.

Garen’s uncle walked through the door with a calm look on his face and went directly to Garen.

"What happened? Are you alright?"

"I’m good." It was acceptable as long as no one was killed in the fight. That was the bottom line for a fight between family members.

"Uncle, just tell me the truth. How’s your condition right now? I heard about your illness already," Garen asked in a light tone, narrowing his eyes.

Anjer looked at Garen with a bitter smile on his face.

"How did you know? I’m not sure actually. My doctor told me I have half a year left."

"You never told me before."

"I really had no idea about my condition." Anjer was searching through his memory. "About half a year ago, I was diagnosed with body hypofunction. I don’t even know why I suddenly became ill. Well, that’s not for you to worry about. Let’s go upstairs."

Garen nodded, and he started to check the clothes and accessories his uncle was wearing. He found a black jade ring on Anjer’s left first finger.

Garen was a bit confused, and he touched the surface of the ring after seeing it on Anjer’s finger. His expression changed as some soothing light Qi flowed into his body. Although it was weak, the flow was stable. However, it was too weak for Garen. It would take the ring years to increase Garen’s potential meter by ten percent, and that was not helpful at all.

The ring was an Antique of Tragedy, and its surface was coated with a sort of isolation paint. If Garen had not touched it, he would never have found out it was an Antique of Tragedy.

"Uncle, how long have you been wearing the ring?"

"This one?" Anjer wondered why Garen suddenly asked about the ring, but he still answered right away, "Two or three years maybe, why? I think I purchased it from a secret organization."

Garen immediately thought that it might be the Golden Hoop.

"It can’t be…" There was a strange look on his face. "But if it’s not in the special location it originated from, it wouldn't do any harm. I think I got this point right. This ring…" Garen started to think.

"Uncle, do you know if anyone did something to the ring after you obtained it? Or did the ring change after you started wearing it?"

"You think this ring makes me ill?" Anjer was not convinced. "Nothing happened to it I believe…"

Garen scrunched his eyebrows, ready to speak, but he was interrupted by Anjer before he could say something else.

"It can’t be the ring, but I will take it off if you think it’s the problem."

Anjer was happy that Garen was so thoughtful.

"Sure." Garen smiled. In the whole southern area, the Golden Hoop was in charge of selling the Antiques of Tragedy, so this ring must be from them as well. Although Garen was not sure if the ring was the reason why his uncle got sick, it was still better for Anjer to stop wearing it.

Right after Anjer took the ring off his finger, Garen could feel Anjer’s Qi start to increase, and it was much better than before.

"That’s the reason then…" Garen was surprised.

"Uncle, I actually like this ring a lot, would you mind giving it to me?" Garen asked.

"If I give you the ring, will you take over my business?" Anjer laughed.

"You are still young, uncle, I will take over when you really want to retire. To be honest, I think the doctor wrongly diagnosed your illness. Their equipment could be faulty, and they probably need a new set."

"I hope so…"

Garen looked at the ring his uncle handed over to him, and he knew Anjer felt much better after taking the ring off. He felt relieved after proving his assumption.

Garen left the meeting room with Anjer since he didn’t want to spend more time playing with the teenagers behind him. There was one thing he needed to do before leaving, though, and it was arranging another date to meet with that young girl.

Garen needed to help Su Lin first, and it was his priority at the moment. Also, he needed to tell his family about what he was doing. He would have to lie about its dangers since he wouldn't want them to worry too much about him.

Garen needed to find a new excuse.

He had no idea how he should explain everything to his family, and he almost got a headache only thinking about it. He was uncertain of how long he would be away from home this time, too.

Chapter 117: Eliza - Harmony City 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Coming out from the small living room, the banquet hall was still as lively as before; the band of violinists comfortably and elegantly played their violins, and in the merry music, a group of dignitaries continued on with their socializing indifferently.

As though they had not heard the scream of despair just now at all.

Garen and his uncle walking out from the small living room with a few bodyguards only attracted the attention of a few people. Other than that, there was no other response.

He swept his gaze over the entire hall, and unexpectedly saw his sister sitting on the side, somewhat frantically looking over in his direction; their eyes met coincidentally.

"It’ll be okay." Garen gave Ying Er a reassuring look.

The banquet went on as usual; as the host, his uncle went onstage to speak a few words. After that, a few other important people went onstage to speak. Everyone joked about them and a few courtesans. The atmosphere was ambiguous and reserved.

Garen walked over to his sister and sat on the black leather sofa, taking a light sip from the glass of dark liquor in his hand. It was sour, kind of like sour plum wine.

"Brother..." Ying Er looked at him with a worried face, she opened her mouth to speak but she was not sure what to say.

"It’ll be fine. There was just a bit of a conflict in there just now, nothing to do with me." Garen gave her a reassuring smile. "Come to think about it, it’s been so long since the two of us had sat down quietly and chat."

"Yes... It’s been a long time." Ying Er lowered her head. "I’ve already felt it very early on. Brother, you’ve become so mysterious. I don’t know what you do everyday. I can’t even see your shadow."

"What else would I be doing? I’m only following the dojo and joining exchange gatherings. There’s nothing else besides that. Don’t worry, if..." Garen had not finished speaking when his face suddenly became stiff; his eyes squinted slightly, before returning to normal. He changed what he was about to say, and continued. "If anything happens, I will definitely tell you. Oh right. Master has fallen sick recently. I still need to handle some stuff for the dojo. You know, after all, that I’m the master’s last disciple."

Ying Er nodded as though she understood.

********************

Click.

In the highest level of the building a short distance away from the banquet hall.

A masked man in black carried a black sniper rifle about two meters long, and was surveying the situation in the banquet hall opposite of him through the rifle scope.

His left hand adjusted the direction of the barrel, while his right hand reloaded the rifle lightly.

The bullets were golden yellow. They were very thin and sharp, like a straight, golden loach. Soft clicking sounds were made as these bullets slid into the bore of the rifle.

"Sting, there’s no need to be so nervous. He’s just a fellow who had been trained in the martial arts." Behind him was a man with short, silver hair, who spoke drily. He was playing around with a folding knife, wearing the same mask on his face; judging by the crystallic, deep-blue eyes and the handsome shape of his face, his disposition and looks were extraordinarily magnificent.

"Every dangerous person requires my alertness." The man carrying the rifle replied coolly. "Since we’ve taken the money, we are responsible for the client."

"Oh please, we are mercenaries, not professional bodyguards. Can you not be so dedicated? I’m afraid that Jia Loran will be looking for you to discuss the matter of you stealing their business." The silver haired man said, very amused.

"This can be considered a summit of the provincial leaders. Don’t underestimate this." The dark shirt man responded unemotionally. "This fellow could have been well trained to fight, and might not be weak."

"Are you talking about the martial artists? Do you think that there is a martial artist who can get rid of their opponents two miles away? I seem to remember, my last record was 2.3 miles…"

"2.6," The dark shirt man added on abruptly. "You are still far."

The silver haired man gave a dry laugh.

"I’m talking about Dan Ke Tang, you are the professional who single-handedly killed Dan Ke. How can you compare yourself to such a small fry as me? Isn’t that an insult to you? Within a mile, your special bullets can pass through an armoured vehicle."

The dark shirt man did not speak anymore, but watched a figure sitting by the right side window in the banquet hall through his circular rifle scope.

That man was holding a glass of dark liquor, drinking slowly while casually chatting with a young girl.

This man was Garen.

At that time, Garen could vaguely feel an extremely sharp aura locking fixedly upon himself.

He was sure that it was a firearm!

But never before had a firearm been able to cause him to feel so strongly threatened.

As he chatted away with his sister, the muscles in his entire body tensed up slightly. It could take a shot at him anytime.

Slowly, not more than a few moments later, this aura gradually moved away. He was then able to relax and breathe easily.

Just as he had let out a sigh of relief, suddenly, there was a small scuffle in the banquet hall.

"Don’t come over here!! Don’t come over! Don’t you hear me! I’m telling you to stand still!" A somewhat crazed voice of a man came from the middle of the banquet hall.

Garen and the guests from the surrounding corners all stood up, and looked to the center.

A young, golden haired man dressed in a white suit was holding a white handgun, holding it against the neck of a middle-aged lady.

What was mystifying, was that the middle-aged lady’s face was cold; there was not a hint of panic on her face, as though this was not the first time she was going through such a fuss.

The guests around them also did not look at all nervous. Some of them had even put their heads together in a whisper, a cold, uncaring look as they watched what was going on.

"Elena... Do you need our help?" A golden haired girl, wearing a red, sleeveless gown, stood out and asked casually. Her long ponytail was swept over her shoulder and fell from her neck all the way to the front of her chest. Her eyes were narrow and sharp, giving off a stinging, beautiful aura.

The woman who was being held hostage shook her head.

"Dante, I did not think that you’d do such a thing."

"You did not think? Ho… Ho ho… For that man, you can throw aside anything, you can give up everything... What would I not be able to do?!" The man in the white suit said in despair. He slowly tightened his grip on the trigger of the handgun.

Bang!

In a moment, there was a round, bloody hole the size of an egg on the back of the man’s hand, which was wielding the gun. The hand was not the place with the bloody hole; right on the man’s sternum was also an egg-sized hole of blood.

His hand and his chest had been pierced through at the same time. The hand that wanted to pull the trigger could not move anymore. The handgun slipped to the rug on the floor quietly.

"All hail... Black Flag Gang!!" He struggled to scream out his last words; a hissing sound, like a balloon’s air being let out, was emitted from his mouth. It was somewhat hoarse. Finally, he fell to the floor. Fresh blood flowed out of his chest in spurts, and dyed the white rug on the floor red.

Garen, who had been standing on the side, pulled his sister into his arms before she could see anything clearly, covering her eyes.

He looked to where the bullet had been shot from, and for a moment the pupils of his eyes constricted.

This bullet had pierced through the wall before passing through the man. The wall was a cement wall of approximately ten or so centimeters; to be able to pierce through a wall of such thickness, and then piercing through a man, before leaving a deep, black hole in the rug, the bottom of which could not be seen. This threat….. This decisiveness of the blindshot…

"This is the power of a true elite sharpshooter, partnered with a powerful rifle." His uncle, who had been nearby, walked over, and stood next to him, speaking in a low voice. "Garen, you can use martial arts to strengthen yourself, but if you really wish to kill your enemies, the strongest martial artist can never defeat a bullet of this caliber."

He patted Garen’s shoulder, and took a deep breath.

"Sting is an elite mercenary in my service, and also the secret personnel that watches over the safety of this event. There are over a hundred of elite sharpshooters like him in the entire federation. They can kill their intended target from a few miles away. An elite Grandmaster of Combat, they say, is not afraid of an ordinary bullet, but... This is not the age of martial artists anymore..."

Garen was silent.

He knew that it was impossible for him to overcome an elite sharpshooter of this sort, and this bullet of such penetrating power. This was already comparable to Adrela’s full strength attack with his sword, the Three Star Convergence. It might even be more powerful. With such a powerful bullet, without even talking about better bullet, if some poison were to be brushed onto the bullet, he would be killed on the spot.

"Come. Help me." Uncle Anjer had already known about Garen’s talent in martial arts, but firearms were not something that martial arts could defend against.

"I still have some matters to deal with. Let me think about it for a while, uncle." Garen said casually.

"Alright, but you had better be quick." Anjer felt like his nephew’s tone of voice had finally relaxed, and he nodded his head somewhat relieved. Casting an indifferent glance at the Ying Er in Garen’s arms, he turned around and left alone.

"Ying Er, something has come up. I’ll need your help later to persuade mum and dad."

"What thing? Just… Just now, what happened? How’s the man? Brother?" Ying Er asked doubtfully. She had already guessed it a bit, and her voice was slightly shaking.

Garen looked to the top floor of the opposite building, and his vision seemed to pass through the walls, seeing a black figure propping up a long rifle, crouching quietly there.

"Nothing. Be obedient, don’t open your eyes."

*****************

On the rooftop.

Sting slowly stowed away the heavy duty silencer, his dark eyes finally peering through the scope to take a look at Garen. He kept having this feeling that the young man seemed to have discover his position.

"What now?" The silver haired man asked, squatting on the side.

"Nothing. Let’s go, on to the next point. The Black Flag Gang would not have only sent this small fry." Sting stood up and said coolly.

"That’s true. I heard that lunatic has been hanging out with Duskdune Shura’s men. Who knows, there might be unexpected people turning up." The silver haired man somehow had something out of nowhere and popped it into his mouth, chewing away.

"Duskdune Shura... Those guys who fuse martial arts and firearms together?" Sting was slightly stunned for a moment, "I heard that elite Grandmasters of Combat can tank bullets. Their speed is incredible, and their ability to fight in close combat is extremely strong. Perhaps I will get the chance to see this for myself this time."

"No one can defeat you, you are our trump card!" The silver haired man patted his partner’s shoulder heartily. "The Black Flag Gang definitely could not have imagined that you would personally strike this time."

"Let’s go." Sting said indifferently, as he turned around and walked into the darkness.

*****************

After leaving the banquet, Garen made a trip home and told his parents in detail about the situation of the dojo. Unexpectedly, someone had already talked to his parents concerning his studies and the reasons behind the subsequent arrangements.

After some enquiries, it was actually the people from the Golden Hoop. They had told his parents that Garen would immediately go to the capital of Eliza Province, Harmony City, and enroll for classes, jumping a few grades ahead. Furthermore, it was an entry exempted from the entrance exam requirements into a private university— the Matra University. It seemed that it was because the antique appraisers’ requirements had been fulfilled, and he had achieved the recruitment standards of this university. That was why they had issued an invitation especially for him.

His parents at home had even received, earlier on, the special invitation by the antique appraisers at Matra University. They were so excited when they had heard the news, and kept on advising him not to keep on going to Uncle Anjer, and he must be independent. That sort of thing.

Garen and his sister’s original plan to persuade them ended completely without a hitch.

Next up was one small issue to be solved.

He needed to bid his Circular Dance Gate friends and the classmates and teachers who were close to him farewell, and go to the telegraph office and send a telegram to Miss Fanny Cindy, to inform her about him leaving to jump grades and enrolling into a university.

Finally, a few days later, he finally stepped onto the train heading towards the capital of Eliza Province.

*****************

In the reddish brown train carriage. The train attendants and the guests came to and for. It was a bit noisy.

Su Lin and Garen sat opposite of each other; the two men were quietly looking out at the scenery outside flitting past quickly.

On the seats to their right, three young men were playing cards. The seats in front were occupied by a pair of young couple with a baby, and were coaxing the baby to sleep. Behind them, there were a few young men and girls who looked like university students, reading thriller novels and horrifying experiences. Their voices were rather loud.

The faint, white morning light shone in through the window, but the inside of the carriage was still very dark and grey. The skies were overcast with grey clouds, and occasionally there was a faint sound of thunder.

Su Lin gave Garen a look. "So sorry to trouble you this time."

"Don’t talk about these things between us." Garen said coolly. "Tell me your situation."

"Me?" Su Lin pondered for a moment, "My parents still don’t know about me. In my eyes, I’m only a toff, the second young master who just knows how to eat, drink and have fun. My parents still have my big brother. Even though they really like me, and whatever I want, I get, but this is not what I want. If it’s not because martial arts has given me the opportunity to train my inner self, I might really still be a young master who only knows how to have fun now. Even though they have already prepared every safety measure perfectly for me, I still want to prepare a core layer of protection. You and another friend of mine. I have not revealed your identities to my family, I’ve only said that you’re my friend, so in case there’s any sudden development, you can still be covert and do what you’re supposed to." He sighed, "After all, my reputation outside is not really good. They don’t care about my squandering, even my family isn’t clear about my background, not to mention outsiders. So you guys are my final trump card!"

Chapter 118: Eliza, Harmony City 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Why aren't you telling your family the truth?"

Su Lin kept silent and didn't reply, a complicated expression on his face.

Seeing that he was reluctant to talk about it, Garen paused then said, "Let's change the topic. How did you get into this much trouble?"

Su Lin frowned.

"I don't know."

He scraped his index finger on the surface of the small table, which started creaking from the friction.

"If my friend in the mercenary industry hadn't passed me the information, I wouldn't have known what killed me. I'm guessing the opponent's motive should be to take a strike at my father and brother by killing me and my sister." At this thought, he started lamenting, "Duskdune Shura… How unsparing. That is a group which dares to proclaim themselves as one of the strongest assassin organizations. If I hadn't realized in advance and secretly tipped my family off, I'm afraid I would have really been killed this time. But this time, no one would have thought that a good-for-nothing playboy would have an additional extraordinary identity. Originally I didn't want to reveal it, but this time they've forced my hand."

"Duskdune Shura! How dare you threaten my beloved family members? I want anyone who dares come near them to be annihilated!"

At the mention of this name, his voice became very low, and a chill showed on his face.

"Garen, it's all up to you now," After witnessing Garen's terrifying strength, he was extremely confident in him.

"Don't worry. I'll do my best," Garen said in a deep voice.

The both of them stopped speaking and fell silent.

The train gradually stopped. Some people alighted while new passengers boarded.

Both of them sat in a cluster of six seats; four were still vacant. Soon, three youths boarded and sat with them.

Garen and Su Lin shifted slightly inwards to make space for them.

They were two boys and a girl. The only girl looked about 18 or 19 years old. She was very pretty, with a slim figure and long pale blue hair which was smooth and shiny like top-grade silk. Only her dressing seemed common.

Of the other two boys, one dressed extravagantly and was quite handsome, but he was slightly thin. He had a bourgeois air about him.

The other one was dressed ordinarily. He was well-built with dark skin, and there was constantly a gentle and polite smile on his face. He seemed to be from an average family.

The two boys sat next to Su Lin and Garen respectively, while the girl sat on the outermost seat.

In the presence of outsiders, Garen and Su Lin refrained from continuing their previous topic, and temporarily fell silent.

The both of them were traveling inconspicuously. They had their make-up artist conceal their extraordinary temperament as much as possible. Even Su Lin's overly handsome face had been covered in unhealthy colors, and he looked much paler. His clothes were swapped for the jeans and t-shirt of ordinary youngsters, nothing special.

When the three youths sat down, they glanced at Su Lin and Garen then didn't pay them any attention. After settling their luggage, they sat down and started to take out their prepared meals.

The well-built boy and the girl brought ordinary white bread and wheat crackers stored in plastic containers, paired with a small bottle of plain water that they had each brought. This was also the most common meal combination for most people on the train.

On the other hand, the thin boy took out cookies and milk, and small pieces of tiramisu cake.

"How pretty…" The girl saw the pieces of cake made into the shape of small animals and were instantly attracted by them.

"Eileen, Jeff, have a taste." The thin boy smiled, quite pleased with himself. He put the cake box on the small table, and deliberately placed the part of the cakebox labelled with the branding to face the most conspicuous angle.

"I'm alright," the well-built boy gave a stiff smile and continued munching his wheat crackers. He seemed uncomfortable with the gap in their family situation.

The girl noticed the stark contrast too, and smiled awkwardly, "No, thanks, Sharman. You eat it. I'm fine with just this."

"Don't stand on ceremony." Even though the thin boy had his faults and liked to show off, he was still quite sincere. He felt bad that he was eating well but his companions weren't, so he split the cake into three with tweezers, and stuffed one each into their lunch boxes.

"It's nothing fancy, let's eat it together. I have milk here too, I brought extra." He piled the milk cartons on the small table.

The other two felt embarrassed initially, but gradually let it go. The thin boy, Sharman, changed the topic and talked about interesting incidents on the last trip. The three of them chatted while eating; the atmosphere was warm.

Back on this side, Garen and Su Lin were slowly drinking some plain water and didn't eat anything. They quietly listened to the three of them chatting.

Maybe he felt embarrassed that only they were eating, the well-built boy, Jeff, touched Su Lin's arm.

"Buddy, did you forget to bring food? Have some." He distributed some wheat crackers and cake and put it in front of Garen and Su Lin.

"Uh, you don't have to, thanks. We're not hungry." Su Lin didn't expect him to be so generous.

"I feel self-conscious that we're eating over here and you're over there just watching us," Jeff smiled and said frankly. "Oh ya, are you two traveling together?"

"Yeah. The three of you are together too? Attending university in Harmony City?"

"Yup. We're students from the St Azure Art Academy. We're reporting for the start of term."

"St Azure, that place…I used to go there…"

Su Lin casually chatted a little with him, then stopped talking and just listened.

Garen didn't really understand the content of their conversation and couldn't get a word in, so he merely sat to one side and listened quietly.

He listened for a while and started to feel bored.

"I've heard that Harmony City is famous for its music events. It wasn't originally called Harmony City, but it was later changed to that," Garen recalled some Geography trivia he had learnt before.

"Indeed." Su Lin nodded, "There are three types of music events in Harmony City: large-scale ones, salon-style events and private concerts."

"I've been to the large-scale ones. It feels very comfortable," the girl Eileen continued. "You seem to have a strong physique, you must like to train? Your body should be very healthy, right?"

Her words were directed at Garen.

"I'm alright, I guess." Garen smiled. His physique was indeed quite buff compared to his peers.

"I'm so jealous. The weather has been really unpredictable this season; it's so easy to catch a cold if you don't take care. The last time I went to a concert I caught a cold which developed into a high fever, and it took me a long time and a lot of rest before I recovered," the girl said helplessly. "Have you been to a concert?"

"Uh…no." Garen shook his head. He couldn't tell the sound of a violin from the sound of an erhu, let alone been to any concerts.

"Lakeland"

"I went to a concert at the Lakeland Convention Center, it was a violin solo. I felt it was mediocre. Ever since Auter has been back from Weisman, his form has been getting poorer," the thin boy, Sharman, continued. "If you're interested, you can buy box tickets. They're only slightly more expensive than ordinary tickets, but there are staff who tend to a fireplace in the box, it's much warmer."

"Forget it. The money savings could be used for a lot of other things." The girl stuck her tongue out cheekily. "The tickets are expensive in the first place; I wouldn't be willing to buy box tickets."

Sharman smiled as he looked at Garen and Su Lin. "Compared to Auter, Cusey Freita's piano is much more pleasing to the ears."

"You like Cusey's piano too?" Said one of the three people who were playing cards to a side, a youth in a white shirt sat over in interest. The Confederate Legislative Council has passed a document to regulate the scale of musical events, and Cusey was one of the people who have been asked to rectify it. It's still uncertain how that will affect his form."

"Did they pass such a document?" The other people playing cards also came over to chat. A curly-brown-haired girl looked towards the white-shirt boy. "Where did you hear that, Hershey? From your dad?"

"It was the news that came out after an executive of the province, Mr Harris, came over some time ago and went fishing with the governor. Dad was at the governor's office handling the document. After a few days, your mother's department will receive the notice too. I've just known it a little earlier."

"Executive Harris?" Su Lin suddenly said. He looked stunned.

"Ordinary people probably haven't heard of him." The white-shirt youth took a look at him. "Working his way up from the municipal general department, it merely took him ten years to reach the sub-provincial level. He's the rising star among officials in Eliza now."

"That's not the point. It’s Mr Harris! He's the youngest sub-province official, tsk tsk. Has your dad met him before? How is he like?" the girl asked curiously.

"He's never met him in person. I've heard he's a very serious man." The white-shirt youth smiled and seemed pleased with himself. "About the thing I mentioned earlier, those are documents coming down from the central government, to the province and then the city. It can't be wrong."

The three people here were listening to the other three chatting, and couldn't get a word in edgewise. Their level was too high for them, and their topic wasn't a common one that youths their age would be exposed to, even relating to policy from the Governor's Office.

"k3"

Perhaps they were too absorbed in their conversation, and after gaining face in front of a pretty girl like Eileen, the white-shirt youth named Hershey got enthusiastic. "How about this? It's lunch time. Let me treat everyone to a meal in the restaurant! Don't say no. Whoever refuses is not giving me face! The taste and grade of the meals at the restaurant on K3 trains are fairly decent. I've eaten there many times."

He pointed a finger at the five of them on Eileen's side.

Su Lin politely refused.

The others found it hard to refuse such generosity, so Eileen and the other two followed Hershey towards the carriages in the front of the train. Among them, Sharman who originally had some sense of superiority had been suppressed to an intimidated state. He seemed shy to even speak loudly.

The six of them left temporarily.

Only Garen and Su Lin were left in their row of seats. The surrounding became quiet all of a sudden.

Garen looked at the odd expression on Su Lin's face.

"Is something wrong?"

"Nothing." Su Lin snapped out of it. "Seeing youths their age, I feel very old. I wish I could go back to the time when I was young…"

"You're not too old yourself…" Garen was speechless.

"43"

"Oh ya. I've arranged your accommodation for you. It's a newly acquired property at 43 Garden Street. Someone will deliver the keys when we alight. What type of car do you want?"

"I don't have a driving license."

"One order and it's settled."

"Then give me whatever's the most expensive," Garen threw all air of courtesy to the wind.

"S7"

"You don't stand on ceremony, do you!?" Su Lin jokingly punched Garen and said. "I've give you my current Rossland S7. With a market price of 12 million, you've got a steal there!"

"Oh yeah. Why did you have a strange expression on your face earlier? Did you still have the nerve to show off and compare yourself to these kids?" Garen asked.

"Do you know who that Executive Harris that they mentioned is?" Su Lin questioned.

"Who knows!" Garen rolled his eyes.

"He's my brother."

"…"

Chapter 119: Assassination 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Your brother is very well-known…" Garen shrugged. He didn't know what to make of it.

"He's always been like that," Su Lin murmured. "Excellent, serious, dignified. He can even have a face-to-face confrontation with father. When I was young, I would often hear them arguing in the study."

"You have a happy family." Garen took a sip of water.

"Indeed." Su Lin reverted to his normal self and smiled. "But now someone is trying to destroy this happiness."

"Kill anyone who tries." Garen smiled. He didn't speak after that.

Soon, designated waiters served them the prepared dishes and drinks. The dishes looked visually appealing and delicious. Chicken, duck, fish, geese, all kinds of meat were readily available. At the sides, there were attendants waiting with more dishes.

Garen got up and glanced around the entire carriage: it was empty except for a gray-haired old man at the other end receiving similar treatment. The old man saw him and raised a glass to toast him with a smile.

Garen smiled back at him and sat down. He looked at Su Lin across from him having a bite of meat mixed with a mouthful of wine and chewing it in his mouth; it felt weird to Garen.

"Seeing you eat, I don't know why but I always feel repulsed."

"I don't look like someone from a rich family, right?" Su Lin wasn't bothered, and kept chewing while he mumbled. "It's normal. I would never change myself just because of other people's opinion. That's my principle."

"It's a good principle to have." Garen nodded. When he saw that one of the dishes had changed, he started eating too.

Su Lin had a large appetite, but his wasn't small either.

Ever since he reached the limit of Secret Mammoth Technique, his appetite had increased dramatically. Seven to eight pounds of meat in a meal was a walk in the park. Converted to Earth units, that was five to six catties. This was excluding bread, soup, vegetables and other dishes.

The train chugged on, slowly and steadily. Every day, Garen and Su Lin chatted or listened to the youngsters around them. Every meal, they would avoid eating with others in case their immense appetite alarmed them.

After a week, they finally reached the heart of the Eliza Province, Harmony City.

Jumping off the train from the carriage doors, Garen suddenly saw Su Lin's body tense up and he was standing still in front.

"What's wrong?" The station was so loud and noisy that Garen had to raise his voice.

"It's here." Su Lin turned around. He was holding a black card about the size of a playing card between his index and middle fingers; a 'J' was printed in the middle of it.

"Duskdune Shura's black card."

"Weren't you already mentally prepared?" Garen smiled. He was far from being that ordinary person from Earth. Confronted with any challenge, he was confident he could face it himself. When he heard that Duskdune Shura's card had arrived, he had a sense of eager anticipation instead. He had come to terms with it: even though firearms were capable of threatening martial art practitioners, he had special abilities and was a unique specimen gifted with infinite possibilities—maybe he could break through that limitation in the near future.

"That's true. Let's go. But I'm guessing father and the others should already be aware about the appearance of the black card." Su Lin gave a wry smile.

Sure enough, right after he said that, a large group of people walked towards them from the station entrance—all soldiers in brown military uniforms. The leader of the group, a male officer, walked up to Su Lin and saluted him.

"Captain Su Lin, following the orders of the Commander, we are here to escort you back to the manor."

Garen looked as Su Lin silently shrugged and turned around to give him a wry smile.

"Come on," he said as he turned around and walked towards the convoy of military vehicles parked in the distance, surrounded by the soldiers.

Garen followed close behind, and was protectively surrounded by several soldiers too.

The travelers around them were astonished and confounded; each had their own theories about what was going on.

At the sight of Su Lin and Garen being escorted away by a large group of soldiers, Eileen, Sharman and the others who were still in the carriage were left speechless.

The faces of the three rich kids who were bragging about their family backgrounds and wealth started to redden in embarrassment. Compared to them, it was obvious that Su Lin and Garen were the truly eminent characters. To think that they were boasting about their family connections and whatnot in front of them…

*******************

At the edge of a lake near Harmony City.

Amidst the dense green trees by the lake, there was a square black-roofed estate.

Double-storeyed steeple buildings formed an incomplete square; the gap in the square was the driveway which led to the estate.

The entire estate was surrounded by a metal fence, with a white gate in a gap to facilitate entry and exit.

Weak rays of sunlight fell on the roofs of all the buildings within the estate, and off the glass, faintly reflecting the light outwards.

At noon, a motorcade of dark green military vehicles drove along the driveway into the vast estate.

The motorcade comprised of four cars. They slowed to a stop at the edge of the lawn in the middle of the estate.

Car doors opened then banged shut as a large group of soldiers dismounted and dispersed. Only two officers were left escorting two youths to the white marquee in the middle of the lawn.

Of the two youths who stepped out of the car, one had flaming red hair and a handsome face with clear skin. He had a small golden earring on his ear.

The other had indigo hair and was well-built. He took in his surroundings after stepping out of the car, as if it was his first time there: it was Garen who had just arrived from the train station.

"Garen, let's go meet my father together first," the youth with flaming red hair said to him.

Garen nodded, and walked towards the marquee together with Su Lin.

On the lawn outside the marquee, a tall and sturdy man raised a brown golf club and mimicked hitting a ball from time to time; he seemed to be practicing.

The man was wearing white casual clothing. His hair was completely white and his forehead was balding. He had a healthy complexion and his eyes were calm but determined, conveying a resolute temperament.

The man was somewhat portly. After he completed a swinging action, he leaned on his club and stood there looking towards Su Lin and Garen.

"Father, I'm back. This is my friend Garen. I've invited him over to stay with us for a while. He's a very close friend of mine," Su Lin stepped forward and took the initiative to speak first.

"This is my father Crohn. You can call him uncle."

"Hello uncle. I've taken the liberty to visit you. I apologize for disturbing," Garen greeted politely.

"It's fine. I see that you're different from those other guys. I hope that Su Lin has more proper friends like you and gets into less trouble outside." Crohn nodded and gave Garen a friendly smile.

"Oh yeah. Don't go out and about for no good reason. Did you receive a black card with a 'J' printed in the middle?" he turned to ask Su Lin.

"Card? You mean this?" Su Lin took out the card and handed it to his father.

Crohn took the card. A trace of severity flashed across his eyes.

"Sure enough. Alright, you show Garen around, as long as you keep to the area around Lake Saima as much as possible."

"I know, don't worry. The area around Lake Saima would be fun enough for us." Su Lin smiled and waved. "Come on Garen, I'll bring you to your temporary residence."

They bid Commander Crohn goodbye and strolled around the estate for a while. Su Lin passed Garen the keys to the house he had prepared for him as well as the car keys, then instructed him on matters related to car maintenance. Only after that did things settle down temporarily.

"Putting these aside, you'll stay at my home for this period of time. It's not officially the start of term yet. You can move out once school is back in session. Any problems?" Su Lin started arranging matters.

"None. But I need to take a look at the layout and location of the house, and maybe get some daily necessities."

"Don't worry. It's right by the university, and well-stocked with all the daily necessities. After this, I'm going to introduce you to another friend of mine, who will also be our companion in this upcoming period," Su Lin said mysteriously.

"Companion?"

Garen was very interested in this other person who was comparable to himself. It was conceivable that a person capable, in Su Lin's eyes, of joining the ranks to counter Duskdune Shura, would absolutely not be an ordinary person.

Holding on to his expectation, Garen followed Su Lin to check out the house. There weren't any problems with it. It was a beautiful white villa, and the expensive Rossland was parked in the garage.

Then it was paying a visit to this new friend who was going to join their ranks.

*****************

Harmony City slums.

Clusters of dark gray buildings were packed together densely; some were even leaning and threatening to collapse.

Garen and Su Lin passed through an alley between two leaning buildings. On the ground floor of the buildings were dirty shops and ordinary housing for the poor. Clotheslines with laundered clothing hung above the alley; some of the clothes were still wet and dripping with water, emitting a strong smell of soap.

The walls on both sides of the alley were plastered with all kinds of small advertisements: mostly housing rental, high-interest loan, and hiring notices. Some parts even had advertisements directly written in green and red paint; it looked like children's graffiti.

In the depths of the alley, the sun couldn't reach them—they were shrouded under the shadow of the buildings. The ground was damp; it was in a constant state of humidity all year round.

Garen and Su Lin walked along the alley and were aware of the curious gazes of local residents they got from time to time. Some harsh coughing noises could vaguely be heard coming from the residences.

Su Lin carefully stepped over a dirty puddle. "I haven't been here in a long time. The city has been carrying out preventative measures against an epidemic. They say it's a new strain of influenza, more problematic. People with poor personal hygiene are the most vulnerable group to be infected. I hope that guy isn't infected."

"I guess not," Garen casually replied. He saw a bedraggled young boy sitting at the entrance of a shop to his left. The boy was weaving something using pale yellow grass. "Why doesn't he live in a better environment?" Garen asked logically.

"No particular reason. It's just how he is. This is where he grew up," Su Lin whispered. He turned a corner in front and walked towards the right. "We're here."

Garen followed him and turned the corner into a forked alley. There was only a small shop selling hoes and iron farming tools at the end of it. The shop was somewhat dark. Two silhouettes could vaguely be seen busying inside.

Garen followed Su Lin to the entrance of the shop.

"Is anyone in?" Su Lin shouted.

"How can I help you, sir?" A young man in mud-colored linen clothes walked out. He was holding his sleeves with his hands, revealing the burn scars on his arms.

"Where is your boss?"

"May I know who's asking?" An elegant young lady walked out of the shop. She wore a drab gray skirt, but her high breasts and vivacious figure revealed her youthful charms.

"Why are you looking for my father?"

Chapter 120: Assassination 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I am a friend of your father's. Ask him to come out and see me, he'll know," Su Lin said with a smile.

Garen stood to a side an observed their exchange silently. Suddenly he heard faint footsteps. When he turned around, he saw the boy who was weaving earlier cautiously stick his head out from the end of the alley in curiosity and look over. His small dirty face had a wooden sense to it. Two streaks of transparent sticky mucus flowed from his nostrils; he sniffed hard and the mucus was retracted back into his nose.

He took a look at him then ignored him and turned back around. Su Lin had already asked the girl.

The two of them were led into the shop and offered two chairs—the cleaner ones of the lot—to sit down on.

Soon, a middle-aged man with a full-faced beard pulled aside the tattered cloth partition separating the inner part of the house and walked in. He looked like an honest fellow. His face was calm and indifferent, his gaze complex with the vicissitudes of life; obviously he had been through a lot.

When he walked out, the impression he gave was no different than that of a common blacksmith.

Honest, straightforward, strong, crude, and of course, he had oil stains all over him.

The first thing that the man saw when he walked in was Su Lin sitting on the chair. He furrowed his brow slightly. He wiped the oil stains off his hands on his clothes, walked over and sat down in front of Su Lin and Garen.

"It's you? Once I saw you, I knew my peaceful life was over. Tell me, what do you need my help for?" His sized Garen up and seemed to have doubts.

"Come on. I had a hard time getting that promise from you before. If you went back on your word, I'll be suffering a big loss. To think for your sake, I had to…"

"Alright, just come out with it. What do you want?"

Su Lin was cut short by the man, and didn't manage to finish his sentence.

The young boy and girl stood to one side and were left confused by the conversation; they had no idea what was going on.

Su Lin looked at them, and knew that the man had no intention of hiding anything from them, so he spoke his mind.

"I've run into some trouble."

"What kind of trouble?" The man leaned forward, and took his outer coat off.

"Duskdune Shura."

The man abruptly stopped what he was doing.

Silence filled the air.

The man didn't speak, Su Lin didn't speak, and neither did Garen.

Affected by the atmosphere, the boy and girl standing to a side didn't dare to breathe too heavily either. They looked puzzled; the girl even seemed vaguely excited.

After a while, Su Lin spoke again.

"What's the matter? The Eight-Arm Dragon King of yore is now speechless at the mention of Duskdune Shura?"

The man's eyes flashed.

"What's the use of reminiscing about the past?"

The Eight-Arm Dragon King!

Garen sitting to a side was instantly stunned. He had never heard of this title, but to be able to carry such a name was proof enough of his terrifying true strength in the past.

Regardless of the field, for one to be called a king, they were definitely no plain characters. Not to mention he was acknowledged by Su Lin as an absolute companion in countering the impending attack from Duskdune Shura!

When he saw the man evade, Su Lin didn't let up. "You're really able to let go of that thing with Duskdune Shura before? I don't believe it."

The atmosphere turned somber again.

The youths were mostly confused, but caught the gist of it. The old man in the shop must have been a powerful big shot in the past. He merely resided here because of some kind of grudge. These two people in front of them had obviously come to ask the old man to come out of retirement.

"I thought I could live peacefully till I died of old age. I didn't think there would be such a day…" The middle-aged man let out a long sigh. "Unfortunately, I have let it go entirely."

At these words, Garen saw Su Lin's face turned unpleasant.

"You're joking?" his voice became very deep. "What about the promise you gave me before? Also, could you bear to see your daughter and apprentice toil on in mediocrity, forever living in this dingy corner till they die?"

The Eight-Arm Dragon King was unfazed. "I will not go out. But owing to my previous promise, I will give you a satisfactory explanation."

"Explanation? What further explanation can you offer?" Su Lin said coldly. Suddenly, he took out a piece of something from his front pocket: it was part of an unknown ornament, like a brass hoop. It was cracked at the bottom.

At the sight of this, the Eight-Arm Dragon King's eyes immediately widened. "Why is this with you?" his voice became unusually frigid. In contrast to his calm and passive demeanor a moment ago, he became frantic and dangerous in an instant.

"Don't you bother why it's with me," Su Lin sneered. "I…"

Snap! The words had barely left his mouth.

The Eight-Arm Dragon King erupted instantly. He drew two machetes out with both hands and hacked at Su Lin's arms with a swoosh.

Chhhh!

The blades froze to a halt inches above his skin.

The Eight-Arm Dragon King lowered his head and saw a large hand clutching his throat.

Bang!

He instantly flew backwards into a pile of debris, and broke numerous items as he went.

Garen gave a cold scoff and retracted his arm.

"Ridiculous."

Su Lin only managed to react then, and started to break out in cold sweat. Although he could hold his own, compared to a Grandmaster of Combat, he was definitely not as good in close quarters. Even Garen, who wasn't fast, had quicker reactions than he.

"This is your so-called expert?" Garen frowned at Su Lin. "Weak."

Su Lin gave a wry smile, and was about to speak.

Suddenly a click could be heard.

Garen's pupils narrowed; a sharp sense of danger overwhelmed him. He turned around immediately to look at the direction he sent the Dragon King flying.

In the dark, four sleek black rifles were steadily aimed at Garen's head and all around his body.

The Eight-Arm Dragon King stood by the wall with an icy gaze. He had two sniper rifles in his hands and two at his feet.

Four heavy duty rifles were aimed at Garen and the directions in which he could dodge.

These four guns gave him a strong sense of danger; they were obviously not to be trifled with.

The atmosphere in the room froze for a while.

"You could try firing at me," Garen said slowly. "Within ten steps, let's see if you kill me first, or if I break your skull open."

The Eight-Arm Dragon King retained his icy cold gaze.

He could tell that Garen was serious. An unprecedented sense of threat continuously stimulated his nerves, like needle tips constantly piercing on his skin. The subtle pain surged throughout his body like a tide.

"The distance…is too close…"

They were clear that, twenty meters away, the Eight-Arm Dragon King was stronger. Within twenty meters, Garen was fearless. Both represented strong threats to one another.

The atmosphere became more distressing and grim by the minute. The youths stood far away in a corner; they looked helpless. It wasn't just them. Even Su Lin didn't expect the situation to change so abruptly.

He was the only one who was clear about their strengths.

Both of them were at the peak in their respective fields, whether it was the Eight-Arm Dragon King or Garen. To really determine a winner, harm would definitely be done to both.

"Alright, alright. For my sake, let's each give in a little. Yoda, I will tell you how I obtained the item. It has to do with Duskdune Shura."

Yoda, the Dragon King, gave an apathetic scoff, then slowly moved the guns away.

"Nobody has dared to threaten me like this before." He looked at Garen, a hint of coldness flashed in his eyes. "You are unwelcome here."

Su Lin looked at Garen, his eyes pleading.

"I'll wait for you in the car."

Garen nodded passively, turned around, and walked out of the shop.

At this, Su Lin let out a long sigh of relief.

He should have foreseen that two people with such aggressive characters put together would definitely cause problems.

Both of them had absolute confidence and pride in their respective fields, and couldn't stand to be provoked. They were like barrels of gunpowder, catching fire with a spark. Fortunately he had a good relationship with Garen, and the latter gave him some face.

He understood that the Eight-Arm Dragon King merely wanted to frighten him so that he would give up the item. He didn't expect Garen to believe the threat and act on it. And from then on, both of them wouldn't see eye to eye.

"Looks like I'll have to split them up to handle things. Otherwise, we'll have an internal fight before Duskdune Shura's forces even arrive." Su Lin felt helpless. "This can't be helped. The more powerful one is, the more confident they would be, to the extent that everything revolves around them. This was the absolute confidence established from long-term success and victory. Therefore, any such person would have absolute certainty about themselves."

The Eight-Arm Dragon King was such, and Garen was no different. Greater achievement determined stronger confidence.

"What's the deal with that guy?" the Eight-Arm Dragon King asked after Garen left.

"Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, Divine Marshal Garen. He's someone I hired as a temporary aid, and also a good friend of mine. Originally, I thought you could get along peacefully and complement each other… Looks like it was wishful thinking on my part," Su Lin helplessly sighed.

"Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate? The one from fifty years ago?" The Eight-Arm Dragon King was stunned. "Divine Marshal, hmph… What an obnoxious title! Obviously it's corresponding to the four Royal Generals of the past!"

"It was probably re-established by the older generation. You should know, whoever is named a Divine Marshal would definitely be a pre-eminent expert. And all in the name of White Bird Holy Fist. I trust you remember the Holy Fist White Bird from before?" Su Lin explained.

"Naturally…" The Eight-Arm Dragon King nodded. "That was the pinnacle of an era. But to be able to make me feel such a strong sense of threat, Divine Marshal…He deserves that title"

"Speaking of which, do you want to join Golden Hoop? You can consider it as paving a future for your apprentice and daughter." Su Lin didn't show any trace of the hostility from earlier, but instead seemed like someone who hadn't seen their best friend in years.

He knew clearly that, in terms of defeating an opponent in a direct confrontation, Garen was absolutely much stronger. But in terms of secret assassination methods and eliminating bodyguards, the Eight-Arm Dragon King was far and away more superior to Garen.

Each had their strengths.

If they could complement each other in action, they would become a force to be reckoned with!

But unfortunately both clearly didn't see eye to eye.

During his youth, the Eight-Arm Dragon King encountered Duskdune Shura, who had the combined skills of martial arts and firearms. In contrast to average assassins, he was clear about how terrifying the combined force of martial arts and firearms could be, so he would pay attention to happenings in the martial arts world.

"Forget it. You wait here for a moment. I'll give my apprentice and daughter a brief explanation." Yoda finally made up his mind, especially after being provoked by Su Lin and Garen like this. Garen had become a Divine Marshal of Holy Fist Gate at such a young age; this truly highlighted how old he himself was.

At this thought, he motioned his apprentice and daughter—who were timidly standing a distance away and looking at him like a stranger—to come to him.

"Piccolo, Nissyan, come over, I have something to say to you."

*******************

Garen walked out of the shop, and saw the boy with a runny nose stand in a corner and looking at him blankly again.

He put both his hands in his pockets. His face was grim; the strong Momentum on him was enough to make any adult frightened. But the little boy—albeit trembling from head to toe—could still persist in holding his gaze.

Crisp footsteps could be heard from leather boots hitting the ground.

Garen walked to the boy, and looked down at him.

"Kid, why are you staring at me?"

"I…I want to learn from you…how to fight," the boy looked up and said, as he inhaled the mucus back into his nose.

Chapter 121: Assassination 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was slightly stunned, and suddenly felt a strange sense of uneasiness. The sentence reminded him of the life he used to live on Earth.

The gloomy Momentum around him gradually dispersed too because he was distracted.

He straightened himself up and looked down at the boy in front of him.

"Why not find someone else? Why did you specifically find me?"

The boy finally started to relax after the Momentum dispersed, and he stopped trembling. He looked up at Garen.

"Because I feel you're…the most powerful!"

Garen's mood inexplicably lifted.

"You have a good willpower," he deliberated, "if you can pass my test, I'll consider accepting you."

He raised his right arm and swung it backwards.

Chrrrh!

The sound of cloth being torn could be heard.

"Do this action a thousand times every day, use all your might. Seven days later, if you think you've achieved it, come to this address." He whispered the address of Su Lin's manor.

The boy saw it only once; the action was fairly simple. It was mainly about perseverance.

In actuality, Garen just set a random test. He took a last look at the dazed boy.

He was mumbling the address repeatedly while starting to practice the action he had just learnt.

Soon, Su Lin walked out of the shop. He looked at Garen confusedly, and then looked at the dazed boy.

"Come on, let's head back."

Garen didn't bother to explain either; he just followed him and walked out of the alley.

That action was a simple use of the Swinging Form. If the boy could really stick to it, one week later his right arm would swell and itch due to a congestion of blood, and the joints in his arm would be damaged.

This would depend on whether he was obedient enough to practice this action with all his might.

Because this action wasn't beneficial to him in any way and was merely part of the test, when the time comes, if the injury to his arm wasn't serious, it would prove that he didn't do as instructed.

Of course, if it was indeed as Garen expected, he would treat his arm and temporarily receive him as a disciple.

Without further delays, Garen and Su Lin took the car directly back to the estate.

**************

The subtle sound of tea being poured into a white jade cup could be heard.

Magenta flower petals would pour out with the tea from time to time, emitting the fragrance of clivias. Underscored by pure flawless white jade, the magenta seemed unusually pure.

"Please, have some tea."

A purple-haired girl put the teapot down and gestured at the piping hot tea.

"Thank you."

Garen and Su Lin were sitting side by side on a bench. The purple-haired girl sitting across from them was Su Lin's sister, Aris.

The girl inherited the good genes of Su Lin's family. She was pretty, and had a serene and vintage aura about her.

Her long purple hair was combed into bangs towards the right, and tied into a ponytail at the back. It was neatly done up, without a single frizz in sight. She wore a black dress with purple motifs on it. Her figure was slender and proportionate; sitting in the chair with her legs together and angled sideways, she was a typical aristocratic young lady.

When she raised her teacup to drink, her actions were delicate: she merely took a sip as the teacup touched her lips.

"I'm truly surprised that my brother has such a proper friend like you, Mr Garen," Aris said with a smile.

"Uhh…" Garen didn't know how to reply. It was obvious that in his sister's impression, Su Lin was extremely shallow.

Su Lin sitting by the side could only smile awkwardly.

"You don't have to mind." Aris smiled. "Alright Su Lin, I'm assuming this visit isn't just to introduce me to Mr Garen?"

"Of course not…" Su Lin chuckled. "It's mainly to see how you've been. After not seeing you for such a long time, even I would miss my beautiful sister."

"Don't go out and about for no good reason," Aris said in a hushed tone. "Settle yourself at home for the time being."

"Actually…" Su Lin paused, "haven't you always wanted to learn authentic combat martial arts? Garen is the martial arts coach I've hired for you."

"Martial arts coach?" Aris was slightly surprised. "You've hired a… At this time…?" She seemed to have figured something out, but stopped short of saying anything, and started to scrutinize Garen.

But when Garen wasn't applying the Body Hardening Technique, his body merely seemed well-built, and wouldn't exhibit any distinctiveness. He had long curbed his Momentum; this would help conceal it from Duskdune Shura in their encounter.

Aris was an ordinary person who had never trained in martial arts before, so she couldn't tell.

She frowned, but didn't reject.

"Mr Garen, where do you work?"

"Oh it's nowhere special. I'm just a trainer at a dojo in a small town," Garen replied casually.

Su Lin sitting to a side cut in by replying, "Garen is a good friend of mine, someone I really trust. I would worry if anyone other than him were to be your coach!"

Aris wanted to decline, but Su Lin's burst of interruption and debate made it seem as though she would be disowning him as a brother if she didn't accept Garen as her coach; the consequences were severe.

All she could do was agree to let Garen teach her martial arts.

Garen observed from the side. He felt that the relationship between this pair of siblings was reversed. Aris was playing the role of an elder sister instead: she was mature, courteous and graceful. She handled things decisively without drawing it out.

Su Lin disappeared after he left Garen with his sister, probably out fooling off.

Garen and Aris were left sitting face-to-face in the tearoom. A maid refilled their tea for them.

"So… Master Garen, I'm over 18 this year. To start training in marital arts at such an age, would there be any problems?" Aris began asking the most basic questions.

She truly took Garen as her martial arts coach. In their casual conversation, the martial arts knowledge that Garen presented was passable.

"In doing fundamental training, age doesn't matter," Garen replied. "Even though you're starting out late, but you're still young; you still have the potential to develop. Don't worry too much."

"I've always wanted to learn authentic martial arts. Where should I start? To tell you the truth, we have quite a number of dojos locally, but I've been hesitant all along," Aris sighed. "Martial arts can improve physical fitness and exercise the body and mind. My body has always been weak. Please see if you can devise a suitable training plan for me."

"No problem," Garen nodded. "Since I'm your martial arts teacher, this is part of my duty."

"I'll trouble you to do it then. How about a salary of 5000 dollars per week?"

"That's very high."

Garen understood that to mean he was not welcome, so he stood up, bid her goodbye and left the room under the directions of the maid.

Aris lifted her teacup and blew at the rising vapor. She glanced at the motifs etched on the side of the table.

"Colonel Moen, is there news on Duskdune Shura? What made you come over personally?"

In a dark corner of the room, a military officer in black appeared from behind a bookshelf. The faint sound of a trapdoor automatically closing came from behind him.

"Duskdune Shura has made a move. The latest information from the intelligence bureau is that he's sent 20 men, split into two groups, directly headed to the estate. It's unknown what method he's employing. Our men failed to trace their whereabouts." A silver scythe hung from the military officer's waist: it was long, with the breadth of a longsword, and there was no sheath. This lent a cold and piercing air to him.

"How soon are they expected to arrive?" Aris rubbed her temples to ease her headache.

"Within this week," Officer Moen replied in a hushed tone.

"So father has sent you to protect me for the week?"

"Yes." Moen nodded.

"And about father and brother…"

"You needn't worry. There is a separate arrangement for Commander."

Aris nodded.

"As one of the three strongest special agents in the Southern Military, even you have come over. I'm assuming there are sufficiently strong guards protecting my father and brothers?"

"Yes. Colonel Turnery and Colonel Von Eckardt have arrived. Also, the Commissioner, Major General Wellington, is having tea with the Commander," Officer Moen calmly replied.

"Even the Commissioner of the Special Agent Bureau is involved? That's right, father is the Deputy Commissioner. If something were to happen to him, it would be a huge embarrassment."

"What a grand setting… Of the individual military elites within the entire Southern Military, more than half have gathered here." Aris started to relax a little. "It seems that everything is ready. Alright, I'm fine here, you can busy yourself elsewhere."

"Please take care." Moen bent over slightly and gave an elegant bow, then turned around and left silently through the secret passageway.

"Luna."

"Miss?" the only maid in charge of serving tea replied.

"The one I'm worried about most at the estate is my brother, Su Lin. You stay with him for this period. If he wants to go out, stop him and don't let him out."

"Yes, Miss," the maid nodded in agreement.

"I can't believe he still remembers that I like martial arts, and actually hired me a trainer. I merely mentioned it casually back then, but he actually took it to heart." Aris smiled, and her gaze softened.

"Oh yeah. What do you think of that Mr Garen?"

The maid deliberated and said, "He has solid foundational skills, but we are trained in military combat arts, so I am unclear about traditional schools of martial arts. I can only tell that he's not a fraudster. From his temperament and age, he seems to be a core disciple who has inherited proper training. But Miss, why don't you train in military combat arts with us? These are the practical combat skills actually adapted to fight and kill."

"Traditional martial arts has its advantages. My purpose for training in martial arts is not to fight and kill, it's to condition my body. Even though the practicality of traditional martial arts isn't strong, it's very good for training the body. That is something military combat skills lack. Forget it. You may go down now. Also, have Annie and the others focus on protecting Mr Garen. I'm guessing he's trained in typical traditional martial arts and would perform poorly in actual combat. Make sure you protect him well, it would be bad if something happened to brother's guest."

"Yes, Miss."

*********

One standing and the other sitting, Su Lin and Garen were skipping pebbles by the lake.

"What is the current situation? When we were heading back, I noticed that security has been increased," Garen inquired in a hushed tone.

Su Lin flung a pebble out: it skipped nine times on the surface of the lake. He smiled in satisfaction.

"All my dad's old partners are here. The four most powerful people in the Southern Military; Commissioner of the Special Agent Bureau, Wellington; and the strongest three selected from hundreds of thousands in the military, three special Colonels. It seems that, in order to deal with this trouble, dad has made countless promises."

"The four most powerful people in the Southern Military? How powerful?" Garen was somewhat sensitive towards such claims.

Chapter 122: Assassination 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I don’t know actually. There’s no one to compare them to. They are strong for sure, and we probably don’t need to do anything this time." Su Lin laughed breezily, "I heard about the Spy Agency when I was very young. The Spy Agency is a special department in the federal government, and its members are all very strong. They’re in charge of solving the special cases all around the country."

"Sounds good." Garen nodded, "It’s great if the only thing we need to do is watch, also, when will the disgusting old gunman get here?"

"Disgusting old man? You mean Yoda, the Dragon King?" Su Lin was speechless, "He said he’d rather take actions alone. He will be here when he thinks it’s necessary."

"I hope he’s not just too scared," Garen scorned.

"…" Su Lin had a bitter smile on his face, "Well, I will assign everyone’s tasks, you go take care of my sister, and I will stay with Yoda. What do you think?"

"Sure, I am a ‘Martial Arts Coach’ anyways."

"That was not just a name… I actually wanted you to teach Aris some things." Su Lin shrugged.

"She’s too old for that." Garen shook his head, although he was only 17 years old, the Secret Martial Arts made him look like he was more than 20 years old, and he had a mature-looking face.

"Just do whatever you can." Su Lin knew age was the problem, "I’ll go check on Yoda. Tomorrow is the deadline marked on the black card, Duskdune Shura had their rules, and they will take actions anytime between the second to the seventh day you receive their black cards."

"Got it."

Garen skipped a stone, and it bounced off the surface for more than ten times. He stood up after watching Su Lin leave the lake and walked into the manor.

"I haven’t improved since the meeting…" He felt a bit disappointed.

Garen’s progression slowed down after he became a Grandmaster of Combat. Without obtaining new Antiques of Tragedy, he could not increase his attributes and level up his skills.

At the moment, Garen could only practice the low-level Secret Martial Arts he acquired a while ago.

Th Firestream Fist and the Dark Iron Palm, he could probably increase the levels of those two Secret Martial Arts. However, the accumulation of venom for the Dark Iron Palm was way too slow. Garen raised his hands and looked at his palms.

Unlike the other parts of his body, his hands looked a bit dark.

Garen looked at his skill bar, "Dark Iron Palm: Entry level not reached."

He had no idea how much venom he needed in order to reach the entry level, based on the normal training duration of low-level Secret Martial Arts, Garen knew it was going to be hard.

The Firestream Fist was also about the hands, and its progression was slower than Dark Iron Palm. Garen had not yet reached the entry level of Firestream Fist as well, and he really could not tell the difference between now and when he just started.

He was a bit nervous, but he calmed down quickly. Garen needed to stay calm to reach his full potential.

"I can’t increase my attributes, and the low-level Secret Martial Arts are not progressing well… Should I go to other sects to collect some Secret Martial Arts that are easier to learn?" Garen scrunched his eyebrows.

After the battle with Andrela, Garen knew he had already reached his limit, and he needed some special methods to help him reach the next level. His plan was to collect low-level Secret Martial Arts from different sets, but he knew Su Lin’s matter was urgent, and he needed to help Su Lin first.

Garen thought he could at least level up the Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm but, although he spent a long time on them, nothing happened. He started to think the problems were on the Secret Martial Arts themselves because he had already done everything he could.

"Maybe I need special talents to level up those Secret Martial Arts?"

He closed his eyes and stared at the skill bar. There were no special signs behind Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm.

"If that’s not the reason, then there must be missing pages of Secret Martial Arts I obtained, and the books in the Dojo are not complete. There must be some key requirements for those two Secret Martial Arts, just like the Explosive Fist Arts and White Cloud Secret Arts, I needed to consume the Body Quenching Pill which was not written in the book. Such requirements are probably passed on by word of mouth." Garen recalled how fast he had learned Boulder Martial Arts and Iron Body, he was sure the Body Quenching Pill helped him a lot.

"I need to find the missing pages quickly, those low-level Secret Martial Arts can be found everywhere. I need to visit other sects after the things here are done."

About the sects that were holding Secret Martial Arts, Garen remembered the new organization founded not so long ago, Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate, and he was one of the three Divine Marshals there.

"I’m a member of it, and I think it’ll be fine if I want to check the normal Secret Martial Arts stored there. The Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was the combination of many different sects, it must have something valuable in its library."

Garen suddenly had the urge to go to the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate.

"Also, White Bird Holy Fist Palosa is there, and I want to see how strong his legendary Fist Arts really are!"

The Holy Fist!

His Fist Arts were remarkably strong that people considered him as a saint.

If it was called Holy Fist, it must be much stronger than average Secret Martial Arts.

White Bird Holy Fist was one of the top Fist Arts Masters in this era, and Garen felt excited that he had the chance to actually meet Palosa in person.

"After this is done, I will head to Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate!" Garen made up his mind.

*******************

For the next several days, Garen trained with Su Lin’s Sister Aris every morning and taught her some basic training techniques. Those techniques were developed by the elders, and they could be applied to almost anyone.

Those techniques were the foundations in the Mammoth Gate, people would not be able to practice them properly without being coached by someone from the gate, and they were mostly used for exercises.

Every single action mentioned in the techniques were important, and Aris needed to meet the standards of those actions. The techniques could help Aris strengthen her body and avoid injuries during the training.

Garen was coaching her and made a special plan for Aris. He considered how much exercise Aris could do per day, and how strong her body was at its current state.

Garen decided what she ate every day, and he also crafted the medicine used to treat general injuries for her. Also, Garen was trying to apply mild venoms on his palms in order to level up Dark Iron Palm, he used things like poisonous insects and plants. However, nothing worked.

Garen was sure the Secret Martial Arts he obtained had missing pages, and he needed something else to help him meet the requirements.

He also practiced Firestream Fist every day based on the standard techniques, he knew he was progressing, but it was so slow that he might as well ignore it.

Garen thought it would take him years to reach the entry level at this rate, and it seemed Firestream Fist also had some special requirements for him to be able to speed up the process.

Five days passed, and he did nothing besides coaching Aris.

Finally, Su Lin sent Garen a message on the last day of the deadline.

********************

On top of a hill not so far from the manor.

A middle-aged man dressed like a noble stepped on the leaves that dropped from the trees, he was surveying the manor and the lake.

The man’s blonde hair was a bit dark, and it spread out over his shoulders. His pupils were pink and beautiful, and they were almost glowing under the sunlight

The man had a black whip rolled up in his hand. He looked like a nobleman that was about to go hunting.

"This is Crohn’s manor?"

"Yes." A man with mask appeared behind the tree on the right. He was wearing green, making him hard to be detected in such environment.

"Crohn and Belfatalia are two of the top commanders in the south, and they are both Lieutenant Generals. I think they already know we are here because there are people from the Spy Agency currently in the manor."

"That Spy Agency?" the man in green wondered. "How much did they spend on this? I heard about the infamous federal agency a long time ago, and I never expected to actually see them in person. Is Director Wellington here too?"

"Yea."

"Let’s wait for everyone to arrive then. All of our member are here this time. Whatever, I am not the one giving orders now, and I will let Duskdune Shura worry about all this," the man said in a light tone.

"Wellington…" another deep voice came from behind.

"The last time I saw him was 30 years ago." A man in a black cloak appeared from the shadows.

"You are here? Duskdune Shura. What’s the plan?" the man with pink pupils leaned to the side and asked.

"Nothing special. We go in, take out the target, and leave," Duskdune Shura spoke in a light tone.

"Are you kidding me?"

"I will do it myself this time."

The man with pink pupil hesitated, he wanted to say something, but he decided not to.

"Let’s wait for everyone before going in. Crohn ignored my offer, and that’s what he will get." Duskdune Shura stared at the manor down the hill.

"Actually… I have a question," the man with pink pupil said. "Is it really worth it? You need all of us to join this mission just for the thing you talked about?"

"You don’t understand. I will explain after everything is done," Duskdune Shura responded.

The man stared at Duskdune Shura, and the atmosphere got heavy. He spoke again after a while.

"Fine. I hope you have a good reason for this."

"I will do whatever you tell me to do. That’s what I promised," a cold female voice came from the top of the tree.

A lady with green hair was sitting on the branch, she was wearing a white eyepatch, and her other eye was open.

"You won’t be disappointed," Duskdune Shura muttered, "let’s move."

He started to head down the hill.

The man with pink pupils followed him in the back, and many green shadows were moving from both sides of the bushes, but they barely made any noises.

"Golden Sword Throne… Duskdune Shura, I hope you don’t lose yourself," the lady on the tree mumbled.

Chapter 123: Heated Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside the manor.

Su Lin stood by the window and crossed his arms, he was looking outside.

"They are here. They didn’t even disguise themselves!" His eyes were filled up with excitement and expectations.

"Show me what you got, the former Royal Generals of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate…"

As a Martial Artist, he wanted to observe and pursue higher-level skills.

********

Inside the changeroom.

Garen was putting on the tight black coat, but he suddenly stopped.

"The enemies are already here, and you are still wandering around?" he turned back and spoke in a cold tone.

"You should worry more about yourself and don’t get killed by the former Royal Generals!" Yoda, the Eight-arm Dragon King, sneered and walked out of the shadow. There were eight heavy sniper rifles on his back, they looked like peafowl tails, and it was almost like there were wings on his back. People would feel scared just by looking at the man.

"I hope you know more than just talking." Garen put on his clothes, turned back, and left the room.

"Same to you!" Yoda stopped saying anything. He turned around and disappeared into the shadows again.

Garen closed the door slowly and walked toward the exit of the hallway quickly.

********

About several hundred meters away from the manor.

Under the sunlight, leaves were dropping down the tree.

Suddenly, several black projectiles were thrown toward the manor.

*BAM BAM*

After the gunshots, those black projectiles exploded and turned into fireballs.

At the same time, the guards hiding inside the manor were hit, they groaned and fell to the ground. Fresh bullet entry wounds decorated their foreheads.

*WUUUUUU*

The alarm was triggered right away.

*BOOM*

The gate of the manor was blown away by a fireball, the flame dropped to the guards behind it like liquid, and they started burning.

Those human torches groaned and struggled before falling to the ground.

Three black shadows flashed into the manor as the gate opened, they looked like three black strings.

*BAM*

One of the black shadows opened fire and multiple shots were fired within a second.

Snipers on the roofs were hit all at the same time and were all taken out.

Machine gunners started firing as well, but they were all dealt with after the first rounds were finished, and the only thing they actually did was making mud splashes.

Two teams of soldiers appeared on both sides of the building and were rolling to dodge the projectiles, but their foreheads were hit halfway and they died instantly.

Three black shadows stood in the middle of the manor’s lawn. They were all wearing black cloaks. From head to toe including their faces, they were covered in black.

Dozens of soldiers followed them into the manor. They all had submachine guns in their hands, wearing green suits and masks. Those soldiers started trading shots with the guards inside the manor quickly.

"Proceed as planned," the first black cloak said in a hoarse voice.

"They are hiding at different positions, and they are far away from each other. Many guards are protecting them. I am not sure what they are planning, what should we do?" another black cloak said in a low voice. There was a lot of gun firing going, but they could still hear each other’s voices.

"They are trying to hit us from multiple angles maybe. If they want to play hide-and-seek, we can do it as well. Let’s separate from here," the leading black cloak said. "They were trying to distract us with the guards and exhaust us. They’ve probably already regroup. We need to move before more guards show up."

"Don’t worry. The manor is huge. At this rate, it will take them several minutes until they can meet up with each other, and that’s more than enough time for us," the last black cloak was a woman, and she said the words in a cold tone.

"Move! Fire the signal after you find the target!"

They moved toward three different directions before the final word left his mouth. Right after they left, a black grenade dropped to their wherever they just were and exploded.

********

Inside a stone house beside the river.

Su Lin’s sister Aris was drinking flower tea with Garen beside a table.

One side of the stone house was open, and dock stairs were built beside it. Waves were hitting the white stone stairs occasionally, sweeping some green water plants to the shore.

Rays of sunlight hit the surface of the lake and reflected back onto their faces. The lake glinted in the sun, and it was glaring.

"I love afternoons, so relaxing…" Aris lied down on the wicker chair, her beautiful hair spread out on the white pillow, and there was a lazy but sexy expression on her face.

She used her slim fingers to block the reflected sunlight, "I want to take a nap…" her voice lowered down.

"Well, no more than half an hour. If you really want to sleep, I can wake you up when it's time." Garen sat on the side, sipping a cup of red flower tea. "We began the training several days ago, and you already got tired. Now I know why you can’t even reach the entry level."

He looked at Aris, "You need the perseverance to practice Martial Arts, without that, it will be hard for you to get the hang of it."

"But I want to sleep…" Aris got familiar with Garen, and she was not acting like a gentle girl anymore, she always had a lazy but sexy look on her face.

"Ladies always need more sleep!"

She turned to the side and stared at Garen in curiosity.

"Master Garen, are you looking for a girlfriend now?"

"Nope." Garen shrugged, "Don’t try to change the topic."

"But I’m really tired…" Aris started acting like a spoiled child, "I need to take care of my skin, comb my hair, read books, and work every day. I need to make sure I have enough sleep so my skin will stay elastic."

"But if you—"

*BOOM*

Garen’s words were interrupted by an explosion, and he heard the alarm right after.

He looked at the direction of the manor in shock.

"Don’t worry. They are probably doing the military exercises again." Aris laughed nonchalantly, but the laziness in her eyes was replaced by some sharpness.

She stood up, left the chair and looked at the direction of the manor. Aris had a glance at a pattern on the stone house’s right side corner, and the pattern rotated by itself without making any noise.

He finally came… Duskdune Shura.

Aris slowly combed the hair to the side of her face with her fingers and tied it up. Although there was a smile on her face, her eyes were not laughing at all.

"Master Garen, let’s move. If we don’t go to the special soundproof room, the military exercise will bother us. It’s usually very noisy."

"I’m fine with that." Garen stood up.

*Poof*

A strange light sound came from outside the door.

The pattern at the corner rotated again, and Aris stopped moving after seeing the change.

"That’s was fast!" Her pupils contracted a bit. The rotation of the pattern meant the enemies were already here, and Colonel Moen, the one in charge of her safety, was already fighting them.

Also, it meant that the enemies had already surrounded them, and Colonel Moen wanted Aris to stay in the house and wait for further updates.

The original plan they had was meeting up in a certain location after the alarm was triggered. They were not so far from each other, and it would take them several minutes to reach the place.

However, the enemies were fast, and they were already here before Aris could move.

"Actually, I’m still tired. Let’s sit down and have some more rest." Aris smiled and sat down slowly.

Garen sat down as well, he narrowed his eyes and knew something was wrong.

*******************

*CHI*

Colonel Moen slowly returned the spiked chain back to his hands.

The end of the chain was pinned to a green masked man’s throat, stained with blood dripping down. The chain shivered and returned to his hands like a silver snake.

After the chain had returned to his hands, he glanced around.

There were more than ten dead bodies of the green masked soldiers lying on the ground beside the lake, their heads, throats, or hearts were impaled by the chain.

Blood was all over the ground, and the yellow shore almost turned red.

"Sir!" two soldiers in brown suits ran to Moen and saluted him, "All enemies have been eliminated! What are your orders?"

"Good," Moen looked at them, "How’s the situation in the manor?"

"Everything is proceeding as planned," the soldiers answered immediately.

Moen was going to say something else, but his expression suddenly changed and rolled to the left.

*BAM BAM*

The two soldiers fell to the ground after getting shot in the heart.

Moen fired two times without looking, he then quickly rolled again and stood up.

The enemy was right behind him after dodging the bullets. The enemy changed his position as Moen stood up, and he managed to stay behind Moen the whole time.

Moen turned around again and fired four times with the white pistol in his hand, he was aiming at all the possible angles the enemy could hide.

He quickly backed off after firing his pistol and dodged two bullets from the enemy.

"Silenced pistol? There is more than one enemy here!"

He kicked some sand into the air and threw out a black grenade sneakily.

He jumped forward and started rolling again.

*BOOM*

The grenade exploded behind him, sand on the shore was blown into the air and dropped down like rain.

Moen quickly got up and threw his chain toward the front.

*Clank*

The thorns on the chain were blocked, wrapped on the silencer of the black pistol.

In front of Moen, there were two twin girls that looked exactly the same. Their eyes, hair, and tight suits were all green, and they both had beautiful faces.

"How did you manage to stay alive?" one of the twin girls said in a deep tone.

"Don’t worry. Let me deal with him, and I’ll let him know, me, Master Sayman, is the No.1 in the green team!"

A tall man in green cloak approached Moen from the side.

"The Royal Generals will know how brave I am." The man named Sayman had a strange expression on his face, and it seemed like he was expecting something.

Moen backed off and returned the chain to his hands.

He had a serious look on his face and waved his hand.

Teams of soldiers in brown walked out of the bushes, they all had gun in their hands, and there were about a hundred of them here.

They surrounded the twin and the man in the middle.

"Kill them all!" Moen ordered.

He quickly moved backward and stood behind the soldiers.

Chapter 124: Heated Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the middle of the manor.

Dadadada!!!

Multiple machine guns furiously fired out a frightening rain of bullets.

The deafening sound of gunfire in the manor made everyone's eardrums ache painfully.

In the center, there was a two-story mansion.

Su Lin's father, General Crohn, stood side by side with a blue-bearded bald man on the second floor in a room with French windows. They quietly surveyed the scattered battlefield.

Both of them were dressed in black army general uniforms. They stood straight with their hands clasped behind their backs. Two calm, beautiful assistant officers stood behind them.

"This is not looking too good," Crohn said in an undertone as he looked over at the blue-bearded man. "Descon, perhaps we have to do it by ourselves."

"If the two leaders must personally take care of this, then it would already be a negligence of duty on their part." The blue-bearded Descon was emotionless. "Duskdune Shura, renowned as one of the top three assassination organizations. If they were to die facing these assassins, it would be a blessing for the Confederation."

"You are this confident in your subordinates? I heard that after I left, you managed to scout some new talents?"

"Not through scouting, it was through courting. You know that the guys at the special agent bureau joined because they had too much bad history with the state. Talented people without a bad record would never join." Descon explained, "The new recruit is an infamous, wanted outlaw from the Seluja Confederation, which makes this a good opportunity to test his skill. As the strongest assassination organization in the Stonecliff Continent, Duskdune Shura have already been encountered multiple times. It would be a good opportunity to gauge their strength."

"That’s a good point," Crohn nodded, "but I am still worried about my son and daughter. Even though I sent some help there, I don’t know if the help will arrive in time." A glimpse of worry flashed across his face. "Duskdune Shura’s speed is remarkable."

"They’ll have to face this eventually as it is their adventure as well. Without hardships, there would be no growth. As parents, the only thing you can really do is worry," the blue-bearded man exclaimed as he stroked his beard.

"All of your children are accomplished, but it is a pity. If Canou was still here…" His eyes dimmed down.

"That was an accident. Don’t think too much, it’s part of what we do." Crohn quickly changed the topic. "Oh right, New Pacific Corporation has recently announced that they conquered a route to the east. I don’t know if this is real or not. Do you have any insider information?"

"Hmm… New Pacific have always been accountable to the Blue Parliament, so I can’t intervene as part of the Red Parliament. But I have heard from Senator Taniyas that New Pacific did in fact established a relatively new sea route to the ancient east."

"Mhmm. The porcelain from the East, spices, and handicrafts are among the most expensive luxuries. With the establishment of a stable route, New Pacific Corporation would be the center of attention for a long time," Crohn exclaimed. "If it is possible to establish a trade relationship with the giant ancient kingdom on the other side of the sea, it would be immensely helpful to the Confederation!"

"Don’t think too much yet and focus on solving the problem at hand." Blue-bearded Descon lowered his voice as he slowly turned around to the direction of the door. "Let’s go take a look?"

"Lead the way." Crohn smiled and followed.

**************

Pa… Pa… Pa…

In a dark yellow office in another part of the manor.

Su Lin spun around in a black leather chair as he played around with a silver pistol. The gun’s barrel was extremely long and wide, while the metal surface looked brand new and gleamed with a bright, reflective, silver light. The handle of the gun was made of wood and featured an upright roaring brown bear carved on it. The letters "KZ" were engraved on top.

"This pistol is so damn sexy!" Su Lin could not stop playing with the gun.

Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King, sat on a wooden chair beside the table with his legs crossed. He had a long-stemmed bronze pipe in his mouth as he continuously breathed out rings of smoke.

"As long as you like it. This is my specially crafted, upgraded version of the Seline Pistol."

"It uses Denuda bullets with engravings. Among special bullets that use purple explosive, its power is not to be underestimated."

"Purple explosive? Damn! You can even get your hands on these types of prohibited items and you have the audacity to say you live in seclusion!" Su Lin disdainfully glanced at the Dragon King. "With the addition of purple explosive, is this the type of bullet that’s used to hunt devil girls as the rumor says?"

"The church has used this type of bullet to hunt down devil girls from what I know, so you could say that. It was different in the past though, so time may have changed a few things." He took a deep drag from his pipe as he jubilantly closed his eyes. "This gun’s effective range is 800 meters, so you’ll have to make the judgement. Make sure that when you use it, you don’t shoot people that are lined up or you will have to bear the consequences when it penetrates multiple people."

"800 meters!!" Su Lin almost dropped the pistol on the carpet. "Are you saying this is a sniper rifle?!"

"No sh*t! If some powerful individuals wore bulletproof vests, the combination would be impossible to penetrate even with a sniper rifle. If I didn’t have anything to offer, how could I be called the Eight-Arm Dragon King?!" Yoda answered in slight annoyance. "Be careful of the recoil."

"I already have a terrible feeling about this," Su Lin mumbled.

"The bullets are specially designed and can only be fired five times. Don’t waste them as these types of explosive rounds are hard to find. This is a potent weapon designed to fight against powerful individuals."

Su Lin felt the weight of the hefty pistol in his hand as a frightened feeling emerged in his mind.

**************

Bang.

Beside the lake, a red flare exploded in the sky.

Fallen Confederation soldiers in yellow uniforms were scattered across the beach. The blood followed the trail of bodies and gradually drained into the lake. A majority of the lake was already colored red.

The twins in green stood quietly at the river bank. Although both of their arms were slowly bleeding, their eyes were full of defiance.

The man named Sayman tried to catch his breath standing in front of the twins with his gaze locked on the Confederation Colonel Moen.

"Woo… So it is you! Silver Snake Moen! You became a pawn for the Special Agent Bureau! I didn’t imagine this!"

Colonel Moen’s body was full of bloody cuts that looked like they were inflicted by a dagger like weapon. His yellow uniform had already been stained a red color.

The battle was too fast and was decided in a matter of seconds.

The twins had wielded two guns that, at a glance, looked like assault rifles and fired rapidly. Each bullet was incredibly accurate and wiped out the hundred elite soldiers.

But it was not without repercussions. Both of their arms suffered grievous wounds and they could no longer use weapons.

Moen and Sayman’s clash immediately resulted in them using their strongest moves as they wanted to finish the opponent in the shortest time. Unfortunately, because Moen lost focus due to losing his soldiers, he was cut despite being equally skilled compared to Sayman.

"I didn’t think it was you either." Moen sneered, "Black Feather Blade Sayman, it’s a pity, but you all have to die here."

He already heard the hasty footsteps of additional soldiers coming to his aid.

This place was surrounded by soldiers already.

"I also feel pity. If you had joined Duskdune Shura, you wouldn’t have died here." Sayman suddenly squinted his eyes as he smiled.

Moen paused slightly as he wanted to say something.

Suddenly, he felt that someone was standing behind him. Then, he felt a sharp pain in his chest as the world began to spin around him. He flew out and crashed on the beach.

"How is this … possible!"

Moen did not understand. When his body was spinning in midair, he saw a figure in a black cape standing behind him.

He was a Special Agent Bureau Colonel that could defend against bullets! The keys to guarding against gunfire were strength and acuity in the five senses. Then, to change position and finish the enemy before they could even pull the trigger.

With such powerful senses, Moen only realized his opponent was behind him when the enemy was inches away.

Bang.

Moen’s body crashed on the beach as blood began to emerge from his chest. His eyes widened as if he did not understand why. The man in the black cape stood at the same place.

"You all are too slow."

Sayman and the twins did not dare to respond as they lowered their heads.

Rapid footsteps were approaching, but it was not confederation soldiers in yellow. Instead, it was masked killers in green.

Two middle-aged individuals, a man and a woman, led the way while wearing a different uniform, but of the same green color.

"Marshal, we have taken care of the situation," the middle-aged man reported as he came to a standstill. He confusedly looked at Sayman and the twins. "What did you guys get yourself into?"

"We met the Silver Snake from before," Sayman answered in a resigned tone as he pointed at the body not far away. "He is a Colonel of the Special Agent Bureau. If it was not for the Marshal’s arrival, we would have been in trouble!"

As they were talking, the black caped man walked to the small stone house.

From the time that the assassins started attacking to Moen’s death, it all had happened within half a minute. These rapid actions did not take much time at all.

**************

In the stone house.

Aris sat quietly on a deck chair as her eyes occasionally glanced at the flower pattern on the wall. Just when she had sat down, the sound of gunshots began to reach the room.

She was hesitant about whether she should leave immediately by herself or wait for the Colonel’s return.

The secret tunnel could only be opened once before it was locked down. This design was to prevent the enemy from chasing.

Within half a minute, the gunshots died down.

Aris knew that there were hundreds of soldiers hidden outside. Although she heard some screams, the only logical explanation for everything suddenly ceasing was that the enemy must have been eradicated! Even Duskdune Shura could not resist a force comprised of Colonel Moen along with a hundred soldiers head on right?

She glanced at Garen on the side as he poured another cup of tea.

"Hmm? Is the drill over?" Garen lowered his voice.

"No, not this fast." Aris smiled as she was just about to explain to him.

Suddenly, the stone house’s door gradually opened.

A figure in a black cape stood silently in front of the door.

Aris’s pupils suddenly contracted as she felt her body freeze. Without thinking, she stomped her right foot as a dresser suddenly opened, exposing the dark underground tunnel passage.

"Go!!" Aris loudly screamed as she jumped into the passage, but she did not hear the sound of Garen following.

"Sorry, no traffic through here."

She heard Garen’s calm voice.

Garen slowly stood up as he directly faced the open door with his body blocking the closing passage.

"It is you, Divine Marshal Garen," another voice said in an undertone.

Aris’s eyes popped. "Brother Garen." All of a sudden, she realized what her brother, Su Lin, had intended.

The intruder slowly lifted the cape exposing a face with pink pupils.

"Now let me see, Divine Marshal and Royal General, who is the ultimate conqueror!"

Chapter 125: Heated Battle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!

In the manor, a black cape suddenly stopped. In front of him, a large amount of flaming debris exploded everywhere. The bright yellow flame removed all the shadow under his cape as a beautiful yet cold female face appeared.

Not far from him, more than ten killers in green were killed in the explosion. A few lucky ones survived, and only their limbs were blown off as they crawled on the ground to escape from the fire.

"Third Royal General Charlotte."

From a hidden window not far away, the Eight-Armed Dragon King locked onto the caped woman as he said in an undertone.

"I can’t believe the Duskdune Shura is using this much force. What did your dad get himself into that made them attack with full forces without considering the consequences?" He turned around at looked at Su Lin behind him.

"I don’t know, I hope it's not like he killed their family or anything like that." Su Lin shrugged.

"Whatever, the hidden bombs are probably not going to be effective. This guy’s instincts are too sharp! Leave first, I’ll do it myself." Eight-Armed Dragon King Yoda bit onto his smoke pipe and began to check and load his sniper rifle rounds one by one.

"Are you sure? One person. A Special Agent Colonel is protecting here on the outside, there is no way they get in here that fast." Su Lin looked rather relaxed.

"The scary thing is that she doesn’t need to go through the door," Eight-Armed Dragon King said quietly.

Su Lin walked over to see outside when he spotted that Third Royal General Charlotte was gradually taking out two black barrels from under her cape. She slowly assembled them together to create an odd looking gun with a barrel sized of a fist.

"What is that…"

"Damnit." The Eight-Armed Dragon King rapidly lifted up a sniper rifle as he aimed at Charlotte and fired.

Boom!

The black cape in vision suddenly exploded as the upper body shattered into pieces of meat. Only the lower half walked a few steps before falling over.

"That’s it?" Su Lin was shocked.

"Still too early!" the Eight-Armed Dragon King sneered. "Let’s go! She has already found this place! That’s a fake."

He dragged Su Lin and left.

From an underground entrance in the corner at the right side of the room, they ran in before the entrance quickly closed.

Bang!

The door was kicked open as a black cape dragged a Colonel in. She scanned the room before her vision locked onto the entrance at the corner of the room.

Boom!

Another loud noise and flames suddenly erupted and emerged from the closet, table, floor, and the ceiling. Flames burst out from everywhere in the room.

The room turned into a sea of fire.

At the tunnel beside the room, a black cape crossed her arms and leaned against the wall. She looked at the room emerged in flame before quietly walked away.

*****

In the underground tunnel.

"Hello, didn’t you say I’d go in alone while you’d stay behind? Why are you running with me!?" Su Lin looked at Dragon King Yoda running in front speechlessly.

"I am running because I am going to help other places." Yoda smiled, "If my guess is correct, that bastard has already entered the death trap. Two fakes already died, even she can’t be overzealous now."

Bang!

A depressed explosion echoed from the back as the ground shook.

"Look. She is done." A cheerful smile emerged on Yoda’s face.

************

In the tunnel.

The black cape stood at the same place silently, not making a single move.

The exploded room burned not far behind from her as the sound of wood burning and crackling was occasionally heard.

Tiny droplets of sweat appeared on Charlotte’s face. Her beautiful eyes were constantly scanning her surroundings.

"This setup. Only you, Yoda," she mumbled as her body didn’t dare to move a single inch.

She knew that if she moved slightly, the hidden bombs would all explode. She didn’t know the nature of the mechanisms. Sensor? Time? Pressure? Trap?

But she knew that if she moved a single step, whether to the front or the back, she would immediately trigger the bomb.

No one could undermine Eight-Armed Dragon King Yoda’s bomb.

Her eyes focused as she suddenly realized that her body was surrounded by tightened transparent silks.

The silks were tightened like metal wires and filled the room. It was like a silkworm's cocoon as it completely covered her.

She knew that if she touched any wire, it would start a chain of violent explosions.

Countless silks created a human-sized space exactly where she was standing. This was the only place where she could avoid any of the silks.

Splash.

A droplet of sweat fell down on the ground.

"Pity, but you are underestimating me." A hint of arrogance slowly emerged on her beautiful face.

*****

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

Four sniper rifles simultaneously fired at all four directions.

Yoda had two on his hands, two on his feet. His feet naked as his toes were as agile as his fingers. They freely adjusted the direction of shooting.

Every shot from the four sniper rifles would accurately take away four lives.

Su Lin stood behind him along with a young man in a Colonel uniform who was responsible for protecting Su Lin. The person that had previously died was a fake.

The two stared hysterically at the Eight-Armed Dragon King’s performance.

The three stood on top of the three-story building.

Bang Bang Bang… amongst the heavy gunfire, Yoda ecstatically roared.

"Haha! Go die! Die!"

The faint gray smokes filled his surrounding as it gave a bloodthirsty taste.

Suddenly Yoda rolled.

A black dot dropped from the sky.

Peng!

A black spear pinned where he was standing before. The silver tip penetrated deep into the concrete floor.

"I knew I wouldn’t get you, Charlotte." Yoda stood up as he moved to the edge of the building calmly.

Bam!

The black hook suddenly appeared from the edge of the building as a person hopped on top.

Black cape, as the head was not covered, a beautiful yet cold face appeared, and one of her eyes was hidden behind a white patch. She retracted the black hook.

"Yoda, I haven’t seen you in a while, you are still this sinister. Too bad, I am within twenty meters of you. Should you give up or should I personally end you?"

"Isn’t ‘sinister’ the definition for you?" Yoda sneered. "You should be the one giving up."

His hands shook.

Crack crack crack…

The cracking sound filled the top floor.

The eight sniper rifles on this body simultaneously divided into two arcs as the gun barrels all pointed directly at Charlotte.

"Do you know why I can be called the Dragon King?" He began to laugh.

"That’s because no one can beat me when I have eight rifles. Therefore, I am known as Eight-Armed Dragon King!"

Charlotte froze in place without moving a single inch.

She was extremely focused as the eight rifles were all equipped with special explosives and bullets with rapid firing speed.

She had originally thought that Yoda’s name was just an exaggeration, but she didn’t believe it was like this.

She noticed that Yoda controlled the eight sniper rifles with his special transparent silks.

"Let me see how much strength is left of the original Royal General." Yoda groaned as two barrels combined to fire simultaneously.

Bang!

Garen and One of the Four Royal General separated as both took steps back.

Pieces of clothes and dust from their impacts still scattered in the air.

Within the stone house, Garen finally heard the tunnel closing behind him, and a smile appeared on his face.

Without thinking, he suddenly bumped left as broken stones scattered.

He broke the wall and fell in the water.

Boom!

The stone room exploded in a second and was completely engulfed in fire. The reflection colored the lake into a dark red.

Garen just walked out of the lake before a black shadow dashed at him.

"Double Star!"

Two blue lights shined from the black shadow and flew directly at Garen’s chest. It was the light from the reflection of the daggers’ tip.

A grimace showed on the Pink Pupil Royal General’s face. Both of his arms were fake as two crescent-shaped daggers popped from below. From the blade, it was obvious that it was made through multiple materials combined together.

The two chilling stars fiercely stabbed in Garen’s chest.

Bang!

Garen’s body leaned upward as the dagger was popped away.

"Slash!"

Pink Pupil Royal General whipped his hands as he released a cloud of gray sands which completely submerged Garen.

He then stepped backward.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Countless amount of bullets fired directly at Garen. These gray sands were explosives and were instantly ignited. The explosion's red flame engulfed Garen.

The shooting lasted for a few seconds before it stopped.

Where Garen stood was completely covered in smoke and nothing was visible.

"Don’t play these boring tricks again."

All the sudden, Garen’s voice gradually appeared from the smoke, calm and collected.

Pink Pupil Royal General’s eyes slightly contracted, and he gazed onto Garen walking out of the smoke.

This strong man’s body looked like steel plates with the light black color, his body size seemed to have increased. He slowly walked out of the smoke as his upper body was completely naked. There was not a single sign of injury on his body.

"Impeccable Body Hardening Technique!" Royal General’s voice lowered. "Looks like normal weapons are useless against you. Too bad Charlotte is not here."

"Charlotte? Another Royal General?" Garen confusedly asked.

Bang!

Another bullet fiercely hit his right eye. The moment the gun fired, Garen closed his eyes, and his eyelid bounced away the bullet.

"Annoying little bugger."

He waved his right hand.

A killer in green not far away was frightened as he held his neck, a blood hole appearing on his neck.

The entire battleground was silent. A bullet couldn’t even penetrate his eyelids!

This terrifying Body Hardening Technique must have reached human’s limit?!

Royal General’s face twitched as he unknowingly stepped backward.

Garen scanned around.

"Too many buggers... let’s clean up the battlefield first."

Before his voice died down, Pink Pupil Royal General suddenly felt a fearsome aura exploding within him.

His face paled as a frightening thought flashed across his mind.

"Lori! Run!" he suddenly used all his energy to scream out.

Boom!

A wave of terrifying aura completely engulfed him in a glimpse.

Chapter 126: Heated Battle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two twin girls heard the scream and unwillingly flipped backward and blended in with the forest. It seemed that something had pulled them into the forest.

Inside the forest, another slender shadow stood. It seemed to be a woman.

The twin girls finally realized what was happening and stared at the fearsome aura by the sandy beach.

The Pink Pupil Royal General was standing there along with the large group of killers in green.

Looking afar, Garen felt the air around him moving in twisted ways. As if something below the ground was howling, there was a horrifying noise of shaking.

Both of his eyes were glowing with the color of blood. It was a premonition.

The twins’ bodies started to shake lightly. A deep insane fear was pouring out of their hearts and was trying to take control of their bodies.

"With opponents like this… How is it possible that we win!!??"

Bang bang bang!!

Machine guns, pistols; bullets were crashing against the frightening silhouettes, yet sparks were flying. It was absolutely useless.

Just as they were taking out the grenades, they exploded after being hit by the thin sands Garen threw out. In an instant, blood and human skin went flying. Even Sayman could only try and shield himself from the powerful aura. Tiredly, he only dared to shoot his machine gun from a far distance.

Only the Royal General dared!

He crazily dashed towards the opponent, wrapping himself tightly with faint auras in order to protect himself.

The twins’ bodies were starting to shake harder.

"Don’t look! This is an illusionary mental stress! It only affects your thoughts. Don’t look at him directly!"

A pair of delicate white hands simultaneously covered the two girls’ eyes.

Bang!!

Bang!!

Bang!!

Garen stood where he was in silence. He pitifully looked at the Pink Pupil Royal General, who was continuously being bounced back by the counter quake. On the ground, on the sand, the opponent’s blood was splashed everywhere. The serious injuries were caused by the counter quake created by the changed Mammoth Secret Technique.

"Time flies," Garen stood there, unmoving. He calmly stared at the Pink Pupil Royal General, who was having difficulties standing up.

"This is your aura?" He watched as his opponent tightened his body. it was only enough to protect one area of his body.

The sound of bullets continuously shooting out of guns started ringing again. Garen’s body was flashing with golden sparks. However, nothing could stop his footsteps.

Step by step, he walked toward the Royal General, leaving a trail of fresh footprints. He stood before his opponent.

"Maybe I am too naïve. Time is unkind. No matter how strong someone is, will become weak as time goes on," in reality, he knew very well that his aura became stronger after he fully consolidated his improvements after becoming the Grandmaster of Combat. In other words, he got stronger.

Hu…hu…

The Pink Pupil Royal General breathed heavily.

"It is true that my capability is only half of what it was like during the full blooming stage… If I still had both of hands… I would beat you up so bad your mother wouldn’t recognize you!!" he cursed.

"Your power then is only twice the power you have now?" Garen was disappointed.

"Ah!!!"

Instantly, a green shadow appeared behind Garen. With the army knife he had in hand, he tried to pierce through Garen’s left year.

Moo!!!

The horrifying sound of an elephant growling rumbled beside the two people’s ears.

Garen’s body swelled up crazily and reached two and a half meters high. His muscles knotted together and tightened, just like rows of steel bars.

A giant amount of aura solidified around him and formed into an illusion of a growling white mammoth.

The black army knife froze right beside Garen’s left ear.

The blade was shaking.

Blackplume Sayman was shaking uncontrollably.

His eyes were watering and his nose was runny, yet he didn’t dare to wipe them off. He held the army knife with both hands and used all his strength to try and pierce through. However, it was as if the knife has been solidified. It stayed motionless.

"M…Move!!" Sayman finally cried out. It appeared that he remembered a similar experience from before. His tears rolled down his cheeks continuously.

Bang!

The blade pierced through.

Garen was astonished. So was the Royal General on the ground.

In the forest not far away, the slender woman was also in shock.

The left-over killers on the battleground also froze in surprise.

"We won?"

Pia!

The army knife fell to the ground weakly. Everyone’s heart dropped.

Garen was expressionless. Not a single drop of blood dripped from his ear.

"What a shame."

Single shot!

Chi!

Garen’s arm entered through Sayman’s chest and exited out the back.

"Jency!!"

At that moment, Pink Pupil Royal General aggressively pushed forward. His auras were seemingly howling like an owl. With two hands holding onto the knife, he swung toward Garen’s soft skin around his chin.

Taking advantage of Garen’s one split second distracted state, he stabbed. This stab took all of the Royal General’s strength. It was the best move he knew that was derived from the Star Fist, incorporating three different sources of strength with each source releasing power at a different time. In the end however, they would all converge at the tip of the blade and release with three times the normal strength.

Rather than saying he stabbed with the knife, it was more like he shot out the knife with two hands, then he used the technique to speed up the knife two times.

The Royal General put his palms together and pushed up the knife toward Garen’s chin. Immediately, the sword’s handle spat out blue and purple flames. He sped up the knife for a fourth time with another push!!

This stab was like a silver and blue vertical line that flashed across Garen’s body, as if it was going to slice Garen into two halves.

"Die!!"

The Royal General, at this very moment, felt like he had reverted back to his most powerful days. This attack was strong enough to have been the best move he had ever made.

The price he paid after one attack, was that he had no more strength left for any more attacks.

"If I can kill this guy then I am okay with it!" looking at the knife blade pricking Garen’s skin, his eyes were filled with anticipation.

Dang!

The Royal General’s expression turned into desperation.

Garen was looking down on him. His right hand blocked that attack.

"If you used this attack while you were in full bloom stage, I might’ve been badly wounded. Pity…"

The Royal General opened his lips to say something. Yet no words came out.

He silently sat on the ground. His eyes, ears, nose, and mouth were all seeping with fresh blood. The effects of the counter quake ensured that he no more chance of survival.

"This move was called Jency? Only one move…no wonder you are a late Royal General," Garen extended his index finger and pushed his opponent’s forehead lightly.

Puff.

The Royal General collapsed onto the ground and never breathed again.

This move was a little too aggressive. Garen had to block it with his hand. Even with changed Mammoth Secret Technique, he still had areas of weakness. He had no choice but to shield himself with his hand.

When he turned up his right hand, Garen saw the blood flowing out of the center of his palm. He was finally wounded.

The Royal General was already over 50 years old, yet he still had such strong abilities and was able to sustain his youthful look. On top of that, he was able to cause slight damage to Garen.

With these facts in mind, it was no wonder he had the title of a Royal General.

Casually flicking, he threw out a fistful of small rocks. The killers in green reduced in numbers again.

Under the stress and pressure of the aura, these killers were as tiny as ants to Garen.

After killing everyone, Garen slowly dispelled the conditions of being in the third stage and reverted to his original form. He glanced at the forest. People in there had long escaped without leaving any trace.

He walked back to where Pink Pupil Royal General was, and searched his body.

A wallet, a piece of ID that could’ve been fake, some white napkins, a few black medal cards. Finally, there was also a small notebook.

He hurriedly put everything together and casually flipped through the notebook. On it was pen written notes of training as well as his experiences. Because the battle was still going on in the manor, he didn’t have time to look through it carefully. Garen stuffed it into his pocket.

His pants were specially made by Su Lin, who added special protection on them. This was why he didn’t have to leave this place butt naked.

Also why he had a useful pocket.

After he took care of the stuff, Garen picked up a random machine gun and jogged toward the manor.

Over there, the sound of gunfights was still ongoing. The battle between the Confederation army and the group of killers was getting more and more intense.

"I wonder how the situation is. I must find Su Lin and them fast."

Bang!!

Yoda shot three guns into the air, aiming at Charlotte, The Third Royal General.

The three bullets each landed on different areas of the body. However, Charlotte’s elastic like body twisted and turned, dodging them all. She then landed on a pole on top of a roof.

Charlotte was getting frustrated and tired. She had long thrown away her black cape. Inside she wrote a red and bulletproof bodysuit made out of stretchable elastics. The bodysuit blocked the bullets a few times, hence why she was not hurt.

"Not bad!" The Eight-Arm Dragon King, Yoda, said with a smile. With one hand, he smoked his cigarette as his left hand reloaded his gun impatiently.

He had eight guns in total and he shot them in turns. This forced Charlotte to dodge and run tiredly and gave her no opportunity to get close to him. His best move was how he was able to aim all eight guns at once. Though these kind of explosive moves were not sustainable as they came with a period of weakness right after he used the technique.

Charlotte hated that move despite her passion for weapons. It was because Yoda had appeared to be relaxed this whole time, yet he was highly alert. He gave her no window for attack and this made her frustrated. Her guns were different from Yoda’s. She chose not to use them but if she did, he would definitely be shot!

The two fell into a stalemate.

Su Li, who was hiding behind the stairs at the entrance, exhaled in relief.

He invited Garen and the Dragon King over to try and stall the strong opponents. The others could be defeated with his father’s power. Under this plan, there then were only Duskdune Shura and another Royal General. Their capabilities had thus decreased greatly because of his plan.

"As long as Garen can hold off the first Royal General, then we have a chance at winning," Su Lin calculated in his head.

Duskdune Shura was different than other criminal organizations. They had their unique arrogance. Even though they called their murders assassinations, in reality, they killed their targets face to face as a way to let the world know of their horrifying ability of combining weapons with martial arts.

Their group of people think of Duskdune Shura as their leader and fully believed that the combination of martial arts and machine guns was the ultimate path to preserve martial arts.

Also, this was the only path old martial artists could choose, as their physical abilities became drained.

This was what they were trying to prove.

They wanted to prove that traditional martial arts would not be eliminated by time!

Yoda and Charlotte pranced again to find the best opportunity to attack each other.

The two of them were seemingly drawing circles on the roof top, twirling with each other.

The sound of Yoda’s gun firing decreased as time went. It was replaced with the sound of the fast movements of the silencer.

Charlotte was in the same position. The two of them started a silent game and contest.

They belonged to the same generation, and they were their generation’s most powerful top talents. Before, they had never had a face to face battle before. Now, they had the opportunity to battle and decide who lives and who dies.

Chapter 127: Peak 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!

This time it was Charlotte who opened fire.

A cluster of sparks created a small pit on the ground beside Yoda, and gravel was blast into the air, forcing him to dodge the gravel with a somersault.

Charlotte was holding a magenta handgun, but it was larger than an average pistol by one size; smoke was coming out of the muzzle.

Missing her shot, she stored her handgun and disappeared from the spot in a flash.

Two more gunshots were heard. Two small pits instantly appeared where she had just left.

Yoda was sweating from his forehead, but he didn't dare to wipe it.

He had some information on Charlotte. Once part of the four Royal Generals, her most prominent characteristics were her strong intuition and agility. Her flexible body was capable of making various incredible attacks and evasions.

But this wasn't the most troublesome issue.

The most troublesome issue was Charlotte's Secret Martial Art, Ten Fingers Flying Needles.

This was a hidden weapon method which used fine needles as hidden weapons, where a layer of compound toxin had been deftly coated on the needles.

Once a person was abraded by the needle, they would definitely die of poisoning. Even Charlotte didn't have the antidote.

Additionally, the special structure of the flying needles was such that they were silent when thrown.

"Looks like we've really suffered miserably this time…" Yoda murmured in a hushed tone. He tugged on a thread; eight sniper guns gave a slight jerk, and let out subtle clicking sounds, as if something was being adjusted.

This was the true mystery that Yoda, the Dragon King had never revealed. No one alive knew about his true secret. But now he didn't intend to hide anymore.

At the same time, Charlotte, who was standing at the edge of the roof, suddenly felt a numbing sensation on her scalp. Without any time to wonder, she leaned backwards and fell towards the ground.

Wham!

***************

Garen stopped in his tracks and looked into the estate in the distance where the sound had come from.

The gunfire over the estate was gradually dying down. It was obvious that the fighting was coming to an end.

This dull gunshot was entirely different from previous ones; it gave one a strange sense of unease.

Garen scanned his surroundings. On the ground, there were bullet holes and blood everywhere, and the bodies of soldiers and assassins were scattered all over. Some buildings and houses were burning; the fire burned the wooden material within, and let out constant blasts.

The entire elegant estate had now been reduced to a dead zone. The stench of gunpowder and blood filled the air.

Garen stepped over two bodies which had died intertwined in a fight. He frowned slightly.

Although he had experienced many killings and had fresh blood on his hands, he still felt a faint disassociation from reality when he saw this tragic small battlefield.

In his past life, he was merely an ordinary youth, an office worker. Since he arrived in this world, he started pursuing martial arts but had unwittingly reached this juncture.

He was a strong Grandmaster of Combat spawned from special abilities. He was already ranked at the peak level in the martial arts of this world. From an ordinary person to a Grandmaster of Combat capable of killing someone by lifting a finger, this huge leap was something he could never have imagined in the beginning.

Walking in the estate which was quieting down, he could only hear gunshots from time to time in the distance.

Suddenly, Garen saw a body which was severed at the waist by machine gunshots. It was a male soldier. His eyes were wide open as if he had not even figured out what happened.

This type of machine gun was the heavy duty type of machine gun mounted to the ground. Garen scanned the bullet holes on the ground and made a rough estimate.

"If five heavy duty machine guns fired at me all at once, the impact would probably impede me from going forward. Such is the power of firearms…"

He sighed and jogged towards the lawn in the middle of the estate. That was the agreed final meet-up point: Aris, Su Lin, the Dragon King and the others would run there to gather.

It was because the Commissioner of the Special Agent Bureau, Su Lin's father and all the most powerful people were all gathered here.

Not long into his run, he casually handled a few surviving green-shirt assassins along the way. Soon, he arrived at the lawn in the middle.

A large area on the lawn looked like it was dug up by an excavator: the green grass had been replaced by black soil, and the ground was full of traces of explosions.

Garen walked to the edge of the area which had been dug up, crouched down and examined the soil.

"What a fierce fight!" he murmured.

"It is inconceivable for a 50-60 year-old expert from the previous generation to have such a powerful explosive force." He was himself a Grandmaster of Combat. Naturally he could make out traces of the fight from these residual markings. "Compared to that Royal General, they are two different people!"

Clap!

A clapping sound came from the distance.

Without hesitation, Garen stood up and dashed towards the direction of the sound. There was a small isolated chapel with a silver cross on top of its white spire.

He banged the chapel door open. Garen stopped in his tracks; his expression turned.

The large domed hall within the chapel was a mess.

Su Lin's father, Lieutenant Crohn, and a bald man with a big beard, were half-lying in two corners respectively. Both were bloodied, and there were human limbs and organs on the floor everywhere around them.

The red carpet turned a darker shade of blood red.

Apart from the two of them, Aris and a few guards with a terrified expression on their faces were standing guard in front of the two generals. Their hands holding the guns were trembling as they stared fixedly at a black-cloaked figure crouched in the center of the red carpet.

"Someone is here again?"

The black-cloaked figure stood up, his voice hoarse. Some blood slowly dripped from the black leather boots at his feet; apparently, he was injured too.

Garen squinted and was about to speak when suddenly, by the side of a wall not far from him in the chapel, the ground started to open up and three people appeared: it was Su Lin, Yoda, the Dragon King, and the Colonel.

"Duskdune Shura!" Yoda, the Dragon King noticed the black-cloaked figure in the center as soon as he appeared. After taking in his surroundings, his expression turned.

"Yoda, long time no see." Duskdune Shura looked towards the Dragon King; his tone was passive and composed. "What a pity. In the end, you are still standing opposite me."

"After all these years, you should have killed me long ago," the Dragon King curbed his expression and replied coldly. "Too bad you didn't."

"Where's Charlotte?" Duskdune Shura asked all of a sudden.

"She fled after being injured by me. She won't return to support you anytime soon. Yoda gave a tug, and eight heavy duty sniper rifles spread out into the shape of a fan and aimed at Duskdune Shura and his surrounding area.

"At this point in the battle, the outcome has been determined." Duskdune Shura shifted his gaze to Lieutenant Crohn who was leaning on a corner wall. "Hand it to me, Lieutenant Crohn."

"I didn't expect your gun skills to be as terrifying as your martial arts skills. You truly live up to being the leader of the strongest assassin organization," Crohn sneered. "You can have it, but it's not here. It's somewhere else a distance away from here."

"My martial arts has reached a maximum limit," Duskdune Shura calmly said. "No martial arts expert in the world is a match for me. Even Palosa is stagnant at my current level."

He spoke calmly, with a domineering tone that seemed to say 'who else but me'.

"I have reached an extraordinary stage, but unfortunately…I'm still unable to resist the tide of time." He held his head up high, and finally removed the hood of his black cloak.

This was a thin, white-bearded old man. All his hair had turned white, his eyebrows too. The strangest part was, even his pupils were white!

His face was wrinkly like the bark of an old tree. It was obvious that he was past his prime; he was at least 70 to 80 years old.

"Golden Sword Throne, the key to unlocking a legendary higher level of martial arts. It's now my only hope." Duskdune Shura gazed calmly at Crohn. "I am almost 80 years old. I don't have any more time to 'find my path'."

"Why are you still talking?" Garen cut him short, then stepped forward and said, "Win or lose, we'll have to fight to know!"

Upon finishing his sentence, he dashed towards the old man and stomped hard on the ground with a Step Form.

The whole chapel reverberated; the gigantic sound wave threatened to crumble the building.

Everyone's eardrums sensed a deafening sound, a soft, incessant buzzing. It was the effect of temporary deafness.

Garen was seen sprinting towards Duskdune Shura, and the vibration of air around him sounded faintly like the roar of a mammoth. When he raised his palm to strike downwards, a whirring sound like an elephant flinging its nose could vaguely be heard.

When he entered, Garen had already sensed a powerful, invisible aura faintly suppressing the entire chapel. The shadow of a lion crouched within Duskdune Shura. It was a spiritual shadow formed from strong Bravery. If Duskdune Shura didn't let it out, an average martial arts practitioner would be unaware of the situation.

But Garen sensed it as soon as he entered the chapel. This person's Bravery was almost on par with his own. It was impressive that, being almost 80, he had managed to maintain such a strong Bravery.

This aura was much stronger than Andrela's. It was comparable to his current form.

"Junior! You think you can take advantage of my injury?" Duskdune Shura sneered and turned around. "It's delusional for a fresh Grandmaster of Combat to think he can challenge an elder. How reckless!"

His brought his hands together and placed them on the side of Garen's palm striking at him and gently hit it.

Clap!

Garen was stunned. That knife-like strike contained most of his strength. It was actually deflected by his opponent with a gentle tap.

Bang!

A bullet hole appeared by the side of Duskdune Shura's feet; he managed to easily evade it by an inch.

This 80 year-old man reached a palm out at a moderate pace, but it was unavoidable. It rattled Garen's Shot Form on his other arm, and tapped his chest.

"Lock!" he shouted in a low voice.

Garen's body seemed like it was struck by lightning, and instantly froze in place.

He felt as though his chest had stiffened all of a sudden, and didn't respond to his actions. It was as if flesh and blood had been transformed into cold, hard stone.

"Young man, you don't win in martial arts by relying solely on strength."

Duskdune Shura took a step backwards; his face was calm.

"Talk to me when you actually win!" Garen gave a cunning laugh. His body suddenly inflated; he grew from 1.7 meters to 1.9 meters.

Shot! Step! Swing!

All three forms combined!

Garen Shot his right elbow out and stepped with his feet; the ground shook slightly. His arm transformed into an arc, and his Shot Form was converted into Swing Form in an instant.

Chapter 128: Peak 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This elbow strike combined the explosive forces of both Shot Form and Step Form, coupled with the huge range of attack and rotational force of Swing Form. It was a powerful blow, and Garen struck with all his might.

Even an armored tank would be instantly wrecked.

The strong gust from the force blew against Duskdune Shura's beard. His expression didn’t change. He stretched both palms out and—although it seemed slow, it was in reality, extremely fast—tapped the underside of Garen's elbows.

Tap tap! Two crisp sounds were heard. Apparently, his knuckles dabbed at the underside of Garen's elbow twice.

The originally violent and strong elbow strike was instantly elevated. It deviated from its original trajectory and flew over Duskdune Shura's head.

Bang!

Another palm hit Garen's chest.

Garen took two steps back, and a strange expression was on his face. He looked at Duskdune Shura's methods and recalled the numerous unique small sects in his past life on Earth.

"You're using Gentle Fist?"

"Gentle Fist? I guess you could call it that." Duskdune Shura calmly nodded. "This phrase is a good summary of it. To be able to become a Grandmaster of Combat at such a young age, it must not be by chance."

He stood with his hands behind his back.

"This is Spiritual Hoop Fist of my own invention. It's the most appropriate counter against Body Hardening Technique experts like you who only know how to use brute force."

Garen touched his chest. The stiff tension that he had relieved by inflating his body with the explosive Body Hardening Technique had now re-emerged.

His chest felt frigid; it seemed to have been drained of sensation again.

"It looks like I can't deal with you without using some real skills."

Garen took a deep breath. His body vibrated suddenly and started inflating again.

He grew from 190cm to 245cm!

He was now two heads taller than Duskdune Shura. Facing each other, the contrast was stark, like an adult and a child.

"The peak of Body Hardening Technique…" Duskdune Shura's expression changed slightly. "You…" He had barely started his sentence when he saw Garen's palm reaching over to grab him. Like a fan coming down at him overhead, the hand blocked most of the light from above. He hurriedly raised his arms to block.

Wham!

This muffled sound made everyone in the chapel dizzy.

Su Lin stood with his sister and father. All of them huddled close and were protected by the soldiers, colonels, and a few military officers.

When they saw Garen frighteningly expand to twice his original size, they were instantly stunned.

"So… so powerful!" Aris covered her mouth and gave a low cry. She didn't expect Garen—who merely looked quite buff—to suddenly transform into such a terrifying size. He swiped at the skinny old man like an eagle preying on a chick. This was too stark a visual contrast.

Aris could already visualize Garen smashing the old man with a palm.

"The peak of Body Hardening Technique?" Crohn exchanged looks with his big-bearded old partner, and they both saw a trace of shock in the other's eyes. They had trained in some traditional martial arts before, but never imagined that martial arts actually had a Body Hardening Technique with such a terrifying effect. Just by the look of his size, they could guess the intensity of strength of his palm strike now.

"It seems that we have underestimated traditional martial arts before. In close combat, the efficacy of martial arts could match elite gun skills!" The thought flashed through Crohn's mind.

Su Lin stood stunned by his sister's side; he felt a strong sense of impact at this sight. Even though he had heard rumors about Garen previously, it wasn't as shocking as personally witnessing it.

But these weren't even the main reasons he was stunned.

The main reason was that Duskdune Shura—by raising his arms in defense—had managed to firmly block the palm strike!

After the loud muffled sound, Duskdune Shura's legs had sunk into the cement floor, almost knee-deep.

Growl! Roar!

The sounds of a mammoth growling and a lion roaring mashed together and reverberated ferociously.

As a martial arts practitioner, Su Lin could clearly see that in the duel between Garen and Duskdune Shura the aura on both of them fiercely entangled and clashed like a mammoth and a lion.

A snap was heard, and both of them were instantly separated.

Duskdune Shura pulled himself out of the ground, leaped a few steps backward, and stood firm. Now, there was shock and doubt in his eyes when he looked at Garen.

"What kind of Body Hardening Technique is this? I have seen all the prevalent Body Hardening Techniques, but I've never encountered yours!"

"White Cloud Gate, Mammoth Secret Technique!" Garen wasn't exactly comfortable either. The moment he struck at his opponent's arms, the terrifying counter-vibration force generated by his opponent in that instance had unsettled his Qi and blood; he felt a faint sense of fatigue.

All Grandmasters of Combat who were Elite Fist Artists grasped the essential skill of close combat: counter-Vibration. It was obvious that his opponent's counter-Vibration was one league above his own.

Clang!

A bell rang outside the chapel.

Duskdune Shura's face sank.

"Hand it over! Otherwise, be prepared to die!" He suddenly turned to stare at Crohn who was heavily guarded. His terrifying Bravery started to expand and superseded Garen's in an instant; it heavily suppressed Crohn and the rest.

Crohn looked grim. He scanned the room and deduced that the situation wasn't going in his favor. Without hesitation, he proposed. "Duskdune Shura, with your martial art skills, there is no need for you to endanger yourself in battles like these every day. Why don't you join the Special Agent Bureau? The Confederation will soon carry out a reorganization of the special experts. By then, I'll be the first minister of the Special Agent Department. If you join us, I can promise you a position as the deputy minister!"

Duskdune Shura threw a look of disdain at him, like a tiger staring at a pig, and then utterly ignored the raging Crohn.

"Time is running out, I need to finish this quickly!" His gaze fell on Garen who was blocking the exit, and he could sense Yoda was hiding in the dark. Yoda, with his guns loaded, had been waiting for the right timing. Compared to opening fire, this gave Duskdune Shura a stronger sense of restraint and threat.

"I can't believe I actually encountered someone with the peak of Body Hardening Technique here! Unfortunately, I'm running out of time." Duskdune Shura looked at Garen, a trace of admiration flashed across his eyes. "Move aside, young man. I have no intention of killing you!"

Garen was now experiencing what the Pink Pupil Royal General felt. His opponent's aura was like the ocean, encapsulating his own Bravery in waves. His aura was restricted to his own body. He restrained his aura and monitored Duskdune Shura's every move as he felt like he was a flying insect, stuck on a spider web.

He had a bad feeling about the situation.

The Mammoth Secret Technique was a supreme Body Hardening Technique fortified by layering the skin hardening on one level, and Qi and blood stabilizing the other; despite the layered fortifications, his opponent completely disregarded it.

"You are indeed a top martial arts expert of the previous generation. But you're still not good enough to have me move aside!"

He had always wanted to see what the next level of martial arts looked like. Now that it was in front of him, naturally he refused to retreat. Moreover, he had heard rumors about a link between Duskdune Shura and the Immortal Palace Alliance; it was impossible that he would let this opportunity slip.

Duskdune Shura narrowed his eyes. A hint of danger emanated from him.

Clang!

The strike of a bell could again be heard coming from outside.

Duskdune Shura was startled. At this moment, thunderous gunfire broke out.

It was Yoda!

Eight sniper rifles simultaneously fired, all aimed at the positions that Duskdune Shura could possibly dodge towards.

Suddenly, Duskdune Shura's body shortened. His entire body size had shrunk by one fold, turning him into a dwarf. He gave a muffled cry; obviously, he had been injured.

"You're gonna pay!" With a roar, Duskdune Shura swung an arm out; there was a purple handgun in his hand and he started firing it.

Bang!

Yoda, who was concealed in the distance, let out a cry of pain. His right shoulder was hit and the wound was bleeding.

At this moment, Garen stomped his foot and started spinning his arms.

Serial Swing Form!

"The first Dragon Gate!"

At the same time, Duskdune Shura gave a low growl as his entire body inflated by a few folds of his original girth. There was a murderous look in his eyes. He pointed a finger and stabbed it towards Garen's Swing Form arms.

He intended to fight brute force with brute force!

Then another gunshot was heard.

Yoda had fired another shot while struggling.

Duskdune Shura was late to react. He was in the midst of a duel with Garen so he could not evade in time. Suddenly, his body had swelled to quadruple its original girth! He had transformed into the body of a muscular and fit man, only slightly smaller than Garen; he too had attained the peak of Body Hardening Technique!

Bang!

Garen felt a pain in his arm and saw the murderous look in Duskdune Shura's eyes as the latter leaned in and gently struck his chest with a palm. That last shot had no effect on him whatsoever.

"The second Dragon Gate!"

Wham!

Duskdune Shura struck Garen in the chest with his palm and then, with a swivel, appeared behind Garen.

"The third Dragon Gate!"

A backhand slap hit Garen on his left shoulder blade with a whack.

The three palm strikes seemed heavy, but Garen didn't seem to budge even the slightest after being struck consecutively.

What the others couldn't see was that Garen's whole body felt like it had been frozen by something; he couldn't move a muscle, and the Qi and blood in his veins seemed to be blocked and couldn't flow freely.

His heart pounded fiercely; his body seemed to tremble with each heartbeat. An intense dullness, palpitations, and nausea—all these negative states—surged towards him in that instant. His heart felt like it could explode at any moment.

He staggered a little and was almost unable to stand firmly.

"The last palm: the fourth Dragon Gate!" Duskdune Shura coldly raised his right palm, and struck hard towards Garen's forehead; Garen stumbled and evaded it awkwardly.

Bang!

Another gunshot.

Duskdune Shura's expression changed slightly. He retracted his hand and took a step forward.

A large amount of cement slag sputtered from the ground behind him; he whacked it with one hand and it instantly transformed into a secret weapon and enveloped towards Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King in the shadows.

Yoda didn't manage to react in time. All he could do was block with a rifle in front of his body. He was injured in a few spots, but fortunately, his vital parts were unharmed.

"Seven Dragon Gates! Duskdune Shura… You've finally…managed to attain it!" He watched with his bloodshot eyes as Duskdune Shura darted out of the chapel in a few leaps. Unable to hold it in any longer, he covered his mouth and coughed up mouthfuls of fresh blood, which flowed through his fingers.

Garen fell to the ground embarrassingly. He wanted to stand up, but couldn't exert any considerable amount of strength.

"If I had encountered this person alone, I would have been dead!" In that moment, he could still calmly analyze his and his opponent's true strength.

He supported himself up and half-knelt on the ground. His gaze tracked Duskdune Shura as the latter darted out the door.

"Is this the true strength of a martial arts practitioner at his peak? He exhibits such a powerful true strength even though he is pushing 80!" He thought he had reached the peak of a martial arts practitioner; he couldn't believe he just encountered a supreme expert like Duskdune Shura who was far stronger than he was.

When he and Yoda arrived, Duskdune Shura had defeated two generals from the Special Agent Bureau and massacred a large number of siege troops; he had obviously been injured. Afterward, he dueled with Garen—using brute force—and was hit twice by Yoda's opportune shots.

Even so, he still managed to apply Explosive Force in the end and almost killed Garen. Moreover, he seemed like he was rushing off somewhere. Otherwise, everyone here would probably have died!

Duskdune Shura didn't even use his full force, and it was likely that he was only slightly injured.

Garen's heart was filled with an inexplicable sorrow.

Duskdune Shura was also a Grandmaster of Combat with peak Body Hardening Technique like him, and in fact, was even more skilled!

"If he had applied Explosive Force earlier, and we dueled in our peak states… I would have been killed in an instant…" Garen felt bitter about it, but more than anything, he was excited!

Chapter 129: Notes 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clang!

The strike of a bell could again be heard coming from outside.

Duskdune Shura's figure finally disappeared into the distance.

At the same time, the assassins in the estate quickly retreated too. Obviously, Duskdune Shura did not intend to go all out against the Yalu Confederation. That was the reason they halted their attack right at the moment when they had the absolute advantage and did not kill the two generals.

With some difficulty, Garen stood up. After a while, his strong physical constitution and Body Hardening Technique had an obvious effect—he was recovering much faster than the others.

He turned to look at everyone else inside the chapel.

Some soldiers who were unharmed were carefully placing the two generals on stretchers. Aris and Su Lin were crouched beside the Eight Arm Dragon King. Yoda's injury was extremely horrifying: his shoulder was directly punched through, leaving a fist-sized wound. The bones and flesh within had all become minced meat. At this moment, his face was pale as he leaned on the wall and allowed the medical staff to deal with his injuries and stop the bleeding. When he realized Garen was looking over at him, he was actually still in the mood to stare back.

"What are you looking at? I'm not dead yet!"

Aris hurried over to Garen's side. At the sight of Garen's chest—which had been injured in the duel—she was tempted to reach and touch it but didn't dare to in case it would hurt him.

With tears in her eyes, she asked worriedly, "Are you…okay?"

"It's nothing. My true strength is much stronger than a certain old man in denial." Garen directed a cold sneer at the Eight Arm Dragon King.

He couldn't stand someone Yoda. It was obvious that Yoda's true strength wasn't up to scratch and he was old, but he still thought he could be arrogant like when he was young. He genuinely believed himself to be the best in the world.

Combined with the fact that his martial arts attainment was terrible, but he still managed to be on par with Garen by relying on firearms, this irritated Garen.

"Do you want to die?!" Yoda was obviously agitated: he quickly stood up and rolled his sleeves.

"Come on! I'll stand in place for you to hit me. If you can injure me without guns, you win!" Garen replied.

"You! Cough cough…" Yoda was angered to the point that he almost vomited blood. "You bastard!"

"Alright, alright. Let's not say anything harsh." Su Lin hurriedly stood in between them. He looked frustrated.

"Both of you are at the top of your field, there's no reason to break the peace just because of a little spat," the purple-bearded bald man on the stretcher spoke. "I have a humble suggestion, why don't the both of you…"

"Forget it. I would never join the Special Agent Bureau. It's easier to be alone and free," Yoda rejected instantly.

"You're not giving it any further consideration? Joining the national force is better than going it alone…"

"No, I don't. To each their own." Yoda shook his head without hesitation.

The purple-bearded man and Lieutenant General Crohn were disappointed as they exchanged a look.

Compared to Garen who directly confronted Duskdune Shura, they actually respected the Eight Arm Dragon King, Yoda more. Talents like Yoda are able to multiply their combative efficacy in proportion to the increase in the power of firearms. Even merely by controlling guns now, he had such great power. If he used more powerful firearms on the battlefield, it would be unimaginable. It would almost affect a small-scale war.

Whereas talents like Garen, no matter how powerful, the most he could do was engage in special combat, assassinate, or be the vanguard of a guerilla attack from behind the enemy. He could not compare to the magnified version of the Dragon King, Yoda. But regardless, courting such talent was still necessary.

The two men halted the people who were carrying their stretchers, and their gaze fell upon Garen who was standing by the wall at the entrance.

"So what about Mr Garen right here? Are you interested in joining the new Special Agents Bureau to be established?" The purple-bearded man knew that he had made Garen feel left out earlier, and started to compensate for it. "If you are willing to join, arranging a deputy minister position for you would not be a problem."

"My apologies, I am not in pursuit of such things." Garen shook his head. His face was equally pale. After being hit consecutively by Duskdune Shura, he still felt that his body had not fully recovered its smooth flow of Qi and blood.

"Is that so?" Crohn shook his head with slight disappointment. "Fine, then. Since it is so, we won't force the issue. Both of you have been heavily injured, you will need to recuperate. The estate will be under heavy security 24 hours a day from here on out. Just tell me if you have any requests with regards to safety or medicines."

He was aware that many martial art practitioners had their own method of healing which was more effective than common methods, but it required different drugs than what an average person would use.

These failed invitations were not unexpected to them either. Shifting the point of view from their actual willingness to join the government to the perspective of playing hard-to-get, even if they had intentions to join, they would not agree so quickly either.

Anyway, since both of them were friends invited over by Su Lin, even if they were unwilling to join, they would be convenient to contact in future. The two of them could be considered a strength that sided with them.

After the fierce battle, a large number of support troops and medics arrived and started to clear the battlefield in an orderly manner.

The fighting within the estate merely lasted for less than twenty minutes, but the number of casualties had reached hundreds. There were corpses and body parts everywhere on the ground and blood flowed downstream. Under the hot sun, some areas had already attracted buzzing flies.

The supporting troops which had rushed over were nervous at the sight of the battlefield. Fortunately the General was safe; otherwise, this would have been the biggest scandal since the founding of the Yalu Confederation.

Two generals from the Special Agents Bureau responsible for special force talents and elites forced into a crushing defeat by an international assassin organization and killed in battle.

This would deal a fatal blow to the reputation of the Confederation.

It was akin to a police chief being burgled in his own home.

If the rumor spread internationally, the true strength of the Confederation would naturally be despised by other countries. They might even see the Confederation as a weak force and send troops over to cause trouble. At that point, even if it wasn't a weak force, it would still be reduced to one.

Supported by two medics, Garen was no longer tense and gradually relaxed.

Just as he relaxed, he felt dizzy; fatigue poured into his head like a tide.

"Give me a quiet room. I want to rest," he said softly.

"No problem," without waiting for Su Lin to reply, Aris spoke first.

Garen felt that even his hearing was muffled, and he couldn't hear clearly. He didn't know which martial art Duskdune Shura's fist strike belonged to, but he was in a very bad state right now, and he desperately needed to recuperate.

It was his first time experiencing fatigue.

This was unimaginable. In past combats, regardless of the opponent—even an expert Grandmaster of Combat like Andrela—he could still maintain an unwavering spirit, and almost couldn't feel the limit of his endurance.

But now he felt extremely tired.

His heard Aris saying something, but couldn’t clearly make it out. He barely managed to maintain a clear consciousness while allowing a few people to support him. He was carried on a stretcher to a room, where he finally fell into a deep sleep.

*********

An unknown amount of time passed.

Garen slowly came to.

He opened his eyes. He was lying on a large round bed surrounded by pure white plush, as if he was lying in countless white feathers.

The ceiling was covered in pastel purple wallpaper with flowers and organic patterns engraved along the edges; it was exquisite.

He took a deep breath. The bed was filled with a subtle fragrance which smelled floral, but was more like the smell of a woman's body.

Garen turned to look at the bedside. Sitting on a curved chair to the right of the bed was a beautiful and elegant girl with purple hair. Her long purple hair was tied into a ponytail and her fringe was combed to a side. She exuded a combined sense of innocence and charm.

This girl was Su Lin's sister, Aris.

She seemed very tired: she had dozed off with her head tilted to one side. This was inconsistent with her usual elegant image, but it gave Garen a more authentic sense of intimacy.

In addition to Aris, there was a basin of clean water for freshening up on the purple bedside table with a black towel soaking inside.

"You're awake?" In a daze, Aris saw Garen open his eyes. She hurriedly stood up. "How are you feeling? Master Garen?" she asked nervously.

"It’s alright. I can condition myself." Garen felt that his lower body had recovered by a great deal. "That fist strike by Duskdune Shura was likely a type of martial art with temporary effects. Coupled with my strong Physique, I should be fine now."

He supported himself up and leaned against the headboard.

"This is…?" Garen had just realized that the layout of this room was very gentle and delicate, full of floral patterns and designs. A subtle fragrance filled the room. The most conspicuous thing was a pink sofa in a corner of the room. It was shaped into a pink hippo taller than an average person. The back of the hippo was the backrest. It looked naïve, and was extremely cute.

"This is my room." Aris gave a weak smile. "All the rooms are filled with injured soldiers, so I decided to let you rest in my room. You don't mind, do you?"

"Of course not." Garen paused, then smiled. He vaguely felt that, after this battle, Aris's attitude towards him seemed different.

He turned to look out the window. It was bright outside; a faint bluish-white ray shone on the windowsill.

"Can I get a glass of water?" Garen was parched.

"Of course." Aris hurriedly poured a glass of water from a delicate purple flask and handed it to Garen.

After two full glasses of warm water, Garen gradually felt relieved.

"What's the situation now?"

"It's fine. The estate is managed by my brother now. The Parliament is furious about this terror attack, so now this place has been stationed with thousands of soldiers inside and out. Three generals are rushing over too, to guarantee our safety, and to track the whereabouts of the terrorists."

She paused for a moment, her beautiful eyes looking elegantly into Garen's.

"We really owe you a huge debt of gratitude this time, Master Garen. Without you, I'm afraid we would have been in deep trouble."

"Su Lin helped me out with a serious issue before. Don't mention it." Garen waved a hand.

"That's right. Father says, if you wake up and feel fine, to request your presence at the conference room. There's an urgent matter. It's about the Golden Sword Throne."

"The Golden Sword Throne?" Garen narrowed his eyes. "This is what Duskdune Shura is after, isn't it?"

"That's right. Father says he will reveal everything. Duskdune Shura's attack means that this isn't a secret anymore."

"Alright then. I'll have to recuperate for a while." Garen nodded.

"I'll head out and leave you to it." Aris was very considerate and took her leave. She understood that tough martial arts practitioners didn't like to be disturbed when they were recuperating.

Garen nodded. After seeing Aris leave and close the door behind her, he slowly shut his eyes.

The Attributes Pane in his lower field of vision was unchanged and maintained its original stats.

'Strength 2.64; Agility 1.22; Physical quality 2.09; Intelligence 1.53; Potential 98%'

Chapter 130: Notes 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"There's just an average increase of 0.01 in Attributes. I still need 2% more to enhance my Potential, just short by a little. Too bad there aren't any Antiques of Tragedy for me to absorb Potential. Antiques of Tragedy… What secret lies within these objects?" He had been unable to figure out what the Potential within Antiques of Tragedy actually was. He merely speculated that the more an antique was associated with a dangerous and bloody ancient legend, the more Potential it contained.

"It's unfortunate. If only the ring in uncle's hands was stronger, I could wear it for a few months to top up that final 2%. But if it were stronger, there would probably be problems before uncle could wait for me to realize it." The level of the ring was too low; it was essentially ineffective for him. He would probably have to wear it for a few years before there was any effect. He might as well approach the issue through Golden Hoop.

"I wonder if this Golden Sword Throne contains Potential. If an antique with a widespread legend could be an Antique of Tragedy, why were the similar antiques that I later found completely useless? Is it that only objects which are able to bring the collector misfortune contain Potential?"

"Forget it, I shouldn't think so much. This matter is unfinished. I will know when the time comes."

He stopped thinking further, and looked at the current Skills Pane.

——Secret Martial Art——

Mammoth Mutation: Explosive (Top level), Skin Hardening Level One (Iron Body), Blood Qi Stabilization (Boulder Martial Art).

Dark Iron Palm: Accumulation has not reached rudimentary level (accumulation of physical toxins Level Two)

Firestream Fist: Weak progress (Level Four)

"Duskdune Shura should have no idea that I killed a Royal General, otherwise he wouldn't have talked so much nonsense in the end, and would have just ended me directly. I've escaped this time, but the next encounter would be troublesome."

"Now that I'm caught up in this whirlpool of trouble, I can't leave to find low-level Secret Martial Arts. But even though I can't, that doesn't mean Su Lin can't! I could maybe seek his help in finding some low-level Secret Martial Arts for me to train in."

The ones most valuable to him were those inferior Secret Martial Arts that required little external criteria. Generally, for middle- or high-grade Secret Martial Arts, the higher the level, the more powerful it was, the less restriction it posed, the more it required external conditions to supplement it. Those would be unfavorable to his training.

He got out of bed and put on the prepared clothes by the bed. Garen suddenly saw, at the bottom of the bed, the martial arts notebook that he had previously found on the body of the Pink Pupil Royal General. He picked it up to browse.

On it were notes about the confusions the Pink Pupil Royal General faced in his martial arts training and the eventual solutions that he came up with. It was like someone recording their own difficulties, then focused their energies to conquer them.

Initially, Garen was merely browsing casually. He didn't expect to be unwittingly absorbed in it.

Much of the notes recorded some unexpected deficiencies and difficulties of martial arts. Garen had encountered many of them and had yet to encounter many more. Most of them contained solutions on the back.

It was then that Garen realized the value of this notebook. Because of his lowly origins from a low-level small sect, a lot of his martial arts experience had been unable to reach a certain height. This notebook could coincidentally make up for a portion of his deficiencies.

This also made him realize why his physical qualities and Attributes hadn't had much progress after all this while.

In other words, if it were not for his inherent special ability maintaining the solidification of his physical qualities, maybe he would have experienced a decline in quality long ago.

"Although its usefulness for me isn't that great, it would be very accessible and helpful for the average person learning martial arts." Garen looked at the book satisfactorily. This was an unexpected gain.

Unintentionally, he turned to a page about difficulties in Secret Martial Art training.

'Attempt to train in cumulative low-level Secret Martial Art, failed, extremely poor progress! Why?' This was a problem faced by the Pink Pupil Royal General. It was exactly what Garen was facing.

He started to look more serious.

He gently turned to the next page. The line of words recorded on it initially made Garen's heart skip a beat, but when he instantly saw the lines underneath; his lips couldn't help but curve upwards slightly.

Dense black wordings were clearly recorded on the pale yellow paper.

'Cumulative low-level Secret Martial Arts are mostly incomplete. Here I have collated the deficiencies of some common Secret Martial Arts.'

'1. Dagger Fist: Boil safflower petals in water and apply the solution to both hands. Method identical to previous medication.'

'2. Buzzbeck Arc Sword Skills: Need to forge a special hilt for continuous practice. The hilt design is as follows…'

'3. Odin Steel Fist: Need to use spiked board together with the medication for Level One Fist Arts in training.'

The more Garen read, the more he felt satisfied. Not for the deficiencies of the many Secret Martial Arts that he had never heard of, but because he actually found the practicing deficiencies for the two low-level Secret Martial Arts he was training in: Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm.

'31. Dark Iron Palm: Need to be upside down when practicing.' After reading this short line of content on the deficiency, Garen searched his memory and recalled the method of training for Dark Iron Palm, and was instantly enlightened.

Those training methods that seemed strange, if practiced upside down, would instantly make sense from the perspective of martial arts concepts.

He turned a page, and read on.

'38. Firestream Fist: A Secret Martial Art that is relatively more time-consuming. Practice needs to be complemented with hot iron sand. Strike and stab fists into a basin of iron sand in the initial stage, which can later be replaced with real charcoals. See illustration for specific training method.' On the back were a few clearly drawn illustrations for practice methods and stages. It covered every stage of practice for Firestream Fist.

Garen could not help but give a low laugh.

"Finally, I am able to complete these two low-level secret Martial Arts even if I don't go to Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate!" This bounty eased the depressed mood he had experienced from his injury and defeat.

"Practicing upside down, hehe, I'd like to give it a try." Garen was impatient to give it a go immediately. His sudden excitement caused him to feel a dull sensation in his chest.

"I have not recovered yet. Duskdune Shura is powerful indeed. Such a light strike has caused me prolonged negative effects." A chill ran through Garen's heart. He recalled Duskdune Shura's tactics and his high spirits were calmed once again.

Knock knock knock.

"Mr Garen, Master requests your presence in the conference room. Breakfast will be served there too."

"Alright," Garen replied aloud. He quickly straightened his clothes and glanced at himself in the mirror.

His strong, fair body was evenly toned and muscular. There wasn't the slightest flabbiness and no muscles seemed overly uncoordinated.

His purple hair was somewhat long and almost covered his eyes. It draped at his shoulders, and seemed slightly frizzy. The faint dark red tone gave others a sense of cool toughness.

Wow.

He put on a black shirt and a white suit, and allowed his shoulder-length hair to hang freely. Garen tugged the shirt collar and looked at himself in the mirror.

The man in the mirror gave off a sense of wildness, as well as a trace of cool and strength. His chin was slightly lifted. He could give others a strong sense of fear and oppression without saying a word.

"Unconsciously, I have become like this…" Garen swept aside the hair covering his vision.

He gently touched his chest; there was still a slight numbness.

"Duskdune Shura…"

He stowed the notebook, turned, and left through the door.

*****************

Estate Conference Room

A yellow boardroom-style table was placed in the middle of a small room with pale yellow tones, with a few black leather chairs surrounding it.

Above the table, a square-ish lamp hung from a black wire, emitting a soft, yellow light.

Su Lin and his father, Lieutenant Crohn sat in the main seats by the curtains. They were clad in black suits, slowly sipping coffees.

The Dragon King, Yoda sat with Su Lin. He looked calm, and was casually drinking coffee too.

A gloomy-looking old lady sat alone at the other end. This old lady was also wearing a military uniform. The golden badge on her shoulder shone with three silver stars and a pair of crossed swords. It was the symbol for lieutenants.

"Apologies, I am late." At the opened door, Garen slowed his pace and entered. He glanced at everyone inside, then sat directly beside Su Lin.

"No worries. Your injuries are not light." Crohn gave Garen a friendly smile. In that moment, after a suitable change of attire, Garen's temperament perfectly embodied his powerful true strength and Bravery.

Su Lin and Yoda looked at Garen, shocked. After the battle with Duskdune Shura, Garen's initial strong Bravery had become more restrained, and the impression he gave now was akin to a volcano hidden beneath the seabed. It wasn't like before, where the sight of him would be associated with strength, power, and pulverization!

He was indeed worthy of being deemed a martial arts expert capable of directly countering Duskdune Shura in a short amount of time.

Crohn was silently impressed. He pointed at the white-haired old woman sitting alone.

"Allow me to introduce. This is the person in charge of the Special Response Unit newly established by the Confederation, Lieutenant Lenny. "

The old woman, Lenny, nodded dully at the three of them, not saying a word.

"Lieutenant Lenny is the main person in charge of tracking and following-up on this terrorist attack. She is interested in your understanding of the situation, and hopes that you can provide her with some information on Duskdune Shura. Of course, I too will reveal the source of conflict between myself and Duskdune Shura."

"No problem," Su Lin was the first to respond.

"I have some reservations about matters related to my personal privacy, but rest assured there will not be any impact on this incident," Yoda answered lazily.

"I have no opinion either." Garen nodded.

Crohn nodded in satisfaction.

"In that case, let me start."

He gestured for the guards to shut the door, then glanced around the room once.

"Actually, no one knows what the essence of the Golden Sword Throne is apart from its maker, including myself, its owner."

He broke off, then continued.

"When I went to the ruins of Nabudas Empire on the Fivestar Continent, I acquired a golden ornament from the chief of the indigenous tribe there. It looked like a sword pierced into a throne-like ancient stone. It is merely the size of a palm, almost like a pen holder. I didn't expect it to be the legendary mysterious Golden Sword Throne."

"Fivestar Continent is different from Stonecliff Continent where we are at, as well as Azure Continent. There are many backwards and ancient areas there, so it's not surprising that they had a golden ornament like that. How do you know that the ornament is the Golden Sword Throne?" Lieutenant Lenny asked.

"Hold on. Can you explain what the effects of the Golden Sword Throne are, specifically?"

"This was confirmed by my daughter, and also by Duskdune Shura. As to its effects, it is said that the secret to the inheritance of an ancient and powerful martial art is hidden within. It has also been said that it was an object used by medieval warlocks to curse souls. There are also rumors that the Golden Sword Throne is the key to a mysterious ruin, and the person who accesses the ruin will obtain a gift from the devil. These are all different words telling the same story. I, too, am actually unsure of its true secret," Crohn explained. "Originally, I wasn't too concerned about it, and viewed it as a nice collectible. I didn't expect Duskdune Shura to contact me about trading for it. You must understand, terrorist organizations like Duskdune Shura's, if able to be eliminated, would be a fortunate event for the Confederation, and for the three continents, so…"

"So you used it as bait and mobilized the entire Special Agents Bureau, all to capture Duskdune Shura. What you didn't expect was for the opponent to be too strong, resulting in our current situation?" Yoda interjected.

"Indeed. My estimates were miscalculated, causing such a big casualty. It is indeed my responsibility," Crohn let out a long sigh.

"Even the entire Special Agents Bureau couldn't stop Duskdune Shura. If not for your son, Su Lin soliciting the help of two elite experts, I'm afraid you would have been killed in a miserable defeat," Lenny said casually.

"I am miserable enough." Crohn shrugged helplessly. "The reason I invited you all here, is mainly because we have discovered the location of the ruins where Duskdune Shura is headed. We are hoping that you would assist our military forces in killing the leader of this terrorist organization. Even though we are reluctant, we still have to admit that perhaps only with Garen and Mr Yoda, combined with the military, can there be a chance in suppressing Duskdune Shura."

Chapter 131: Practice 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Yoda coughed twice.

"I won't be able to make it. The injury on my shoulder would take a few months to heal."

"I have been remiss in my considerations," Crohn nodded to show that he understood.

Garen contemplated for a while.

"I need to recuperate too. I can't fight immediately. Even if I did, I would be no match for Duskdune Shura. Although I'm unwilling to admit it, Duskdune Shura's martial arts have reached a peak level."

The atmosphere in the room was temporarily subdued.

Crohn sighed. He gestured for the soldiers to open the doors. Several maids entered to serve breakfast: a type of pale blue baguette paired with some apple slices, large chunks of pineapple, and a cup of unknown red drink which was fizzing.

Everyone didn't speak much. They just silently started having breakfast. Only the sound of knives clashing with forks could be heard from time to time.

Garen ate silently, while at the same time carefully estimating Duskdune Shura's true strength, as well as the time he needed to recover from his injuries.

"Duskdune Shura painstakingly schemed to get a hold of the Golden Sword Throne, it's apparent he has a certain level of confidence in succeeding. I wonder how much any of you knew about Duskdune Shura before?" Crohn asked in a hushed tone.

Garen was the first to shake his head, expressing ignorance.

Su Lin shook his head too. He merely shifted his gaze towards Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King.

Yoda had thick bandages on his shoulder. He swiftly reached for the food on the table with one hand and stuffed it in his mouth.

"Don't look at me. I'm not too clear about it either. Duskdune Shura and I are experts of the same generation. This organization was something he joined or established later, I've just heard about it for a long time."

Even though they knew his words were not entirely reliable—it wasn't that he didn't know, he was merely reluctant to reveal what he knew—Su Lin and the rest didn't force the issue.

Garen finished the drink in one gulp, and gently put down the cup.

"In fact, regardless of what motives Duskdune Shura harbors, regardless of what ruins he's gone to, it's impossible that he doesn't reappear. When he emerges from the ruins, we'll know what he really wants. What we need to do now is figure out how to deal with him. Previously, we had so many people but were still defeated. If we had to do it again, based on the true strength and power we have here, do you think we would actually be able to hold him off?"

Upon hearing Garen's words, everyone fell silent.

Only Lieutenant Lenny who had just joined them frowned.

Garen shook his head.

"I'm just a martial arts practitioner; I don't want to get too involved. Whenever you come up with a plan to deal with Duskdune Shura, Su Lin, you just tell me. I need to go down to recuperate now. Regardless of what the plan is, now everyone is injured, and won't be good for anything if we don't recover. Excuse me."

He stood up, turned around and left through the door.

Walking through the red-carpeted corridor with soldiers standing guard along it, Garen exited the small building.

The sky was bright outside. Small patrol motorcycles would come over from a distance from time to time.

The originally empty space in the estate was now full of patrol guards in yellow uniform. Temporary security fortifications were built in corners which were easy to defend and hard to attack. All around the buildings, on the roofs, were patrol guards on duty.

The whole estate had transformed into a large military camp.

Garen took a deep breath. The smell of smoke and blood remnant from the battle yesterday still filled the air.

He strode towards the lake outside of the estate. He planned to have a good rest and go for a swim to relax.

Suddenly, a guard wearing a yellow helmet ran towards him from a short distance away. He stopped in front of Garen and saluted him.

"Mr Garen, a young boy is asking for you outside the estate. He refused to leave no matter what."

"A young boy?" Garen instantly recalled the kid with a runny nose he met near the home of the Eight-Arm Dragon King. "Could it be him?"

"Thanks for informing me. Please lead me to him."

"Certainly. Please follow me." The guard nodded, turned around, and jogged towards the entrance of the estate.

Garen followed at a moderate pace. His one stride equaled two to three of the guard's. It looked as though he was striding casually, but in fact his pace was not slow.

Soon, going past the heavy defense, in the temporary guardhouse constructed on the right side of the entrance, Garen saw the young boy with a runny nose.

The boy looked pale. Both his arms were swollen beyond recognition, almost double their original size, like he had two adult arms affixed to his shoulder. He was wearing a sleeveless gray linen shirt and his hair was messy like a chicken coop.

Once Garen walked in, he recognized the kid who had previously asked him to teach him how to fight. But what made him speechless was that the kid had a burden with him: an adorable petite young girl.

When he saw the young girl, Garen squinted.

The atmosphere in the entire guardhouse became somber. A terrifying sense of oppression lingered overhead like dark clouds, as if the sky was about to collapse on them.

It wasn't just the boy, even the two guards supervising by the side shivered, and almost pulled out their guns in alert.

This was the strong sense of oppression that Bravery had towards all living beings; it was their biological fear towards danger and predators.

The boy was trembling from head to toe, and his face seemed paler than before. His chapped lips were almost bleeding.

"Shenanigans!" Garen sat in a chair and looked at the boy and girl indifferently, without a hint of compassion in his eyes.

But the strange thing was that, when everyone was trembling in fear, the expression of the pretty little girl who had a pitiful expression on her face changed, from one of terror and panic, to a calm and sly look. A trace of surprise flashed across her face.

"How did you discover me?" Her voice was clear and subtle, like a bird call.

"Looks like it was you who instructed him previously…" Garen didn't give a straightforward answer. He stared fixedly at the girl. "I wondered how a young kid could have possibly noticed my true strength. You're so old yet you pretend to be young. It's really my first time encountering a martial arts practitioner like you."

"Bastard! What do you mean by 'old'?!" The girl's gaze changed; it looked as though she had been stabbed in a sore spot. "Don't you recognize the virtue of respecting your elders and caring for the young?! If this kid were not unsuitable to inherit my martial arts, do you think I would have specifically asked him to find you?!"

The girl's words instantly shocked a few guards around them. They swiftly drew their guns and aimed at her.

"Keep calm. She's merely an expert trained in a unique martial art." Garen raised his hand to calm the guards down. "Please leave us. I want to have a proper conversation with them."

"I'm sorry. Towards unknown foreigners, we have to supervise the whole process. This was the highest command given by Lieutenant Lenny," a captain walked in and said calmly. "Mr Garen, please don't put us in a tough spot." Upon entering the guardhouse, he felt a strange sense of danger triggering the hair on his body to stand on end, and his hand subconsciously clasped the gun on his waist. He stared at the strange little girl.

Garen shifted his gaze to the young captain.

""

"It's fine. I understand your difficulties. We'll speak outside then."

He retracted his Bravery, and everyone instantly let out a sigh of relief.

He stood up and walked straight out of the guardhouse towards a small forest outside the estate.

The boy, led by the little girl, followed closely behind. The three soon disappeared into the woods.

Walking at a fast pace for a distance until they couldn't be discovered, Garen turned around and stopped walking.

"Well, who are you and what are your motives?" Garen calmly looked at the girl behind him.

This seemingly adorable and petite girl who looked no more than eight or nine years old gave him the sense of an old monster inhabiting a child's body; she was definitely not an ordinary martial arts practitioner.

The girl's height only reached his waist. She was wearing a shabby currant strappy dress. Her maroon long hair was straight and smooth, with horizontal bangs on her forehead. On her feet were thick black cotton socks and red leather boots. Her skin was supple and fair as snow, and her wine-colored eyes were blinking.

Walking through the woods thick with foliage, she had a skip in her step as her long hair fluttered with her every move; it gave the impression of innocence and charm.

But ever since Garen attained the level of Grandmaster of Combat, he had stopped judging people by their appearances alone.

""

"What are your motives?"

He silently looked at this strange little girl.

"You can call me Celine. My motive is simple. I want you to receive Erudas as your disciple," the girl Celine skipped the nonsense and got straight to the point. "Originally, I didn't intend to expose myself. But to be on the safe side, I think it's better to be honest, in case it would affect future relations."

Garen glanced at the gullible young boy who followed behind her.

"I've heard that, in the Secret Martial Art world, there is a type of Secret Martial Art that shrinks the body to reduce the loss of spiritual essence in order to prolong life. I didn't expect to actually see an example of it."

""""

"I'm glad you recognize this old lady's power." The girl proudly raised her chin. "I intended to accept him as my own disciple, but my martial art does not match him. That day, I saw you at Yoda's house and realized that your martial arts style fits this kid's characteristics perfectly. Most importantly, Erudas seems to be determined to follow you. He was actually foolish enough to complete the training as you instructed!"

At this point, she looked as if she had a headache.

"I have just witnessed Duskdune Shura's true strength, rumored to be the peak of the previous generation. I wonder what your true strength is like," Garen changed the topic and said casually. He began to slowly gather a surge of strong, terrifying Bravery.

The large amount of Bravery surrounded him, and condensed into the invisible shadow of a mammoth.

No roars, no movement, the mammoth just silently shrouded over Garen. It stood there with a murderous look in its eyes.

An invisible pressure fell on the girl, Celine's body.

"Duskdune Shura…You've actually met him before?" Celine was shocked. Her petite body somersaulted away as she gently evaded the oppression of Garen's Bravery.

Garen narrowed his eyes. She had evaded the oppression of his Bravery with such ease and avoided a direct confrontation with him. It was apparent that she was no ordinary character. To be able to accurately sense the speed and extent of the Bravery oppression of another martial arts practitioner, she must have been a Grandmaster of Combat with Bravery of her own.

He gradually raised his right arm, ready to fight.

"Keep calm! It's not your style to bully children at random, is it? If it were to get out that the Divine Marshal of Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate bullied a seven year-old little girl, sob sob…" Celine's expression turned in an instant. Tears streamed out of her eyes. She tugged her clothing down a little to reveal her fair shoulder and started screaming, "Ra…!"

Clap!

Garen's face twitched as he rushed over to cover her mouth.

Chapter 132: Training 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Celine struggled for a while, but Garen’s strength was much stronger than hers, so she failed to escape.

"Help! He’s trying to…" Garen put his hand over her mouth and greatly muffled her voice, but he could still understand what she was trying to say.

Garen’s head ached. People would consider him a pedophile if they saw what he was doing to this little girl and he did not know how his parents and sister would think of him.

"Let me go…!" Celine shouted.

"Stop saying random sh*t and I’ll let you go." Garen felt his temples were throbbing.

"I won’t say it anymore!" Celine nodded like a chicken pecking at its food.

Garen slowly released her after hearing her words.

Celine wiped the dust off her clothes and stepped back. "Pervert!"

Garen’s expression changed again. "Well, I already gave you the chance…" He spoke in a gravelly tone and pounded his fists against each other several times.

"Fine, I’ll stop." Celine finally had a serious look on her face. "You were planning to take Erudas in even if I didn’t come, right?"

"You already knew?" Garen nodded. "He has talent and perseverance. Actually, if he’s trying to learn from me, perseverance is much more important than just talent."

He stared at Celine. "I think you already knew a lot about me, but I still know nothing about you."

Celine hesitated for a second. "I’m the heir of the ancient Martial Arts, Neptune Fist, and I think you already know that I’m much older than my appearance. I used the Essence Locking Techniques to keep myself in a peak state. As an apology, I can give you the secret techniques if you want.

"Neptune Fist…" Garen scrunched his eyebrows. "I didn’t know that there was still a heir of that sect."

"I’m the last one," Celine answered in a light tone. "By the way, I’m still a virgin."

Garen was speechless. "Well, I don’t care about that! Please don’t change topic or else I can’t follow."

"Virgin Grandma, someone’s coming," Erudas suddenly said.

Garen was surprised and had not noticed the footsteps until Erudas told him.

He turned around and stared at the young boy Erudas. "Your sensory perception is keen… I didn’t notice at all…"

Garen thought for a second and glanced around. He noticed that Celine was getting nervous.

The footsteps were getting closer, he could hear people swearing, and the tension was building up.

"Follow me," Garen finally spoke. He turned around and walked toward the manor. Celine felt relieved, grabbed the boy, and followed behind Garen.

****************

After resting in Su Lin’s manor for three days, Garen felt much better and had recovered from the injury.

Angela asked for a courtyard close to the lake and moved in. Garen spent most of his time training the Mammoth Secret Technique and he wanted to make sure that his body was in the best condition. He also started preparing the equipment needed to learn the Firestream Fist.

Celine and Erudas stayed with Garen the whole time and did not go to any other places. They lived in a temporary tent beside the courtyard and the army brought them supplies every day.

Garen helped the boy recover by invigorating the blood circulation around his arms, but Garen did not mention anything about teaching him Martial Arts.

However, it seemed like the two did not care. They looked happy living in the tent provided by the army and probably had not had a good rest in a while.

It was afternoon, the setting sun decorated Lake Saima with rays of red sunlight, and the golden reflection on the surface of the lake was breathtaking.

Inside the rectangular yard beside the lake, Garen dangled from a black iron frame. Garen’s hands and face turned purple due to the exertion.

He inhaled deeply and his stomach rose. The purple color disappeared slowly from his face and hands as he inhaled.

Hoo!

Garen exhaled all the air in his torso and started hitting his palms with his fingers. This repeated process was how he learned the Dark Iron Palm. In order to practice this low-rank Secret Technique, he had to hang from the frame.

The Dark Iron Palm was a low-rank Secret Technique and a lot of people tried to learn it. Martial Artists or people who were just interested in Martial Arts would try to learn it after obtaining the Secret Technique. No matter how weak a Secret Technique was, it would still be stronger than average Martial Arts.

Of the many people that practiced the Dark Iron Palm, the best of them had palms harder than iron and their palm skills could deal damage with their evil power. However, they were only slightly stronger than normal Martial Artists.

Low-rank Secret Techniques were created by Martial Artists that broke past their limitations. The Dark Iron Palm was a bit better than the Iron Body because it could convert the toxins and useless substances in the body into evil power.

By practicing the Dark Iron Palm, Garen could better maintain his health. Garen kept repeating the procedure and would hit his fingers against his palms every time he exhaled all the air from his abdomen.

His long purple hair blocked his view, so he decided to close his eyes and check the skill bar. After practicing the basic training method for a while, some changes finally occurred to the bar.

The row for the Dark Iron Palm started getting blurry.

"Finally…" Garen was excited. He started practicing this morning and finally made some progress by the afternoon.

The words behind the Dark Iron Palm changed quickly: "Dark Iron Palm: Beginner Level (Two levels in total)."

Garen felt something heavy and muddy inside his body that quickly travelled toward his hands. His body was relaxed but his hands became heavy.

He opened his eyes and looked at his palms. Garen’s hands had already turned grey as if they were soaked in ink.

Garen looked at the attribute bar unintentionally and noticed that some of the attributes had changed as well.

209215

His Stamina increased from 2.09 to 2.15.

"Nice, I didn’t expect the Dark Iron Palm to help increase my Stamina," Garen observed his hands carefully.

"I wonder how much damage it can do. Let me give it a try first." Garen looked around and found a small white tree at the corner of the yard.

Garen reached at his feet and untied the rope. He landed on the ground and walked toward the tree quickly.

He raised his palms and pressed them against the surface of the tree. Nothing spectacular happened, but there were two black handprints left on its surface after Garen lowered his hands.

Two black ants were climbing up the tree and they slowed down right after reaching the handprints. Their legs trembled, their bodies curled up, and then they fell from the tree after several seconds.

"That’s the poison from the Dark Iron Palm?" Garen glanced around. "I need something more than the ants. Umm…"

Angela called the guards and asked them to find some cats or dogs. Then, Garen started forcing them to touch the handprints on the tree. The handprints disappeared after killing a dog.

Garen finally had a general understanding of the strength level of the poison from the Dark Iron Palm. "Way too weak. Killing some small animals is the best it can do. Maybe it’ll work on a normal person, but all of the Grandmasters of Combat have high resistance and Dark Iron Palm will do no damage to them."

"Well, let me see what the Firestream Fist can do." He asked the guards to bring him the equipment for practicing the Firestream Fist.

It was a whole basin of black iron sand and the basin was placed above a large pot of burning charcoal. Garen stood in front of the basin and rolled up his sleeves.

"The Mammoth Secret Technique can be combined with the Iron Body, but I’m not sure if the Dark Iron Palm can be combined with the Firestream Fist. I hope I still have some Attribute Points left. If I do, I’ll be able to level them up to the highest level!" Garen shook his head and stopped thinking. He quickly put his hands into the sizzling sand and then immediately took them out. Garen kept repeating this process.

He also used the special breathing and blood circulation methods from the Firestream Fist technique to ensure that the blood flow in his body was correct.

Garen’s hands slowly turned reddish. Although he reached the master level of body hardening techniques, his hands were still burning after constantly contacting the heated sand. His skin had turned black due to the Dark Iron Palm and the resulting dark red color looked like rust.

The size of his hands doubled and dense maroon patterns slowly rose from the skin of his hands.

He could feel the heat from his hands and a chill rushed down to them from his brain. This chill started to slowly neutralize the heat from the iron sand.

Garen closed his eyes and stared at the skill bar. After a while, changes appeared to the row with the Firestream Fist.

The text became blurry: "Firestream Fist: Beginner Level (Four levels in total)."

Another change appeared on the skill bar after he reached the beginner level of the Firestream Fist. The Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm’s text became blurry at the same time.

"I knew it! The Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm were all Secret Techniques that train people’s hands. Learning them together will create a new combination, just like the time I trained the Iron Body and Boulder Martial Art!" Garen stared at the changes with excitement. This was the reason why he had decided to learn these two Secret Techniques first.

The Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm disappeared from the skill bar simultaneously and were replaced by a new skill.

Chapter 133: Clarity 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The new skill finally appeared clearly.

'Unnamed - Mutation Firestream Fist: Level One (of Four), Firestream Fist skills blended with Dark Iron Palm, eliminating impurities and toxins by applying heat from the inside and out, while enhancing Vitality and heat resistance. Attacks on enemy will produce heat poisoning. Training is conducted by alternating both skills to advance.'

"So it's based mainly on Firestream Fist, blended with Dark Iron Palm?"

Garen was deep in thought. Previously, it was the same for Mammoth Secret Technique, with Mammoth as the basis blended with other Secret Martial Arts. It seems that the current situation is similar.

"Nomenclature-wise, since it's a combination of Dark Iron Palm and Firestream Fist, then the name should consist of half of each. I'll call it Dark Crimson Technique then."

As the thought flashed across his mind, the new skill on the Skills Pane quickly changed from 'unnamed' to 'Dark Crimson Technique'.

His special ability let flow a continuous refreshing stream of Qi into his hands. Garen could clearly feel his hands were being fortified at an alarming rate; it was obviously the effect of Dark Crimson Technique Level One.

Chhh!

He immersed his hands simultaneously into boiling hot iron sand, and didn't bother removing them.

The hot iron sand pressed on the skin of his hands; his palms felt a numbing sensation.

The part of his forearms above his palms was gradually reddening, with blue veins popping up. Qi and blood kept coursing through his palms at a high speed.

After 10 full minutes.

Garen suddenly took his hands out and laid a backhand on the wall behind him.

Sizzle…

A gust of white smoke instantly effused from the wall. The wall covered in green moss was imprinted with a black handprint, and there was an unpleasant burnt smell in the air.

"Dark Crimson Technique… Level One can withstand temperatures of about a hundred over degrees. Such a high temperature can be achieved by transferring Qi and blood to the palm, amazing!" Garen was secretly impressed. "This is merely Level One. If I can raise it to higher levels, combined with my mutation Mammoth Secret Technique and Body Hardening Technique peak, then I'll be able to kill and injure at will!"

He retracted his hands, walked to a basin of water on the left of the fire basin, and put his hands in it.

The clear water in the cool basin slowly emitted a sizzling sound, and a waft of water vapor drifted upwards. Garen's fists gradually returned to its normal pale tone.

He removed his hand and used a little bit of force. Blood flowed through his palms as it regained its temperature, and once again emanated a scalding heat. Both palms instantly turned from white to a pale red.

From afar, his hands merely looked like they were filled with blood in the veins, and nothing seemed abnormal; it could very easily be concealed.

"This tactic could only increase deadliness in close combat, effective only when I am able to have physical contact with the enemy. Unfortunately, the biggest disadvantage of low-level Secret Martial Arts is that there is no corresponding combat skill to match with them."

Garen recalled the scene of confrontation with Duskdune Shura. "If I had mastered Dark Crimson Technique then, I could have caused additional damage to him in the direct confrontation, and deterred anyone else from having direct confrontations with me."

At that time his hand-knife strike collided with Duskdune Shura directly. If he could have used Dark Crimson Technique then, he could have injured him by surprise.

"Dark Crimson Technique shall be my concealed skill, just to increase deadliness by dealing a surprise strike."

He relaxed the Qi and blood in his palms, and they were gradually restored to his original pale skin tone.

He tugged on a coat and put it on then walked to the entrance of the courtyard, opened the door, and exited. On the riverbank were the short and tall figures of Erudas and Celine; the former seemed to be telling the latter about something.

When both saw Garen come out, Erudas immediately scuttled over.

"Master! When can I learn your martial arts?"

"Don't call me Master. You're not my disciple yet." Garen was clad in white casual clothing. His long hair was messy and loose, with a hint of red visible between the strands. Coupled with his tall and muscular physique, merely by standing in front of the both of them, he exuded an immense sense of oppression.

He glanced at Erudas's shoulders; it seemed to have completely recovered. Obviously, it was related to the help from Celine throughout this time.

"Looks like you have almost recovered?"

"Yes, Master!" Erudas replied loudly. His small body stood straight. He had cleaned himself up too; he looked much better than at their first meeting. He had defined features, and his short copper-brown hair paired with his delicate white skin showing a tinge of a blush, made him seem like a doll.

"Today, I'll first teach you about something fundamental," Garen said calmly. He put his hands, one after another, on his chest. One hand grasped tightly while the other held on loosely; his legs were in the bow stance.

This was the combat stance that he had revised from White Cloud Combat Arts of White Cloud Gate and perfected.

"This is the initial hand pose inherited from my original sect. It is able to handle attacks from all sides except the back in the shortest amount of time. Let me tell you something important in advance. Martial arts practitioners absolutely should not allow themselves to have their backs facing their enemies. Apart from certain special combat techniques, common martial arts from general sects adhere to this taboo."

"Grandma Virgin told me that before too," Erudas replied innocently. "I'll be powerful as long as I start out with this pose?"

"Because you've saved some time needed to raise your hands to attack. Just like…this!"

Chshh!

With a spin, Garen's right arm axed horizontally like a butcher's knife in a Swing Form strike directed at Celine, who was standing with her body facing sideways.

His arm was like a blade, creating a hissing sound as it cut through air.

Wham!

A section of wooden log was broken in two, and the pieces fell to the ground.

Celine flipped backwards, and evaded the strike with grace. She landed steadily on top of a large white rock nearby; she looked fazed.

"What are you doing?! Don't you know that you should respect your elders and love your young?!"

"Erudas, watch carefully."

Garen disregarded care and quickened his pace forward, his stance instantly converting into Shot Form. His slapped his right palm forward.

"This is Shot Form!"

Wham!

The rock cracked at his palm strike, and bits of rubble flew in all directions. Celine barely managed to evade with a jump, and was shouting in anger.

Garen curved his right arm, and let his right hand swing outwards swiftly like a whip.

"This is Swing Form!"

Crack!

A small tree in the woods by the lake, with a trunk as thick as an arm, crashed to the ground.

Celine was scampering about as she was chased by Garen.

"You bastard! You only know how to bully underage girls! Ahhh!" Almost hit by the falling tree, Celine's face was flush with anger as she ran off into the distance, cursing all the way.

Garen reverted to a normal pose, turned around, and gently exhaled. Those few strikes were all made in one breath, but it was over before he had time to exhale.

"Stances are the postures that make it easiest to attack and defend. If you were to casually stand straight, then the distance it takes for your arm to be raised is much larger than if you were already adopting a stance. Don't belittle this minute amount of time saved. In a real fight, it may come down to this little bit of distance."

"Yes, Master!" Erudas replied loudly even though he didn't fully comprehend what he heard. After seeing Garen's powerful and tough attacks earlier, his eyes gleamed in admiration.

"From today onwards, stand in this stance every day, until you can't hold it any longer, until your knees tremble!" Garen said calmly.

"Yes!"

Garen nodded. This kid had some decent talent, was resilient, willing to endure hardship, and even obedient—he would do whatever he was told—this was the ideal disciple. Even if Garen didn't have any intention of receiving a disciple at the moment, he couldn't help but give him a few pointers now and then.

When he saw Erudas begin to create the stance on his own, Garen corrected his mistakes then directly walked towards Celine standing in the distance.

"Come with me."

Celine stared at him fiercely, hesitated, but still followed.

The two of them walked to a set of stone table and stools in the woods, where Garen sat down naturally.

"The descendant of Neptune Fist, it is said that your Neptune Gate was a crucial great sect in the North. In ancient times you almost separated to declare your own duchy. I'm sure you must be privy to a lot of secrets?" he took the lead to speak first.

Celine jumped onto a stone stool and crouched on it.

"What do you want to know? Let me be clear upfront, I don't know much either."

"I want to know about Duskdune Shura. He defeated me using a type of martial arts called Dragon Gate. What is that?" Garen asked his first question.

"Dragon Gate?" Celine's petite face wrinkled. "You're sure it's Dragon Gate?" Her expression started to turn serious.

"I'm sure. The names that he exclaimed were 'the first Dragon Gate' and so on, from first to fourth. Every strike that hit me completely paralyzed my body, it was strange." Garen was fixated on this point. His Body Hardening Technique was based on the principle of flowing Qi and blood, yet his opponent's Dragon Gate could actually paralyze the body and control Qi and blood—it was like the bane of the Body Hardening Technique.

Celine became silent, seemingly recalling a memory.

The night breeze made the leaves in the woods rustle, and brought with it a slight chill. The rays of sunset shone through the leaves at an angle on the ground, tree trunks, the stone table and chairs, and the two of them. There was a vague sense of beauty like a painting of maple woodlands.

Celine stretched her fingers out to gently brush away the fallen leaves from the white stone table. A yellow beetle gently climbed her index finger.

"Seven Dragon Gate is rumored to be an ancient martial art that is a unique general sect martial art. I do not know the specific methods of training in it, but it is very powerful."

She paused, then continued, "The unique characteristic of Seven Dragon Gate is that it continuously increases in power."

"Starting from the first Dragon Gate, the second, then the third. If a person was continuously hit by all of it, the power of each fist will continue to increase. At the same time, it is capable of obstructing the flow of Qi and blood. The further it progresses, the more it is capable of slowing down the movement of the opponent, to the point of complete paralysis. This is an extremely terrifying consecutive-strike martial art. I can't believe Duskdune Shura has actually mastered it."

Garen's brow twitched. "We're equally Grandmasters of Combat, but he is so much stronger than me!"

"EDDC"

"'Grandmasters of Combat' is merely a collective description of a select few martial art practitioners who have reached the human limit. Naturally there would be stronger and weaker categories within. It's only normal," Celine said matter-of-factly. "Now there are these so-called Grade E and Grade D categorizations. Those are the levels used to categorize the strength of firearms. In actuality, almost all Grandmasters of Combat are Grade D, including you. One level higher would be Grade C, which is currently the category for special unit weapons, such as special gunpowder and powerful weapons made from special materials. These are incapable of being defended by Grandmasters of Combat. Perhaps only a very small number of Grandmasters of Combat can achieve this level. Duskdune Shura might be one of them."

"Then do you know about the existence of people with supernatural abilities?" Garen asked in a low voice.

"Supernatural abilities? You mean telekinesis?" Celine was shocked. "You've encountered such people?"

Garen nodded.

"In my years of wandering, I've encountered them multiple times too. Those people are very mysterious. They have developed strange abilities through telekinesis, and view themselves as beings transcending mortals. But in actuality, they are merely poor souls from failed experiments, detesting the world because of a tragic incident," Celine said softly.

Chapter 134: Clarity 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The experiment failed? What happened?"

"I don’t know. Several dozens of years ago, a group of people escaped from a human subject research center. I’ve seen telekinesis before and I knew they were strong, but that’s all I know." Celine shook her head.

"Last question, do you know anything about the Golden Sword Throne?" Garen asked in a light tone.

"What’s that?" Celine looked confused.

Garen stood up. "That’s all I wanted to ask. I don’t know what happened between you and that little guy and I don’t care. However, if you want me to stay with you and protect you, you should at least pay me."

"I already prepared something for you." Celine sneered. She took a black scroll out of her pocket and threw it toward Garen.

Pah!

Garen carefully caught the scroll and looked at it. There were several tiny words printed on the surface of the scroll: "Essence Locking Technique."

"That’s the payment."

Garen stared at her for a second, turned back, and left with the scroll. He returned to the courtyard and finished his dinner before receiving Su Lin’s message.

He quickly headed to the meeting room inside the manor. Garen had promised Su Lin that he would help to fight against Duskdune Shura, so he would not leave the manor before it was done.

Most of the others had already sat down in their seats by the time Garen entered the meeting room. Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King, was not here and his seat was taken by a tall slim blonde lady wearing a tight black leather suit. Garen could see that her breasts were covered by black bandages through her open collar. The lady was not wearing underwear and was quite alluring.

"Let me make an introduction. This is Miss Mayer Iriland, an international police officer, " Su Lin said after standing up. "She’s here for Duskdune Shura as well."

"She’s trying to track down Duskdune Shura?" Everyone in the room looked surprised. Duskdune Shura could easily escape when surrounded by many special agents, yet Mayer was trying to track him down alone. They thought that Mayer must be someone special.

The two generals, Su Lin, and Aris all stared at the lady. Her face was not that attractive, she showed absolutely no expression, and it seemed like she did not want to spend too much time with strangers.

"It seems like I’m late. I think everyone here has already heard about how strong Duskdune Shura is, so I’m not going to go over that again. Based on a telegraph I obtained from Kandivella, at the borders of the Yalu Confederation, Duskdune Shura has already arrived at the ruins of Kandivella." She gave everyone in the room a cold look.

"Everyone, as an officer of the international police, I hope you can follow my orders so we can catch Duskdune Shura together. I heard that there is someone here that can fight against Duskdune Shura one on one. Please stand up."

The others immediately began to stare at Garen. Garen scrunched his eyebrows. Although he was not happy, he still stood up.

"Try your best to slow down Duskdune Shura and create space for my people. Follow my orders when we start the mission," Mayer said in a calm tone.

"Wait," Garen stopped her, "my sole purpose is to protect my friends. I don’t care about other things."

"Please notice that I am not asking. I’m giving you an order and you have no right to disobey it." Mayer furrowed her eyebrows. "I’m an officer from the international police and I have the authority to give orders. You can sit down for now."

"Orders?" Garen sneered. "Who the hell are you?"

The two generals had bitter smiles on their face. While Su Lin and Aris sat by the side, they also did not know how to deal with such a situation. Su Lin was trying to ask Garen to calm down by signaling with his eyes.

Mayer’s expression did not change and it seemed like she had already expected a situation like this.

"Mr. Garen." She took out a pile of information sheets and put them down on the table.

"These are the records of the murders you have committed since you debuted. You killed about 35 people, directly or indirectly. You can choose not to follow my order. and I’m willing to shoot you to death for all the murders you committed.

"Are you threatening me?" Garen narrowed his eyes.

"I’m not. Actually, I’m giving you a chance." Mayer stared at Garen calmly. "Follow my order or die. Your choice."

"I choose to kill you!" Garen grinned and pulled the door off the wall.

BOOM!

The door was about two meters tall and it flew toward Mayer while spinning like a fan blade. Garen’s aim was accurate and the door did not hit anyone else.

CRACK!

Mayer used a high kick and easily smashed apart the entire door. She quickly turned and did a side front snap kick toward Garen’s head.

Her long leg drew an arc in the air and a silver blade popped out from the bottom of her high heel. She aimed at Garen’s temple.

Strangely, Mayer’s side front snap kick was vibrating intensely, as if she could change the direction of the kick at any time she wanted.

Su Lin held Aris’s arm and retreated with her. He knew how strong Miss Mayer and Garen were. Although Su Lin was a great Martial Artist himself, he still did not want to get involved in this.

BAM!

Garen hit Mayer’s dagger with his palm. The dagger broke and pierced the ceiling.

BAM BAM BAM BAM!!

The two kept trading hits, with Mayer using an array of different kicks with her slim legs. Garen blocked most of her attacks but was still hit in the chest several times. Mayer was much faster than him.

They already left the meeting room and the fight had moved into the hallway. The guards did not know what to do and decided to stay away from the two combatants.

"Axe Kick!" Mayer yelled as she raised one of her legs high into the air and kicked down vertically as quick as lightning.

BANG!

"Naive!" Garen grinned, grabbed her leg, and swung her toward the wall.

*BOOM*

Garen suddenly stopped moving and it was almost like time had paused.

He grabbed Mayer’s right leg and was about to smash her against the wall.

Mayer held onto a wall lamp tightly with her left leg still planted on the ground. Her face turned pale and she bit her bottom lip hard, but there was still no expression on her face. Mayer was breathing heavily and she had not expected Garen to be so strong.

Garen looked at a head-sized hole in the wall beside him as dust sprinkled down to the ground.

"Old man, what the hell?" He looked at the other end of the hallway.

Yoda, the Eight-Armed Dragon King, wielded a black heavy sniper rifle in his hand and he was aiming at Garen. Yoda’s face flushed and he looked furious.

"Let Mayer go. I don’t care about the others, but I will f*cking kill you if do anything to her! Don’t even try!"

Garen gave Yoda a cold stare. "You really want to die."

A strong aura spread through the hallway as Garen’s body started expanding. At this distance, he was sure he could kill them both after taking one hit from Yoda.

"Go away Yoda! I don’t want you to help me!" Mayer yelled. It seemed like she was not appreciative of Yoda’s support.

"Yoda! Garen! Stop. For the God’s sake," Su Lin said suddenly. "Miss Mayer, it’s a misunderstanding. Let’s calm down. We should work together to fight against Duskdune Shura."

"Alright, calm down everyone." Lenny walked out of the room with her cane. "Miss. Mayer, I understand that the international police has the right to give orders, but Garen is not a part of your system and he doesn’t like being ordered to do things for you. You know what, how about we let General Crohn give out orders this time? He knows the situation very well."

Garen released Mayer’s right leg. He did not really want to kill her, but he simply disliked her arrogance.

The generals did not want to get involved in this fight. Yoda’s presence made him want to kill Mayer and Su Lin immediately stepped in after realizing what Garen was going to do. Su Lin did not want the situation to get worse at the point.

"Cunning old prick," Garen mumbled. Mayer’s leg was injured and she was having trouble walking away. She had previously given Garen a hard look the whole time while she was speaking and Garen needed to assert his dominance. Otherwise, Mayer would think he was scared.

Garen did not want to waste time anymore, so he turned back and walked out of the building.

"Garen, wait." He heard someone’s voice coming from behind.

Su Lin quickly caught up and put his arm on Garen’s shoulder.

"Sorry, there’s nothing my father can do at the moment, so we had to let you deal with Mayer. She was always so arrogant and we needed to make sure she did not mess up our plan."

"I understand. Mayer was trying to flaunt her skills by fighting me, but she did not expect me to be so strong. Her combat skills are good and she’s a Grandmaster of Combat. She must be strong since she’s going after Duskdune Shura." Garen crossed his arms and laid his back against the wall by the exit. "What’s her relationship with Yoda?"

"Yoda has been chasing after her for many years…" Su Lin had a bitter smile on his face, "However, Mayer doesn’t like him at all. That’s all I know about them. She’s one of the registered Grandmasters of Combat in the federation. Her kicking techniques and tracking skills are incredible."

"Well…" Garen was speechless.

"You did very well last time and we’d be dead without you. We’ll take care of Duskdune Shura later. They already learned how serious the matter was and they will send more people here. There is one more thing. I need you to go to a place with me and we will be finished after that. What do you think?" Su Lin spoke calmly.

"Sure, no problem." Garen did not hesitate.

He owed Su Lin two favors, the one for his sister and one for the time he got surrounded by the enemies on his way back. He had not yet reached the Master Level of his Body Hardening Techniques at that time and he would have taken some serious damage without Su Lin’s aid. The government was pursuing him as well and the situation could have become much worse.

These were the reasons why Garen decided to stay with Su Lin first before going to the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate to obtain the secret techniques. Garen wanted to keep his promises and Su Lin was his friend.

"Let’s go. We will drive there." Su Lin patted Garen’s back and walked toward the parking lot.

After several seconds, Garen saw Celine appear out of nowhere and she landed on his right shoulder.

"Get off me." He scowled.

"I’ll go there too. I need you to protect me," Celine responded in a cute tone, while sitting steadily on Garen’s shoulder.

"Fine. Come with us." Su Lin looked at Celine and smiled, "There is no point in hiding it anymore."

Chapter 135: Hunted 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Howl…

A white line cut through the middle of the vast sandy plains, extending into the distance beyond the horizon.

A silver car was slowly driving on the white line. Silver patterns were engraved on the side of the car; it looked exceptionally luxurious.

The car quickly reached a flat land. The back of the car kept blowing up sand and dust, which made it seem like a yellow tail.

From above, this flat piece of land had a few tiny yellow balls on it, arranged in a whirlpool shape.

The car slowly stopped at a ball on the outermost rim.

After a series of car doors opening and closing, three youths alighted from the car: two adults and a child.

The two adults had different images. One man had flaming red hair and looked handsome. He looked like a playboy who enjoyed women and drinking.

The other man was tall and well-built. His dark purple hair draped over his shoulders. There was a hint of coldness in his ruby eyes. He had an arm across his chest, and on it sat an adorable little girl.

"What is this place?" The tall man was Garen, who had followed Su Lin out. He gently shook his arm to allow Celine to dismount.

"Somewhere on the edge of Thakanriknar Desert, I'm not too sure either. I've merely followed father's instructions to find this place," Su Lin said while shaking his head. "Let's go. The thing I'm looking for is in the middle."

He took the lead and walked towards the center of the round whirlpool formation.

Garen and Celine followed closely behind.

The three of them advanced inwards in a straight line along the gaps between the balls of the round whirlpool formation.

From time to time, Garen would touch the balls as he passed by. They felt cool and hard to the touch, and rough too; there were a lot of honeycomb-like holes on the surface.

These balls were all two meters tall and entirely dark yellow, almost inseparable from the sand that it stood on.

The three of them reached the center of the round formation. In the middle was a three-meter-tall yellow ball, the largest of the lot.

Su Lin stood in front of the ball, constantly groping for something. Soon, with a gentle press of his palm, a round piece of yellow stone block the size of a fist gave way with a click, and revealed a deep, dark hole beneath.

He reached and groped for a while, then gently took something out: it was a black bundle of cloth.

He swiftly opened the bundle. There were remnant pieces of yellow pebbles inside, and nothing else.

"I can't believe we still haven't found it," Su Lin sighed and turned around. "He is indeed Duskdune Shura. He managed to eliminate so many locations to find this place merely based on father's lie."

Garen walked up from behind.

"What is it that you're looking for?"

"The real Golden Sword Throne was hidden here by father," Su Lin explained. "But now it's been removed. This gamble with Duskdune Shura, no matter how you look at it, father has lost. Only this piece of black cloth which was wrapping the throne is left."

Garen ignored the deeper meaning of his words and other circumstances. Suddenly he narrowed his eyes and stared at the black cloth bundle in Su Lin's hands.

He slowly reached out to take the black cloth bundle from Su Lin's hands, just like how one would take something for a casual look.

At the touch of the black cloth, a refreshing stream instantly flowed from the bundle into his fingers.

Garen trembled slightly, then inconspicuously started to pretend opening up the cloth to inspect inside.

The stream from the black cloth continuously flowed into his fingers, then along his palm, shoulders, chest, and finally into his brain.

Within seconds, the stream from the black cloth instantly weakened and disappeared.

He could suddenly feel in his hands the scalding heat of the cloth from being baked in the dessert for too long.

"Let me have a look," Celine said excitably.

Garen casually threw her the black cloth. He vaguely heard Su Lin say something, but he couldn't hear clearly anymore. His entire attention was concentrated on the Attributes Pane at the bottom of his vision.

'Strength 2.64; Agility 1.22; Vitality 2.15; Intelligence 1.53; Potential 112%'

Potential at 112%!

"Sure enough…it really is Potential!" Garen was delighted. "Finally! Finally I have new attribute points!"

It had been too long since he last acquired new attribute points, he couldn't even remember when it was. During this time, his enhancement had all been due to his training in Secret Martial Arts.

"Garen, Garen?..." Su Lin's voice came from beside him.

Garen snapped out of his daze, and looked at Su Lin who was looking at him puzzled.

"Sorry, I was thinking about something and zoned out."

"So now are you planning to go back to Huaishan or…?"

"I've changed my mind," Garen said in a low voice. "I want to track down Duskdune Shura with you."

"Oh?" Su Lin was mildly surprised.

"Come on, let's head back." Garen turned around and walked straight towards the car.

He didn't care what Celine and Su Lin thought. He got in the car and, with his back on the seat, closed his eyes as if he were sleeping. But in actuality, he concentrated all his attention on the Attributes Pane and Skills Pane.

His current situation was clear at a glance.

‘264 122 215 153 112%

'Strength 2.64; Agility 1.22; Vitality 2.15; Intelligence 1.53; Potential 112%

———— Secret Martial Arts ---

Mammoth Mutation: Explosive (Top level) Skin Hardening Level One (Iron Body); Blood Qi Stabilization (Boulder Martial Art);

’Firestream Fist: Level One (of Four)'

"There are a few options now. The first is to enhance the effect and level of Mammoth Mutation Secret Martial Art. Another is to enhance Iron Body and Boulder Martial Art, which are now at rudimentary level, to Level One. This would also have a similar overall effect to enhancing Mammoth Mutation Secret Martial Art, but the specific effects of enhancement would be unclear."

"The there's enhancing Firestream Fist from rudimentary level to Level One. It only requires a little attribute points. The question is whether it's worth using the points on this attribute."

He started to hesitate.

There were a few mysterious symbols on the back of the Skills Pane. It represented the clarification on the attribute points required to forcibly enhance skills.

'Attribute points can enhance low level skills by one level per point, and mid-level skills forcibly by one level every two points. For high-level skills, five points are needed to enhance one level, not to mention the need to meet skills learning and enhancement requirements. Failure to enhance might be due to incomplete data collected.'

Initially, his Mammoth Secret Technique was supplemented by the wad of paper soaked in medicinal water, and after that aided by his Master, Fei Baiyun’s medicinal pill. Otherwise, he would have to honestly practice and train sequentially to enhance it, or rely on adding attribute points.

"Practicing Secret Martial Art is unusually difficult…" Garen suddenly gave a long sigh. He considered the progression of Secret Martial Art difficult even with his special ability and conditions, needless to say how it would be for other martial art practitioners.

Most martial arts practitioners were the same. Even if they had talent and trained diligently for 10, 20 years to achieve a hard-earned Secret Martial Art, they would still be helpless in the face of firearms. This bitter sentiment was perhaps only understood by Secret Martial Art practitioners who have trained hard to hone their craft.

At this moment, Su Lin and Celine had gotten in the car as well. The car slowly started, turned a corner, and headed back towards the direction they came from.

The three of them did not speak in the car.

Garen kept considering which skill to add the attribute points to. He obtained these points after much difficulty, it was a world of difference compared to the attribute points he easily obtained before.

Attribute points are easy initially but would gradually become difficult. After his body developed resistance towards most Antiques of Tragedy, it had become more difficult for him to easily obtain Attributes. Unfortunately, he had understood this too late.

After final consideration, Garen’s vision finally fell on Agility.

So far, he had realised in his battles with myriad experts, that the defence of his peak Body Hardening Technique was sufficient, but he seemed to always have to put up a forceful resistance because his speed was unable to keep up with his opponents’.

In his martial arts journey, the most important skills were Strength and Vitality, followed by Agility and Intelligence.

"My defence is sufficient for now. Even if faced with Duskdune Shura’s Dragon Gates, as long as he doesn’t engage anything above the fourth Gate, it wouldn’t cause me much harm. So now the most important thing is to add to Agility and Intelligence. If I can’t keep up in agility and speed, that means I would constantly not be able to keep up with the enemy’s position. The enhancement of Intelligence would also benefit me in terms of my grasp of the situation. But for now it’s better if I enhance practical true strengths.

He looked at that bit of hard-earned Attributes and finally made up his mind. He cast his vision firmly on Agility.

On the Attributes Pane, the value for Agility gradually blurred and changed from 1.22 to 1.52.

"Huh? Attribute points have reverted to increasing by 0.3 every time?" Garen was slightly surprised. He instantly noticed that, as Agility was enhanced, Strength followed suit, and gradually changed from 2.64 to 2.66.

Just as he finished adding Attributes, Garen instantly felt as though his body was about to float. Obviously it was caused by a large-scale increase in Agility.

The enhancements gained from the addition of 0.3 to Agility in one go, for a Grandmaster of Combat who had precise control of his body like Garen, were exceptionally great.

He closed his eyes and felt the change which made his entire body feel light.

Originally he planned to split the Attribute points up and add some to Intelligence. After all, the enhancement of intelligence would eventually have a trickle-down effect on all other aspects. But in the end he gave up on that idea. The effect of the Intelligence Attribute, based on his prior analysis, was the integrated enhancement of comprehension, analysis and memory. But for someone like him who was able to directly and swiftly grasp the basics of academic subjects as long as the Attribute requirements were satisfied, that wasn’t very important.

Intelligence was like a skill in martial arts: indispensable, but would only play a role in a situation where the gap between strengths wasn’t too wide. Under absolute Strength, any skill or strategy would be superfluous.

After all, the more concealed and meticulous a plan was, the more it required a precise linking of every moving part; a mistake in any one part would result in the complete collapse of the plan.

And most importantly, he was not aiming for victory in the grand scheme of things, but was instead in pursuit of the true purpose of martial arts. It was the same reason he was passionate about martial arts—his goal that he carried over with him from his previous life on Earth—to break through the human limit and achieve evolution.

The purpose of martial arts, apart from combat and killing, was to break free from the shackles of human limit, and achieve personal evolution. This was also the limit that many Grandmasters of Combat in this world were pursuing.

Garen was familiarising himself with the changes to his body. He reached a fist out and repeatedly opened and clenched it.

Learning from the words and deeds of Fei Baiyun, Farak and Eldest Senior Sister, he had now become more firmly set on this goal.

The car was slowly turning around. They were further and further from the round whirlpool formation behind them, until it disappeared beyond the horizon.

In front of them to the right, a stationary white car appeared in the distance, its headlights reflected the blinding sunshine like the eyes of a goldfish. A man stood in front of the car. He was a bearded man who wore a white cloak and wrapped himself up like an Arab. He was leaning on the front of the car bonnet and doing repairs. The car constantly emitted black smoke and strange clunking noises could be heard from time to time.

Su Lin drove past the bearded man.

Outside the right car window, a caravan of camels carrying loads could vaguely be seen cutting through the desert in the opposite direction. Dark-skinned men swayed as they rode the camels and marched on forward. A breeze brought with it the crisp sound of camel bells from the distance.

In the car, the three of them were quietly admiring the scenery outside.

The endless stretch of yellow desert gave the illusion that it was delicate and smooth under the sun, like top-grade fine porcelain.

Su Lin gradually slowed the car; the sound of the engine became much softer.

Snap.

A small grey figure stepped on the car window then rapidly leaped over the car, from right to left. It landed on the sand to the left of the car and swiftly ran into the distance.

Only after it was a distance away did the three of them clearly see that it was a small animal similar to a cat, like a kitten with rabbit ears. Its body was covered grey fur. Compared to a cat, its ears were much larger, much longer, and were constantly wiggling.

The eyes of this little guy narrowed into slits as it ran; its four little legs moved without pause, but it was still very stable.

"Bat-eared fox. A common small animal." Su Lin looked speechlessly at the four tiny paw prints left on the car window.

"Isn’t this area close to the entrance of the desert? I didn’t expect to see a bat-eared fox," Celine lamented.

Chapter 136: Hunted 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sat to a side and didn’t speak. He was still quietly experiencing the changes to his body brought about by the enhancement to Agility.

The car continued to move forward. Not long after, Celine suddenly turned around to look out the back of the car.

"Someone is following us from behind."

Su Lin looked into the rear-view mirror and was slightly stunned.

"Followed? I don’t think so. I checked carefully before we set off."

Vrooom…

The sound of an engine coming from behind the car got closer and closer.

Wham!

The car was hit hard once. It started shaking violently and they were almost thrown off course.

"Damn it! We really are being followed!"

Su Lin had an idea. He hurriedly turned the steering wheel to evade the tailgate.

Wham wham!

Two more crash sounds. Two black cars flanked them from the right and left. The rear-view mirror broke off in the crash.

"What the…! Where did these guys come from?! My limited edition Bolshoy!" Su Lin glanced at the broken rear-view mirror with a pained expression. He was frantically turning the steering wheel in an attempt to escape from the flank attack.

Wham!

A loud crash came from the side again. The right side of the car was instantly dented and almost hit Garen who was sitting in the back passenger seat.

"Find somewhere to stop the car!" Garen shouted in a deep voice.

"I’m trying to!" Su Lin was panicked too. In this kind of situation where the car was flanked, the cars behind would crash into them if they stopped. It would be difficult even for him to sustain such an impact.

If the timing wasn’t right, the car might even flip.

Wham! Wham wham!

Three consecutive crashes made the car shake violently; it started spinning like a top from the impact.

Garen and the others inside were dizzy from the spinning. Garen was relatively fine; Celine and Su Lin’s heads bumped onto some hard parts in the car.

Rattatatat!

The rear windshield broke with a crash. Garen shielded Celine with his body and held her down on the car seat. Bullets continued to strike the interior of the car and golden sparks could be seen from time to time.

"Damn it, it’s a light machine gun!" Su Lin shouted.

"Find a chance to stop the car!" Garen roared. The sound of the machine gun was too noisy; they couldn’t hear each other clearly.

"I’m trying!!" Su Lin replied loudly. He leaned over the steering wheel to steady it. Under these circumstances, Garen would probably be fine, but Su Lin and Celine definitely didn’t have such a strong peak Body Hardening Technique. They would be badly injured if they got hit a few times.

Wham!

It was another crash. The black car to their right closed in on them. A man in black clothes pulled out a black rifle and aimed it mercilessly at them.

Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!

A cluster of bullets hit the silver car.

Su Lin stepped on the brakes as hard as he could, but the car—clipped by the three black cars—continued to spin and zoom forward.

Suddenly, a large hand reached in from behind and held his head down.

With a bang, a cluster of bullets broke the side window and flew over the large hand. A few bullets actually hit the back of the hand, and blood spurted out from it.

"Damn it, I can’t stop the car! What cars are they driving anyway? The horsepower is so big!" Su Lin started cursing. The brakes under his feet had been completely rendered useless.

He took out a handgun from his waist and wanted to shoot out of the car, but there was no chance.

Garen was just about to stick his head out and jump out from the broken car door when, with a bang, a cluster of bullets suddenly shot in from the hole on the door and hit him squarely on the body. The immense impact shook his entire body and he was shot back into the car.

"Damn it!"

Garen grabbed a piece of debris from the car door and flung it out of the car.

With a whoosh, the debris shot out spinning.

Bang!

A cluster of bullets hit the car door debris and actually sent it flying backwards. It hit Garen’s chest with a bang.

Bang bang bang bang!!

A stream of violent gunshots continuously greeted Garen’s body; the impact completely prevented him from getting up. His body started to get warmer as the temperature rose; it was the intense heat generated from the impact and friction of the bullets.

Garen was completely pinned down as shot after shot of shotgun pellets forcefully struck his body.

"Stop the car!" Garen roared.

"The brakes have failed!" Su Lin punched the steering wheel hard.

Garen barely raised his head again when—

Bang!

—another shot hit him hard in the face.

"Go to hell!"

Crank!

He tore out the entire rear passenger seat and flung it at the black car to the side.

With a thud, one of the black cars on the right started flipping at the impact of the sofa and veered off the road, rolling down the sand dune by the road.

With a boom, the car suddenly exploded. The few men in black clothing who had just leapt out of the car were engulfed in flames.

The two other black cars were shocked and didn’t dare to stay too close anymore, backing off a distance.

"Are you alright?" Su Lin asked loudly.

Garen took a breath and was about to reply when, suddenly the edge of his eye caught sight of something behind them, and all his hairs instantly stood on end.

"Fuck! It’s a rocket launcher!" He didn’t have time to think beyond that; he merely felt a chill run down his spine. "Jump!"

There was a low roar.

He was the first to jump out of the left side. He rammed the car door off with a bang; Celine and Su Lin followed him out.

Boom!

The silver car transformed into a ball of flames and exploded.

The three of them rolled for a distance on the sand. The black cars sped forward from the force of inertia before they halted to a stop a distance away.

Garen had just managed to raise his head when he saw a group of people alight from the black cars. Two of them were carrying rocket launchers and were already aiming towards Garen and the others.

A terrifying sense of threat surged towards him.

Without second thought, he grabbed the petite Celine and jumped out a few meters in a side leap.

Boom boom!

A large amount of sand and dust was blasted into the air and sprayed down all around like raindrops.

Garen grabbed Celine and rolled down a sand dune, finally avoiding the sight of that group of people.

They kept on rolling for quite a while until they were dizzy before stopping motionless at the base of the dune.

"Pfff! Pff pfff!"

Spitting out the sand in his mouth, Garen rolled over and stood up. He picked the dizzy Celine up with one hand and slapped her across the face a few times.

"Wake up! This isn’t the time to faint!"

Celine’s face was red hot from the slapping, but it managed to wake her up.

"You bastard! How dare you slap me?" She struggled to break free from Garen’s grip, but to no avail. After that bout of rolling, she was dizzy and weak, completely unable to exert any force.

Garen stood up and looked up at the peak of the dune.

"This is the first time I’ve been chased into such a miserable state!"

"Bastard…they’re after me. I’ve implicated you in this!" Celine coughed for a few times.

"You stay here! I’ll go check on Su Lin," Garen said, and immediately started to climb the dune.

As he reached the top, he saw Su Lin walk towards him, also covered in sand.

"Are you hurt?" Su Lin asked loudly.

Shaking his head, Garen walked towards him.

"Where are the people who attacked us?"

"They’re all gone." Su Lin pointed towards the distance. Two black dots could be seen in the distance: it was the two black cars escaping. "They were obviously after you or Celine. They targeted all their firepower at you! Damn, even the KTR rocket launchers are out! I’ve only heard of this being the new product developed in Weisman, I can’t believe they dare use it blatantly in such a place! My 36 million dollar limited edition Bolshoy!"

Su Lin was obviously very irritated, with the pain of losing his car shown across his face.

"This is not the time to be worried about your car! Alright, I don’t think they were after me. They should have been going after Celine."

Garen carefully recalled the situation earlier. It felt like all the firepower was directed at Celine.

It was indeed like she said: those people were after her.

Clang!

Suddenly at the bottom of the dune, a piercing metal clanging sound came from where Celine stood.

Garen and Su Lin looked downwards. They saw Celine and a person in black clothing fighting each other. In a distance, there were three other figures cloaked in black rushing towards Celine.

"We have to save her!" Su Lin said in a low tone and rushed down the dune.

Garen was slightly slower, but followed behind.

Clang!

Celine’s petite face was serious. She did a back flip and landed on the sand. There was something in her hand that seemed to be capable of forcefully resisting her opponent.

"You again…" With a tiny hand, she gently pulled from her waist a silver belt—more than two meters long—and flicked it hard. The silver belt produced a series of crisp cracking sounds and transformed into a straight, hard rod.

Two whooshing sounds were heard, and two metal blades appeared at the tip of the rod. The belt had transformed into a trident-like exaggerated weapon in the blink of an eye.

Celine waved the trident around, and drew a few silver lines in the air with it.

Bang!

At the sound of a gun, a cluster of bullets hit her squarely in the back.

Clanging sounds could be heard from the collision. The yellow sand around them strangely sprayed up and a large amount of bullets were repelled and hit the ground. The yellow sand and dust enveloped Celine.

Chhh.

Not far from Celine, a young man with long, white hair pulled out two daggers from his thighs and ran straight into the sand without hesitation.

"Stop the other two."

"Yes!"

The three figures clad in black nearby turned around and leapt at Garen and Su Lin without hesitation.

The white haired youth dashed towards Celine: his footsteps on the sand became more and more rapid, faster and faster.

Hiss!

A black mark suddenly appeared under his leather boots where he stepped on the sand.

The youth instantly combined his daggers into a short knife. Celine's petite figure reflected on the blade.

"One flash!" the young man shouted as he rotated his body and slashed a silver-white mark with the blade.

Chhh!

Clang!

A bang was heard.

The yellow sand scattered from the shock, turned into a rim of yellow stripes, spread out in all directions, and gradually dispersed.

The white-haired youth who was holding the short knife, was elbowed hard into the ground.

The sand and dust dispersed to reveal Celine holding the trident.

Her head of copper-brown hair fluttered in the wind. It was as if Celine turned from a child into a mature teen. She gripped the trident in one hand, and covered her chest with the other. Her legs were long and her waist was slim; her pale translucent skin had a jade-like luster when it reflected the sunlight.

"Neptune Fist, Myriad Water Jasper Technique!"

Celine was overlooking the white-haired youth from a height; her eyes seemed to contain the roaring and rolling waves of a vast ocean.

She flipped the trident pressed on top the youth's head.

Clang!

Blood spurt out from countless wounds on the white-haired youth's body. He had a look of disbelief in his eyes.

More than a hundred wounds tore the skin of his entire body. All his arteries burst and blood squirted out, as if overwhelmed by some immense pressure.

"You…actually…are able to…" Before he could finish his sentence, he fell backwards and died.

Celine retracted her trident and concentrated her gaze on the weapon in her hand. The turbulent shade in her eyes quickly calmed down.

Pfff!

She quickly covered her mouth, but still could not prevent a mouthful of blood from spilling out. The viscous blood dripped from the edges of her palm.

Chapter 137: Sin Gerro 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You alright there?" Garen asked walking towards Celine, carrying two the men in black.

"Well, you've grown, haven't you?" He added, glancing at Celine’s matured hourglass body with a hint of mild surprise.

What used to be children's clothing had now morphed into a few strips of cloth, barely covering her important parts. The cloth again threatened to fall off just as Celine was about to cover her mouth. Startled, she quickly reached for her clothes and clutched them tightly.

"I’m fine. You don't have to come any closer!" Celine panicked slightly and whipped her trident off the ground, bringing with it a large amount of yellow sand.

The whirlwind of dust and dirt blocked Garen’s vision, and as the sand slowly fell to the ground after some ten seconds, Celine had reverted back to her usual six, seven year old childish look with her ragged, oversized clothes . Her body was covered in blood and she carried a pale white look on her face.

With a gentle push off the ground, Celine leapt up into the air and sat on Garen’s right shoulder. The trident in her hand had shrunk back into its original shape, resting on her waist.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

"You'd better explain everything when we get back, or I’m afraid I’ll have to toss you out."

"It’s just a combination of the modified version of the Contortion Technique and Essence Locking Technique. I can’t maintain my real body for long, it's seriously injured. In any case, I can only move about freely in this state." Celine answered, softly.

Garen looked down at the corpse and said. "And what of these people?"

"They were sent by an old enemy of mine. They just want me dead." Celine finished, her expression slightly forlorn.

Garen squatted down to examine the white haired corpse.

It seemed as if it was gored by hundreds of knives simultaneously; dense, fresh wounds covered the corpse, leaking blood that dyed the sand on the ground crimson.

"One of my secret techniques, from the Neptune Fist. Myriad Water Jasper Technique. It’s too bad I can’t use it very often." Celine said plainly.

Garen didn’t reply her. He fished a card out from the corpse, and on it bore a symbol: the seven of diamonds.

"Did you find anything?" Su Lin asked as he hurried over from afar. He was holding up another card: the 3 of diamonds. "I found this."

"Was it on the body of the assailant?" Garen asked.

Su Lin nodded.

"It’s the Poker Organization, from Weisman. I'd heard of them in the past, but I hadn't expected to see them within the federation."

"Poker Organization… ? Do you have any concrete information on them?" Garen asked softly.

"It will take time. These people had the balls to attempt to kill us. They're not getting away with this, not on my watch." Sulin let out a cold laugh. "I will investigate this Poker Organization once we're done with the Duskdune Shura incident.

"Are you sure?"

"This isn't Weisman, and they dare to act wildly here! Do they suppose they're the Duskdune Shura, then? " Su Lin mocked. "Whoever touches me means to pick a fight against the Belfatalia household! They're picking a fight with the whole Special Agent Bureau and the government!"

"No one would come out unharmed when they go against the government!"

Garen’s lips twitched ever so slightly, as if he wanted to say something, but held his tongue.

"For now, we need to take care of the Duskdune Shura first, it's a matter of the Federation’s prestige-." stated Su Lin.

"Whatever the case, we should head back fast. We'll need to walk back or hitch a ride, since our car is blown to pieces." Celine said as she cut off Su Lin.

Su Lin nodded. "And about that other issue, you'd better see it through to the end." he added.

"Don’t worry. I'm not going anywhere." Celine replied, curling her lips

.

****************

Thud.

Tea cups were set softly onto a black wooden table.

Two siblings, Celine and the Aris took their seats side by side on the same row, and opposite them were Garen and Su Lin.

The four of them sat in a small study room opposite each other. Celine, bored to tears, flipped a large, black book endlessly, as if looking for something among its pages.

To her side, Aris was fiddling with a red raindrop shaped gem, not bothering to raise her head up and look at Garen at all.

Su Lin and Garen were gazing out the clear study window to their right, where an innocent looking plain sat just outside the building.

Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King was scolding Erudas loudly, whip in hand.

"Straighten your god damn arm!"

"Yes, sir" Erudas replied loudly.

"Don’t stick up your ass!"

"Yes, sir!"

Crack! The sound of the whip rang through the air

"Do you understand human language, you brat? Don’t stick up your ass! Do you understand?!"

"Yes, sir!!!"

"My fucking God, could you be any more stupid!?"

Yoda seemed to have take a sudden interest in scolding Erudas, who was standing outside, upside down, on his head. It seemed like Yoda was teaching him Gun Art.

The sound of endless rambling permeated through the window into the study room.

Garen broke his gaze and looked at Celine. The girl was smirking as she looked out the window; it was very likely that she had something to do with it, as well.

"We have news of the Duskdune Shura, by telegram. I called you guys over the moment I received the news." Su Lin tapped the table rhythmically.

"Let’s hear it." Garen was very interested in the Duskdune Shura. To be more precise, he was interested in the Golden Sword Throne, currently in the enemy’s hands. He could imagine the huge potential it would bring; there were still remnants of the Antique of Tragedy’s power left inside the black cloth. This might be his first time coming across an Antique of Tragedy with this amount of potential.

Su Lin glanced sideways at Garen, puzzled at his change of attitude at the mention of the topic. However, he didn’t think much of it.

"The Duskdune Shura were last seen on a road towards Sin Gerro."

"Sin Gerro?"

Not only Garen was surprised, Aris seemed taken aback as well.

"That one near Xi Fan Province..? That Sin Gerro?" Aris asked in a low voice.

"That’s the one."

"They’ve crossed the border, then.. Sin Gerro is pretty much half sealed up at the moment, it’s going to be tough; although the place is tiny, it’s rich with trade. It receives much more income than the federation" Aris said as she furrowed her eyebrows.

"I know of this, too." Garen nodded his head. "I’ve heard that Sin Gerro deals in ores and gems. To think the Duskdune Shura would bring the Golden Sword Throne to such a faraway place."

"The federation has assembled a small task force, codenamed Slash. Within it are people who are proficient against the Duskdune Shura. All of the experts in the southern region that we could gather have all been called together" Su Lin explained. "I have seen what the Grandmasters of Combat can do, so we’ve invited two of them into the force. One of them is from Crimson Sand Sword. Garen should have heard of them before."

"Oh? The Crimson Sand Sword? Could it be Beo?" Garen asked curiously.

"It is. One of the twin stars of the south, the strongest martial artist in the Crimson Sand Sword, surpassing even the Great Elder and Founder. Rumor says that he’s on par with Andrela." Su Lin nodded in agreement.

"And what of Andrela?" Garen asked, as he recalled the days fighting alongside that man with such talent.

"I heard that he had an epiphany after the match with you. He went deep into the mountains to further his training, and no one knows of his location at the moment. That guy is obsessed with martial arts, he’d stop at nothing to pursue it." Su Lin said, voice filled with emotion

"He’ll be at a different level once he resurfaces." Garen beamed with confidence. "I’ve learned a lot from that fight as well. If not, I wouldn’t have stood a chance against the Duskdune Shura in battle."

In actuality, Andrela was more talented than Garen was. If not for his own innate talent, he confessed that he would be no match against the rate at which he is improving.

"So where does Andrela stand among the Grandmasters of Combat?" Unaware of just how strong Andrela was, Garen took this opportunity to ask.

"I know this! I look up very highly to Master Andrela" Aris exclaimed, butting into the conversation. "I would have entered the Celestial Circle Gate if not for my love of the sword arts."

She cleared her throat.

"Master Andrela’s sword art has already far surpassed the Celestial Circle Gate’s elites, with the exception of Rolexia. As a Grandmaster of Combat, he is currently sitting well above average. To be precise, he is one of the best in this generation, save for the elites from the previous generation. Oh and of course, you’re currently the strongest Grandmaster of Combat in this generation Master Garen."

"What I wanted to know was against all of the Grandmasters of Combat, including the ones from the previous generation." Garen bellowed in laughter, shaking his head.

"Andrela. I met him a year ago."

Celine’s voice spoke up, from the side.

She gently closed the book in front of her and closed her eyes, as if reliving a memory.

"Even if the previous generations were included, his prowess is, without a doubt, one of the best. Assuming the Grandmasters of Combat are separated into four categories - Lower, Middle, Upper and First Class Ranks, he will probably stand at the edge of the Middle rank, skirting the Upper rank. He is climbing to the Duskdune Shura’s level at an incredible pace." Celine explained. "After that match with you, he would likely be at the Upper rank."

Garen’s heart leapt in his throat.

"Duskdune Shura… Is it even possible for a human to attain that kind of level?"

"It’s plausible. Duskdune Shura have been considered the pinnacle of martial arts for a long time. No one is stronger than them. Among us humans, they are known to be the best." Celine finished. Her gaze then fell on Garen, eyes brimming with emotion.

""Andrela is improving at an incredible rate. Aren’t you worried Garen?"

"What’s there to be worried about?" Garen asked, holding unease.

Celine’s lips curled into a sly smile.

"Your secret martial art but a low grade third rater - the White Cloud Mammoth. Under such a poor foundation, you’ve managed to reach a level so high that people have thought it impossible; but that’s the limit. There’s no way to get any better than you are now. Can you live with that?"

Everyone could read between the lines written by Celine. The duo became the focal point of the occupants in the room.

Garen was silent.

He knew; the White Cloud Secret Art had indeed reached its theoretical limit. He had stretched this secret technique to the extreme limit, so much so that even the founder of the White Cloud Gate himself was no match for him.

As he was now, he was imprisoned by his own secret technique.

Its grade was simply too low.

"If you had a higher level secret technique like Andrela of Celestial gate, you might be able to reach Duskdune Shura’s level as well." Celine’s voice had a slight tone of temptation.

"What are you trying to say" Garen looked at her calmly.

"Why not be the Dragon King of Protection of the Neptune Fist?" Celine smiled with cunning. "I can give you an even stronger secret technique."

Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

It was certainly a tempting prospect. A stronger secret technique would mean a brighter future.

However his mind was on the the promise between him and his teacher, Fei Baiyun. The White Cloud Gate had nurtured him, brought him where he was. With the Founder unconscious, he had a great responsibility upon him.

"I regret to say," Garen answered decidedly, "that I will not learn the Neptune Fist."

Chapter 138: Sin Gerro 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Celine’s face fell.

"My Neptune Fist is one of the best in the history! The secret techniques are ahead of its generation; the pinnacle of secret techniques! With the amount of talent you have, you can achieve what nobody has achieved before. You might even achieve what the Duskdune Shura are trying to obtain! I am giving you the opportunity to reach the pinnacle of martial arts, the opportunity to improve further from there onwards! You're not even considering it?!"

"Don’t waste your time. My mind is made." Garen replied flatly.

"Fine. You are still young anyway. There are plenty of chances to regret afterwards " Celine said in a low voice.

"Forget about the secret technique for a minute; when do you plan on leaving?" Su Lin asked.

Celine immediately looked elsewhere and whistled.

Su Lin immediately knew that this girl had taken fancy to this place, was trying to use it as a shelter.

"Celine." Garen’s deep voice boomed. "As the successor of the Neptune Fist, besides your own Neptune Fist, surely you know of other lower grade secret techniques right?"

"Low grade secret techniques? I know a whole bunch, why are you asking this?" Celine lowered her head and asked out of suspicion.

"Don’t you feel that you need to repay us somehow since you’re treating us as bodyguards right now?" Garen asked as he glanced at Su Lin, looking at him for support.

"Yeah that's right. We never agreed on letting you stay with us. You’ll only bring us trouble." Su Lin nodded repeatedly.

"If you do not want us to leave you behind when we’re in trouble, you should give us something in return, right?" Garen sneered.

"You want low grade secret techniques?" Celine asked. "Why do you need low grade secret techniques? What use are they?"

"I won’t object if you want to fork out secret techniques with higher grades, but would you want to? " Garen shrugged.

"Fine." Celine replied happily after some consideration. "What kind of secret techniques would you like? Of what type? I have quite a few secret techniques under my Neptune Fist. Let’s see what you have in mind."

"But I'll have to warn you first; once you've decided, a long period of time is required to master it. Your rate of progress will plummet once you reach the age of 25, and will only get harder from then on. You have to get the basics down pat first, before anything else. The higher the grade of secret technique the better it'll be for you, and the highest I have with me is the Neptune Fist Fundamental Secret Method." She added on.

"Your highest grade secret technique? Is it stronger than Master Andreas?" Aris asked out of curiosity.

"Definitely." Celine proudly replied. "In addition, I can only give one set to Su Lin and Garen. My Neptune Fist’s secret technique is not free after all."

"Fine. I want a secret technique that's based on hidden weapons." Su Lin voiced out immediately.

"I want one that is based on palm strikes." Garen added on.

"Hidden weapons and Palm Strikes? No problem." Celine nodded her head. "Have you made up your mind? This will be the compensation for protecting me and Erudas. You'd better be sure!"

"Of course." Su Lin answered without any hesitation.

Garen nodded in agreement as well.

"The grade better be good."

Celine nodded her head with some finality.

"Don’t worry, I will give you the basics first. I'll teach you guys the level 2 once you have mastered level 1. Figuratively speaking."

"Alright! Let’s do this now, since the Slash organization is set to leave this afternoon." Su Lin said as he couldn’t wait anymore.

"There’s no need to rush, I'm sure they won't be able to touch the Duskdune Shura even if they're there. He's on another level of cunning. I know a bit about him, and of the situation at hand. It’s most likely correct." Celine curled her lips as she explained. "I'll let you decide on the secret technique first. Alright, tell me what you'd like to learn. What path will you take?"

Half an hour later…

Both Garen and Su Lin went back to their own rooms and started packing for the trip with the task force.

On their hands were two pieces of paper, both packed to the brim with information on their respective secret techniques.

Garen half-sat, half-laid down on his bed, studying the first page of his paper on the first line, the name of the secret technique was written clear as day.

‘Red Jade Secret Method’

It was a full set, consisting of different kinds of palm strike techniques. It even had guidr to achieving the special effects of the secret technique.

It was similar to the Mammoth Secret Technique containing the White Cloud Combat Technique and Explosive Fist Arts. They come in a set.

Garen flipped to the annotation section in the last page.

‘The Red Jade Palm, once mastered, instills the palms with extreme heat. Combustion of any object is easily attainable when combined with proper palm techniques, an the heat of palms has very high penetration and is thus able to disrupt the temperature balance of the enemy’s body, killing the enemy silently.’

This Red Jade Palm was catalyzed off a subspecies of poisonous snake known as the fire jade snake. Its combat techniques were classified into wrapping, biting and twisting.

These three techniques were mainly used for evasion, attack and defense.

Garen gazed at the skill progression tree in front of him.

A technique from the Red Jad Palm had manifested on the paper.

‘Red Jade Palm: Not Learned (Three levels total) Requirement : Strength 0.7, Agility 1, Constitution 1.5, Intelligence 0.9. Requirement met. Do you want to learn this technique?’

"Looks like constitution is the main attribute for Red Jade Palm. One needs at least 1.5 in order to be eligible to learn it. In other words, only the trained professionals are eligible to practice this technique." Garen thought to himself.

Garen’s stared at the ‘yes’ symbol for 3 seconds as the notification to learn Red Jade Palm popped up.

With a searing zap, the symbol disappeared.

The paper that was in front of him had, like a scanner, been transferred into his head. His understanding of the technique rose in quick succession, as if he had been studying it for a long period of time.

"Alright then, let's start with the basic breathing technique!"

Breathing technique, specific posture and even musical rhythm were a must during practice for any secret technique. The higher grade secret techniques may even require external energy as a catalyst. The Red Jade Palm was considered to be a second rate secret technique that was a grade higher than the Mammoth secret technique. It was one Celine wracked her brains to pick; one that did not require any external support.

For all its advantage of not requiring a catalyst, it had one caveat: it was incredibly difficult to master.

This secret technique was the type that required some blood and sweat.

Garen calmly matched his breathing with the technique. Breathing rhythmically without pause, his huge lungs inhaling and exhaling large amounts of air. A hissing sound began to echo around the room. As if there were snakes in the room, poised to attack.

It was morning, and he needed to head down to Sin Gerro with the Slash task force to eliminate Duskdune Shura in the afternoon. Although Yoda would not be with them this time around, the line-up was still very impressive; much stronger than their previous attempt. Although Garen hadn’t seen Beo in action before, he knew that he was no ordinary Grandmaster of Combat. With them were 2 more Grade D professionals, who could go toe to toe with himself, as well as members of the international police. There were also some from the Special Agent along for the mission.

Garen confessed that with this line up, with Beo singlehandedly locking him in place, in addition to the sheer firepower within the team, even Garen would be humbled.

Now that he had obtained a new secret technique, one that is of a higher grade than his own Mammoth Secret Technique, training was imperative in increasing his power.

"Now if I had the Golden Sword Throne…" Garen’s eyes were brimming with energy. The Golden Sword Throne had become his number one priority, as it would greatly improve his physical attributes and technique levels at an incredible pace. It was a once in a lifetime opportunity!

********

Sin Gerro.

The Needle Green Pine Forest Ocean Park; a place covered in sweeping lands of greenery. In its center was an almost mirror-like pond, along with a river that partitioned the land with its meandering banks.

It was like drawing a landscape on a green coloured handkerchief

Within the forest lies a small, white road, penetrating through the forest. There was a signboard at the entrance, written in the Gerro language: Lake Road.

The center of the Lake Road was about 300 meters away from the entrance--

The sun blazed overhead, seeping through the cracks in the forest canopy, bathing swathes of land that littered across the uneven land in pillars of glorious sunlight.

Monochrome police cars were lined up in the forest clearing, flash lights in strobe; uniformed policemen were stringing a perimeter of yellow tape, and others were surrounding a deep crater at the center of the clearing. Camera flashes mimicked the police lights as flashes of strobe lights accompanied the shutter clicks of pictures being taken. Still others were furiously jotting down points on notebooks.

The sound of buzzing engines could be heard nearby, as another police car pulled up short of the yellow tape.

Three young policemen, two male and one female, exited the car with a rhythm of thumps of doors closing. They were dressed in plainclothes, the badges in their hands shining as they reflected off the sunlight.

"Officer Joseph from the Emergency Agent Department. These two are my colleagues. Please let us through."

The officers on duty looked at his police badge and immediately let him through, responding with an air of respect and reverence.

The man called Joseph was dressed in a black leather shirt. He had pale yellow skin, large eyes with thick eyebrows, and deep eye sockets typical of workaholics who work in the office. He bore a very stern look on his face.

He brought his colleagues toward the pit and knelt down to take a better look.

Inside the pit was the blurry outline of a male corpse, one half of its body nowhere to be found. It was as if something had torn it apart from its right shoulder to his right leg. Where his body would be, there was only soil, dyed red with blood.

"Identity of the deceased?" Joseph asked as he stood up.

"We’re still investigating. We can determine its identity by backtracking his time of arrival, and by matching his attire with ones of other places. However, we require more time." The policeman answered.

"Any witnesses?"

"None. It was as if there were wild animals moving about in the surrounding area. We think it was an attack by one of them."

Joseph massaged his own temple.

"Were there any forest rangers nearby?"

"Thomson has been looking. It might take a while for him to find one." The girl who came together with him spoke softly.

"This is the third incident within three days!" Joseph murmured.

"Are you ok, Joseph?" The girl beside him hugged him lightly and kissed him on the cheek.

"I’m alright, Annie." Joseph returned her kiss.

"Sir! I’ve found something!"

Joseph rushed to where the policeman was shouting; it was a green field under a big pine tree.

A white identity card sat serenely on the grass, unmoving.

Joseph knelt down, and wearing a rubber glove, picked the card up.

"Bring it back and perform a fingerprint scan."

"Yes sir."

Chapter 139: Tailing Behind 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was standing in the bedroom, his hands drawing circles slowly in the air, like he was stirring something.

Slowly, he pushes his hands out in front of him and halted. He kept his arms the moment both of his palms glowed a deep red.

"Success. The Red Jade Palm… What an incredible trick. I’ve the basics down, but for this to be used in combat still requires some practice. All I can do now is train."

Although he was among the ranks of the Grandmasters of Combat, making his combat skill far superior than that of a commoner, practice was still needed to bring the most out of any secret technique, especially in combat.

Garen relaxed his posture. He was excited to see what the Red Jade Palm would bring in the future.

He took a look at the skill progression tree again. The Dark Crimson Technique had disappeared as it was combined with the Red Jade palm.

‘Red Jade Palm: Learned (Level 1), Fire Strengthen Grade 1 (Dark Crimson Technique), Vitality Strengthen Grade 1 (Dark Crimson Technique)’

"How strong is the Red Jade Palm in combat, I wonder, on top of being enhanced by the Dark Crimson Technique." Garen slowly re-adjusted his blood flow, and released himself from the practicing state for the Red Jade Palm.

He never got a chance to use the enhanced Red Jade Palm during actual combat. However, he knew that his destructive power would definitely be much stronger than it was before. He had a hunch as to how powerful the Dark Crimson Technique was. He even had obtained a technique enhancement and another set of technique that had strong palm strikes, which was a higher grade than the White Cloud Combat Technique.

He still needed 0.3 Agility to be eligible for enhancement.

Garen could feel that his strength had increased. In the realm of the Grandmaster of Combat, most of them had already maximised their physical attributes, and it would be incredibly difficult to further them from then. In this realm, the difference between the strong and the weak were defined by the prowess of the technique, fighting state, experience and techniques. As the Grandmasters of Combat’s physical attributes required a certain quality to maintain at the highest level, they needed to spend a lot of time each day to maintain their body states. If they hadn’t put in the effort, their body attribution would without a doubt regress.

Only Garen, who had an almost terrifying innate talent, could prevent any regression on his physical attributes without training. He could even rely on these attribute points to reach peak physical state.

This was an almost unthinkable method of improvement.

The difference a small point of physical attribute would make to your physical abilities was massive. In the eyes of the Grandmasters of Combat, any small advantage was considered a gorge in terms of battle strength. These small differences could determine life and death, victory and defeat during battles.

What more, then, would 0.3 Agility points be!

Garen packed his shirt and gathered his thoughts, and, swinging the door open, went out of the room.

Nearby, Su Lin was talking to Yoda, his back resting against the corridor wall.

Celine was hitting Erudas with a stick as she was giving out instructions. For some reason, she seemed very interested in him.

"Ready?" Celine turned around and asked Garen.

"All set." Garen nodded his head. "But, are you going as well?"

"Of course. You guys won’t stand a chance capturing Duskdune Shura if I were absent. He’s not a simple as you might think." Celine replied.

"When are we moving?"

"We will let the people from Slash leave first." Celine glanced at Su Lin nearby.

A few people were going about with their business in the open lot beside the small building, as this was a rather large alley between the two buildings, it was repurposed as a small training ground.

After a while, footsteps of the soldiers and the humming of car engines could be heard coming from the manor.

Everyone stopped what they were doing and turned their attention to the manor, walking to the manor entrance, and into the garden driveway to see what was going on.

A large number of soldiers and military vehicles were being mobilized out of the manor, and at the center of the fully equipped military men stood a white vehicle.

At this moment, four people dressed in different attire boarded the vehicle, among the

four were martial artists, military officers, and the most eye catching of all of them was a young man with blue eyes, blue hair and even eyebrows.

This man was in blue attire and had a blue sword by his waist, as he gave off a cold and cruel aura.

Garen recognized him in an instant as he saw him.

"That’s Beo! He finally broke through! The last time I saw him he was still behind Andrela. He managed to do it in such a short time!" Garen was shocked.

"He’s still not as fast as you!" Su Lin shook his head. "Beo must have been agitated by you and Andrela. I heard that he wanted to challenge you after that duel you had, when the time was right. He obviously thinks that he’s still not strong enough to do it though, since he hasn’t approached you even though he knows that you’re here."

"Which means that when he challenges me, he’ll believe himself to be above Andrela then." Garen said softly.

"He’s not called the number one martial artist from the south in this generation for no reason. You’d better not take other challengers lightly." Su Lin said as he looked at Garen.

"Please lead the way, Celine since you said you know where to find the Duskdune Shura." Garen told Celine.

Celine frowned at the Slash team, as if deep in thought.

"There’s no need to rush. We’ll follow them from afar. This is considered a personal investigation since we are separated from the team, we have freedom of movement. I’m sure those two generals know, and agreed to this. They obviously want to have us as an insurance since we will be in the dark from all these parades. Plus we have Garen if all else fails.

"That’s alright, I’ll leave it up to you then." Garen said as he shrugged his shoulders.

"The only problem is, what should we do if we meet Duskdune Shura again?" Su Lin asked with some apprehension.

"Let me handle it when it comes to that" Garen added. "I’ve learnt a lot after the match with him the last time. We should be fine as long as we don’t get hit by his Seven Dragon Gate Combo."

"Indeed." Celine nodded her head in affirmation. The party looked at the car slowly leaving the manor. Only when it could no longer be seen did they start for their own journey.

"Alright, it’s our turn to move out. Be careful if you meet Duskdune Shura. We’re not here to have a death match with him."

"That we’ll be sure to do. Alright. I’ll go and prepare us a car and we’ll head straight for the airbase."

Su Lin was the first to exit, followed by Garen with Celine on his shoulder.

Only Yoda and Aris were left to note their departure. Aris’ eyes gleamed with a hint of worry.

"Brother is the weakest among them all. Why did he want to go and join in the fun?"

Yoda smiled, "Don’t worry. Although Su Lin lacks strength when up against a Grandmaster of Combat, but he is considered a very strong opponent for a commoner. And with a trump card up his sleeve, he’s not to be trifled with."

"A trump card?" Aris looked at Yoda curiously.

"In the words of some, he is a talented person…" Yoda replied.

**********

13th May 2987

Sin Gerro - Pinehill City

One day later…

Bang!

In the meeting room in Pinehill City, Beo, his face full of rage, slammed his palm onto the desk. His equally fiery eyes were staring at the cops in the room.

"Let the people in this room be my witnesses," Beo said word by word. "There will be a big incident tonight!"

"Please calm down Beo." A middle-aged police officer who was sitting in the master seat said. "We don’t have any evidence or any clues, and you want us to approve mobilization of the special forces to lock down the central building? You have to understand that that area is the Pinehill City’s central. It would affect the whole city if there were any movement there! This is no child’s play!"

"Executive Jayne, I…"

"Save it, Beo. I know you’re talented, but you are clearly being too rash about this incident. I think you should take some rest, since you’ve lost your cool over these three cases." Officer Jayne said flatly, before standing up to leave the meeting room.

Tch.

A fat, white policeman opposite of Joseph stood up and glanced sideways at him, as if he wanted to burst out laughing.. "Don’t be angry now, Sir Joseph."

Others in the room laughed and shook their heads.

"A murder in the central building? Hah! This is the funniest thing I’ve heard this year." A tall and lanky policeman sneered at officer Joseph as he walked past.

Soon, Joseph is the only one left in the meeting room.

He stood, fists clenched, silent without a word.

"Remember, Joseph. You’re different from the others. The world you see is much more than the others. That is your ability… It is the ability of the Hilarita Household."

Grandfather’s last words appeared in his mind once more.

"Listen closely… close your eyes.. and listen… those words in the night…" Grandfather’s weak yet firm speech echoed in his mind once more.

.

"Joseph unconsciously closed his eyes and listened closely with his ears.

Ding…. Ding Dang… Ding… Ding Dang…

The sound of a gramophone in the distance floated into his ears. Along with it came sounds from the gentle breeze and leaves rustling outside… the low rumble of a car engine, footsteps along the corridor. He could even hear the sound of his own breathing, his heartbeat, blood circulating in his veins.

Joseph focused on his hearing, and slowly, his surroundings drowned into the background, with the exception of a piece of soft music.

The muddy music started to clear up, and the static within came along with it, louder and louder, louder and louder.

Bzz... Bzz Bzz… Bzz… Bzz Bzz…

"That’s...." Joseph furrowed his eyebrows.

The music faded into another piece once again. A small, hushed voice emerged from deep within the static, having a conversation with itself.

Bzz.. Ahh!!... Bzz Bzz… My beloved… Dear.. Bzz.. Come to my side… No!!... My love… Bzz…

The rather sweet conversation had suddenly turned into a bloodcurling scream. It was inexplicably strange.

Joseph was drenched in cold sweat. He opened his eyes, and a girl with a pale face was staring at him.

Woah!!

He was so startled that he took two steps back. He blinked, and then in front of him was nothing but a quiet, empty room.

He almost fell on the chair, his hands running through his hair. After a few lungfuls of air, he shook his head in disbelief

"She’s going to appear whenever you close your eyes. That’s the price you pay for listening…" He spoke softly to himself.

He quickly stood up, grabbed the dossier on the table and stormed out the meeting room.

He couldn’t idle by and let a tragedy occur.

Even if no one were to support him, he still had two of his colleagues!

Chapter 140: Tailing Behind 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Click!

Joseph, loaded the gun, a look of determination on his face.

"We need to stop them! They are planning to hold a grand hunting ceremony tonight at midnight sharp. We have to be there before then or else the whole Pinehill City will be in danger!"

Under the yellow lighting of the basement, there were two others, one female and the other male, armed with guns looking at Joseph.

"Have you gone nuts, Joseph!!" Johnson’s eyes were filled with both shock and worry. "The central building will be fine. The police have already sent people there in case anything would happen…"

"Listen, my partner!" Joseph raised a hand to his shoulder. "Do you trust me?" He stared directly into Johnson’s eyes.

"Of course! We’ve been by each other since we were kids, and you’re the best friend I have!" Johnson replied with affirmation

"No one believed me! Not a single one!" Joseph took a big breath. "I know this is absurd. I beg you Johnson, my best friend, and Annie, my beloved! Just for this night. We need to stop them tonight!"

"Stop what?" Annie butted in. "I believed in you Joseph but what can we do for you?!" Her eyes overwhelmed with worry and love. "You’re not shouldering this on your own! You still have us!"

Joseph took in a few lungfuls of air and whipped out three small brown leather pouches from his waist. He gave everyone one each.

"Bring this with you! Remember that! Do not let this pouch leave your side no matter the reason! Bring it with you whenever and wherever! Do not lose the pouch! The enemy we’re facing is nothing like we have ever faced before! No one can go against them without this!"

"What is this"? Annie asked as she shook the pouch. She could barely hear some water sloshing inside.

"This is holy water. We can restrain them with it. If we have this with us, they’ll be weakened if they come within 10 meters.. Please do not leave this without you at all cost! Please!"

"Are we entering some horrifying Sci-Fi novel?" Johnson joked. "Do you need me to gather a few more people? My cousin is a professional boxer! Ameteur level six! He’s the local’s boxing association’s vice president, too!"

"It’s no good. I’ve tried getting help from others but it’s no use." Joseph shook his head. "They’re not human…" A bead of cold sweat escaped his brow as he recalled the scene.

Annie and Johnson looked at each other; they both knew, from Joseph’s voice, the pain he was in.

*************

Hum…

It was the afternoon, and the sky was grey and cloudy.

The green mountains and hills covered the landscape like a carpet, and in between was a river flowing freely, just like yellow silk across the land, stretching to the distance.

A white, four-winged plane glided serenely above the greenery, its engine producing an incessant rumbling sound.

The airplane flew over a waterfall at the river mouth; the roar of water crashing into the valley below echoed above, shooting large amounts of vapor so high it seemed like it could brush the plane’s bottom hull.

The airplane’s side door was ajar and in it was Garen, wearing a T-shirt and jeans, looking at the river below.

"Where is this?" He asked loudly.

The pilot was, surprisingly, Su Lin. He had styled his fiery red hair into ordinary bangs, and he had a golden earring on one of his ears. He was whistling a melody that was slightly off beat.

"We’re just outside Sin Gerro. There’s a private rest stop half an hour away from here and we can take a rest there, and at the same time refuel the plane."

"It’s so beautiful…" Celine looked down at the giant waterfall from the other door. "Is this the Great Waterfall Shifariya? The one located on the borderline of the Federation and Sin Gerro?"

"That’s the one. Based on our current speed, we still have about three hours before we reach the place Duskdune Shura was last seen; Black Rock City." Su Lin replied.

"You don’t have to come with us, you know. This operation is highly dangerous." Garen said as he looked at Su Lin.

"Don’t worry. Don’t you look down on me. Although I’m not as strong as you, I’ve no problem running away when my life is in danger!" Su Lin smiled, rows of white teeth lining his mouth.

"I can smell the scent of the Slash team." Celine twitched her nose and said suddenly, "It’s fresh; the Slash team left was less than half an hour ago. They should have taken off again based on the height of the smell. Judging from the timeline of our path, they should havetook off from the place Su Lin mentioned, 30 degrees North East from us."

Su Lin whistled and said. "Are you that accurate? Looks like the puppies ought to be ashamed!"

"Go to hell!!" Celine shouted in anger as she choked Su Lin by his neck.

The airplane jerked up and down violently for a moment.

Garen shook his head calmly throughout the exchange, choosing to remain silent.

Since their journey from the manor, Su Lin and Garen witnessed Celine’s true ability. She had an amazing sense of smell.

Celine had memorized the scent of all the members of Slash and Duskdune Shura, hence there was no need for them to tail the team from behind too tightly. She could smell them as long as they were not an hour or a specific distance apart from each other. In addition, they also knew the Slash team’s route, so it was impossible to lose them.

As Garen had gotten tired of the view below, he closed his eyes and started his breathing technique for the Red Jade Palm, and begun his practicing his secret technique once more.

If he could obtain more attribute for the Red Jade Palm he had learnt yesterday, he could greatly enhance the effect of the Red Jade Palm to an unimaginable level. This was the only thing Garen was excited about.

Recently, he realized that superimposing low grade secret techniques was not necessarily a good thing.

He managed to obtain another secret technique, be it the lowest grade, from Celine. It was a secret technique that involved kicking. Regrettably, this secret technique required a body with high flexibility. Although Garen had learnt the technique, it was merged together with the Mammoth Secret Technique and there has been no change since.

He suspected that it was because these two techniques were of opposite nature, or most of the techniques were the same, which had no help to the Mammoth Secret Technique.

Garen then went to Celine again and ask for secret techniques that were body enhancement in nature but to no avail. There were little secret techniques that did not require external assistance. It was impressive of her to be able to recall so many from her memory. Garen had no choice but to go inquire about one at the Southern Sky Holy Fist headquarter.

"But before all that, I need to obtain the Golden Sword Throne." Garen eyes were brimming with fire. "The Golden Sword Throne is useless to most people since it would lose its primary purpose upon usage. I might be able to get my hands on it when the Slash team is dealing with Duskdune Shura. But first..."

He clapped his palms and they were bright red for an instance.

"I have finally learnt the Red Jade Palm. With the body enhancement from the Mammoth Secret Technique and the effects from the Red Jade Palm, I really want to know which one is stronger when we clash, my Mammoth Secret Technique with the Red Jade Palm or your Seven Dragon Gate!" It was without a doubt tempting to every fighter to challenge a Grandmaster of Combat of the highest level from the previous generation.

A fighter’s aim was to be able to improve, to evolve and constantly challenge the limit of one’s own body. This was what it meant to be a true fighter.

Garen was no different. There were too little people who could go up against him, and Duskdune Shura had showed him the power of the ancient and mysterious secret technique, the Seven Dragon Gate.

As both of them were strong in body hardening technique, Duskdune Shura had a much softer strike than his. Although the Seven Dragon Gate was not that strong, the crazy ability to stiffen others was definitely the big killer.

Garen’s main plan was to go head to head with the Duskdune Shura. He wanted to see how strong his Mammoth Secret Technique’s maximised body hardening technique superimposed with the Red Jade Palm and the enhancement of the Dark Crimson Technique was. Furthermore, he had added 0.3 agility points into his attribution. Garen clearly felt that he could keep up with Duskdune Shura’s attacks now.

Duskdune Shura’s attack was not considered fast among the Grandmaster of combats. He didn’t have strong powers and high defense as well. However, as every aspect of his attributions were moulded together, it reached such a perfect balance that there were practically no flaw in it.

He was faster than the strength based fighter, and stronger than a agility based one. He also had techniques that could bypass any defense.

However, no matter how strong he was, he was too old to fight for any extended period of time. Even in this state, Garen was not confident that he could win against his opponent. He wouldn’t dare to fight against Duskdune Shura if Celine hadn’t taught him a little trick to counter the Seven Dragon Gate.

Half an hour later…

The white airplane descended slowly as it landed on a strip of parking apron caked with mud. It slipped on the brown mud for a few hundred meters before finally coming to a stop.

The airplane’s propeller spun its final rotations with a whiz before coming to a halt.

The parking apron was a gigantic reddish brown circle. Soldiers in dark green uniforms came rushing into it to the airplane. One of the soldiers had a small notebook on his hand and he seemed to be noting down the airplane’s serial number of sorts.

Another soldier dismounted his horse, and hurried the still running soldiers rushing to the plane.

"Sir, how much fuel do you need?" He ask Garen, who jumped off from the airplane.

"Ask the person behind me. I know nothing about these things." Garen shrugged his shoulders.

Su Lin was the next one who jumped down from the plane.

"Glenz number 7, max it out as, we will be heading off shortly. Do you have any food here?"

"Definitely, but we only have local dishes here." The soldiers grinned as he rubbed his hands and said, "We can find a couple of native girls as well..."

"Native? Are there still native people here?" Celine jumped down from the airplane shortly after as she combed her long hair.

"Yes. The Surian Forest is huge, and there are a lot of primitive tribes living in it. We managed to capture a few native women…" The soldier shut his mouth up as soon as he saw the little girl.

"I will go and settle the preparations..." He smiled embarrassedly and turned away.

Su Lin nodded his head as he looked at the soldier walked away.

"This parking apron is built by Sin Gerro and the Edge Security Company. It looks quite fancy here."

Garen looked at Celine.

"What , have you notice anything?"

Celine looked confused as her nose twitched again.

"They’ve separated."

"Which direction?" Garen asked further.

"Slash and Duskdune Shura have separated. Both of them are heading to different locations." Celine looked up at Garen’s face. "Who should we follow?"

This was the time for the strongest, Garen, to lead the team.

Su Lin looked at Garen, as if he wanted him to make the decision as well.

"We’ll follow Duskdune Shura." Garen hadn’t expected this at all. He took a deep breath and said, "The Slash team will definitely realize this sooner or later. We will definitely gather together if we follow Duskdune Shura now."

Both Celine and Su Lin agreed to his proposal.

"Let’s move once we had something to eat and finish refuelling" Su Lin immediately arranged the plan. "Let’s catch up to Duskdune Shura before the sun sets."

"Is that even possible?" Garen looked at him skeptically.

"No problem! This plane is my beloved limited edition collective series number 1043,

Daphne!" Su Lin’s smile was so bright that even his teeth peeked out from behind his lips.

"How many limited edition items do you have?" Garen was speechless.

"This will never be revealed to the public, just like a girl’s age." Su Lin patted his shoulder as he walked towards the row small houses next to the parking apron.

"Are you guys going to call some girls later?" Celine asked Garen.

"Yes…"

"Give me two of them as well."

Garen was lost for words as he looked at Celine, who then jumped onto Su Lin’s shoulder.

"Just joking. Haha…" Celine burst out in laughter the moment she was far enough away from Garen.

Hopeless, Garen started in the same direction.

Chapter 141: Night 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After filling up their stomachs and the fuel, Garen and the team continued their journey tracking Duskdune Shura through his scent.

The White airplane flew above the sea of a forest for at least 2 hours until a white road could finally be seen. The number of lanes gradually increased until it’s so complex that it looked like a spider web.

The sky was slowly getting darker.

The plane descended slowly as it followed the directions from the airport’s control tower and approached a gray, oval-shaped airport.

"This is the place. Duskdune Shura landed here!" Celine said with affirmation.

Garen and Su Lin looked down at the airport and saw seven to eight airplanes of different sizes parked. Four of them were a small airplanes, one of them was pure blue in color whereas the rest were either brown or white.

Celine pointed at the blue airplane.

"That’s the plane. He must have left less than half an hour ago!"

"Let’s land here and we will tail him right away!" Garen said.

Without any hesitation, Su Lin quickly lowered the plane. At the same time, there were already people at the airport waving a white flag to indicate the landing position to Su Lin.

******

Sin Gerro

In the forest of the Pinehill City’s suburbs.

Night.

Noises among the trees could be heard periodically coming from the forest. An owl’s hoot came from the distance and the crescent moon was silently sitting in the sky, bathing the place in soft moonlight.

The dark green pine trees stood as tall as towers. Even the shortest one was about twenty to thirty meters. They stood pencil straight, like sticks potruding from the earth.

Although it was very spacious between the pine trees, the whole area was covered with dense, greenish yellow weeds.

Inside the forest, there were three dark figures wandering about carefully, going deeper in.

"Be careful, hold my hand Annie. And don’t step there! You’ll leave a footprint." A male voice whispered.

"Joseph, what does this place have to do with the incident at central building?" Another man out of the three figures asked.

"We can’t stop them if we don’t come here." Joseph looked his partners and continued, "The beasts will perform a hunting prayer, and the central building is the location for the hunting ceremony! We need to destroy their altar after they leave this place!"

"Altar?"

"Yes. Their ritual will be broken once the altar is no more. Hence it would be meaningless for them to keep hunting!" Joseph said with confidence, although his voice was shivering.

Annie held his hand tightly.

"Don’t worry Joseph, we will be fine…"

In truth, Annie and Johnson did not believe anything about the hunt or the prayers. They only believed in Joseph and followed his leadership. Although they didn’t believe in the beasts, they knew something was going to happen, looking at Joseph how sure Joseph was.

This was because Joseph was different, he was special.

Hoo!!

Out among the dense forest, a bonfire emerged in the spacious clearing between the pine trees. There was a big cattle skull on top of the bonfire. It was about for to five meters high and three two four meters wide. It seemed to be created from a multitude of bones.

The bonfire was getting stronger and stronger, it was so huge that the flame shot almost three meters high. There were fuzzy figures surrounding the bonfire; tanned male and females who were tall and muscular.

The males were bare from the waist up, whereas the females had a black cloth covering the chest. They wore black jeans below their waist, where long hairs spread wildly. Black marks could also be seen on their face.

The fierce fire reflected a similar expression on each of them. They took turns stabbing their own arms with a small knife, and smeared their blood gently onto their face.

After they had finished smearing their faces.

"It has been five centuries since the hunting tradition had been passed down before us." An old man who stood by the bonfire whispered. "Do not forget our ancestor’s pride. Remember what I have just said."

"Elder, where are the damned hound bugs? I smelled their scent behind earlier." A strong man with braided hair asked.

"They have left, which is why I took this opportunity to organize the hunt, so that we will not be disturbed." The elder replied.

"I would have killed all of them if not for the holy water! These damn bugs!" The braided man replied gloomily.

"Who is it!! Who’s there!" The Elder’s nose twitched as he smelled something. His head was facing at where Joseph and his two colleagues were hiding.

Bam!

A gunshot rang across the forest.

One of the figure beside the bonfire went down, but the rest of them spread out and came running towards them.

Bam Bam Bam!!

Three more gunshots were heard. However, it hadn’t come from Joseph’s party, but from the other side of the forest. In an instant, more than ten people with black coats came rushing out of the forest.

In their hand were hand grenades. In quick, swift motions, they kept throwing the grenades towards the bonfire.

Boom~~~!!!

The man who was initially shot stood back up all of a sudden, as his body started sprouting large amounts of black fur. In a blink of an eye, it had became a humongous wolf. The black wolf howled and ran towards the people with black coat in a rage

The crack of gunshots rang again and again, but the black wolf managed to dodge a lot of the bullets.

Ah!!

One of the man with the black coat was taken down as half of his body was ripped apart by the black wolf’s claw. As the wolf sunk his teeth into his victim, the man’s grey matter was torn open.

Soon, chains of howls rose through the forest floor. The remaining people near the bonfire had transformed into werewolves, and all of them rushed towards the men black.

"Damn! It’s the Thukk Tribe!!" The leader of the black coat panicked slightly.

Soon more people in black were shredded into pieces by the werewolves. At the same moment, others started screaming as black smoke rose from their bodies. They shrivelled and dried rapidly; some fell off and died with teeth still sunk deep into flesh, and became a puddle of black water.

"It’s the Thukk Tribe! Everybody retreat!!" The leader of the black coat started to panicked as he shouted. They hadn’t enough holy water. The Thukk Tribe is much more resistant to the holy water compared to other similar species. The amount of holy water needed to purify one Thukk Tribe members could purify three other ordinary werewolves. These beasts’ true potential would be unleashed once there was no holy water nearby. They would be twice as strong! The Thukk Tribe was unstoppable once they were not restricted.

"Retreat! Retreat!" The group of men in black fired their guns as they stumbled backwards Under the lead of the braided werewolf, werewolves continued their onslaught. Both parties were at war inside the Pine forest with both parties sustaining heavy casualties.

*******

On the other side of the pine forest.

Garen and Su Lin were following Celine closely as they moved deeper into the forest. If not for the night sky, the three of them would have looked like tourists with their attire.

Celine kept sniffing with her nose as she lead the way.

"Duskdune Shura went through this place. He must be right in front of us."

"You have brought us through a lot of detours already. We’ll go directly to the Ancient Ruins tomorrow if we can’t find him." Su Lin yawned as he replied.

"Absolutely not. We will definitely lose him if we don’t can’t find him now. I wasn’t sure at first, but I’m confident to say that Duskdune Shura is definitely not heading to the Ancient Ruins. He had other objectives!" Celine affirmed.

"Other objectives?" Garen was confused.

"There’s someone in front!" Celine lowered down her voice as she focused ahead.

A man with a black coat walked towards them slowly out of the darkness..

"Who are you people? Up ahead is a protected area of the national security agency. You may not enter." The man said as he furrowed his eyebrows.

Garen and the rest were skeptical. Garen kept took a stepped in front as Celine and Su Lin slowly backed off.

"Did you not hear what I just said? It’s very dangerous up front! You may not proceed any further! And you! You too! Leave this place immediately!" The man in black coat said to the big pine tree in front of Garen and his gang.

A humanoid figure slowly came out from the branches of the pine tree. His gaze was calmly focused onto Garen and the gang.

Garen and the gang stared back at him in the same manner.

THe four of them did not bother to pay any heed towards the arrogant man in the black coat, as all of their attention was now focused on each other.

"You people are persistent." Duskdune Shura spoke under his cloak. His voice was hoarse and deep.

"Hand over the Golden Sword Throne. Though I know that’s probably not happening, I’ll say it anyway" At this moment Garen had became the leader of the three man group as his vision was tightly locked onto Duskdune Shura.

This man had once defeated two generals from the federation when he was heavily surrounded. He was the at the pinnacle of strength, being able to escaped from an ambush from all directions.

Although he had became stronger, he did not dare underestimate his enemy.

"You’re here for the Golden Sword Throne as well?" Duskdune Shura was amused, "Do you think you can stop me all by yourself?"

"I won’t know if I don’t try." Garen replied.

"Hmph!"

Duskdune Shura sighed before he pointed his toes and swiftly leapt backwards, disappearing into the darkness.

Garen immediately went after him. With his speed increased by 0.3 points, he was as fast as Duskdune Shura.

Celine and Su Lin were not slow either. They followed Garen closely from behind and disappeared into the darkness with him

The man with the black coat was left alone in the dark, in a rage.

"A trained fighter? Does being a fighter make you all that? This is no longer my business. You guys are the one who did not heed my warning. Even a fighter would have the same fate if you do not have holy water! These beasts had already killed dozens of fighters! You guys are digging your own grave!"

*************

Deep inside the Pine Forest.

Joseph’s party watched the battle between the men in black and wolves in terror. Blood was shed from both parties. It was a scene of horror. This was especially so for Johnson and Annie, having not seen anything like this in their lives. They were so rooted in fear they failed to move even an inch from where they were.

"Jo..Joseph.. Tell me… What… What is going on?? Am I dreaming?" Johnson stuttered as he asked.

"This is reality Johnson. If I’m not mistaken, these men in black coat are there Demon Hunters. The enemy they are facing now are the legendary werewolf clan."

Chapter 142: Night 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Werewolves!" Annie and Johnson had thought about that possibility, but it was still hard for them to accept that fact.

"Werewolves are strong and resilient, and their ability to kill is terrifying. Humans were once their slaves in the Ancient Era, and were only kept as livestock. That is until we discovered Holy Water." Joseph explained, "Holy Water greatly weakens the werewolves, reducing their strength and vitality to a level us humans can handle."

"You mean… this?" Annie held up the pouch Joseph gave her earlier.

"Yes, that’s it, keep it safe. Now that you’ve seen all these, won’t you believe me?" Joseph wanted to let his close friend and girlfriend truly believe in him. Only after seeing it with their own eyes will they believe in something this ridiculous. The Demon Hunters1; well, that was a coincidence.

"The strength of humanity comes from our ability to utilize tools." Joseph whispered, "Okay, now that the Demon Hunters are here, we should retreat."

It was Johnson and Annie’s first encounter with so many corpses at the same place, both of them were pretty shaken up, so they didn’t protest.

Slowly, the trio started pulling back.

In that exact moment, a silhouette charged past them toward the battlefield between the werewolves and the Demon Hunters.

In the blink of an eye, another silhouette chased after the first one, dashing past the three.

"You want the Golden Sword Throne? You’ll have to catch me!" A deep, gravelly voice challenged. It was from the first silhouette.

"Hmph!" The second silhouette snorted with disdain, then accelerated abruptly.

"Oh? You’re faster than the last time we met!" The man with the gravelly voice had a hint of surprise.

Joseph and his companions looked on, stunned by the two silhouettes who rushed toward the battlefield.

"Are they Demon Hunters too?" Johnson asked, as softly as he could.

"No, they’re not. They don’t have the fragrance of Holy Water on them! They are human fighters." Joseph furrowed his eyebrow.

Arooooooooo!

A werewolf with black fur howled and glared at the newcomers, Duskdune Shura and Garen.

"Fighters? Heh heh, I haven’t had fighter flesh for a long while now! You must have a death wish to come near here without Holy Water." The werewolf blitzed toward the two fighters.

In the same moment, Garen caught up with Duskdune Shura.

They collided and dashed forward together.

Thud!

Garen parried Duskdune Shura’s attack with his arm.

"Single Shot Form! Swing!" Garen shot his right arm, aiming at Duskdune Shura’s chest, like a cobra lunging for its prey. As soon as he closed in, Garen’s arm jerked upward into Swing Form, stabbing at Duskdune Shura’s chin with five fingers kept straight in the shape of a cleaver.

Slap!

Duskdune Shura diverted the attack with a slap, and returned an attack with his other palm, to which Garen met with his own.

Thud!

Garen grunted and fell back, just as the black-furred werewolf pounced at him in a bloodlust.

"Out of my way!"

Thud! Rip!

The black-furred werewolf was torn into two halves, spilling blood all around the ground. Without wasting a breath, Garen rushed at Duskdune Shura again.

A sound of a heavy thump echoed. Both Garen and Duskdune Shura landed on a patch of grass. After regaining their balance, they hacked at each other again, echoing thuds and thumps and thwacks, like the sound of shotgun blasts reverberating throughout the woods.

The battle between Demon Hunters and werewolves was stopped by the two newcomers in the centre. There were stray bullets that hit both of them, but every single bullet was repelled, creating golden sparks.

Every creature around the area was astonished beyond comprehension.

The werewolves stopped attacking, as did the Demon Hunters. Including Joseph’s group, all three parties were blankly staring at Garen and Duskdune Shura’s fight.

The two people in combat ignored everyone else, fully focusing on attacking each other. Whatever that got in their way was destroyed.

One by one, pine trees thicker than a human’s embrace fell, leaving behind holes and craters of different sizes, as if it had been hit by bombs.

Thwack!

A figure got hit and swooped across a tiny glade, only dissipating his momentum after he hit another pine tree. It was Garen. His shirt was torn and shredded, and even the trunk of the pine tree he landed on cracked, but he looked as if he wasn’t hurt at all.

Scoffing defiantly, Garen leapt toward his opponent. The two engaged in another round of combat.

Whenever Garen hit anything, he would leave behind rips and intense shaking, meanwhile Duskdune Shura would slash everything he touched in half. When they clashed, it’s as if they were armored to the teeth, wielding extraordinary weapons of their own.

"Excellent! You deserved your title as the Champion of the era! I approve of your strength." Duskdune Shura leapt backward and landed softly on a fallen tree trunk more than ten meters away.

"If you want the Golden Sword Throne, come to the Dahl Falls. I will be waiting for you there."

"Don’t you dare run away!" Garen’s eyes was wild with excitement. During his battle with Duskdune Shura, he felt his mastery over Red Jade Palm growing. If he had continued using it for the fight, he has no doubt he can master it in no time. Granted, the fact that he had affinity to special abilities on top of his understanding in Grandmaster of Combat techniques helped, but undeniably, only actual combat experience can deepen his mastery over combat abilities.

Without hesitation, he dashed toward his enemy.

Duskdune Shura promptly dropped into the crowd of werewolves.

Whack! A soft clap.

A werewolf stumbled out toward the pursuing Garen. Even he was in bewilderment about his action.

Wham!

The werewolf was whipped away with a Swing Form and fell at least ten meters away, half his body was torn apart, leaving his flesh and blood in a gory mess. The werewolf could only whimper on the ground.

The werewolves, and even some of the Demon Hunters shuddered.

"Do you really think you can stop me with this pile of garbage?" Garen had a flash of fury in his eyes.

Garbage?!

"How dare you!" The werewolves, and even the elder werewolf was angered by this show of arrogance. "Without Holy Water, you are but-"

He couldn’t finish his sentences as Garen shot him a glare. He only felt a pressure made of fear forced upon him.

Garen’s eyes flashed red, the space around him bent, unfolding a gigantic red-eyed mammoth tens of meters tall. The air around him wheezed loudly, as if it was going to swallow everything within dozens of meters.

The elder werewolf turned pale and trembled uncontrollably, unable to hold his werewolf state, he collapsed on the ground kneeling.

"We are… the great… Thukk Tribe!" The elder struggled, trying to stand up, but he couldn’t move a single hair. His bones cracked under the pressure.

To other people, Garen only glanced over at the elder, and he immediately reverted to human form and kneeled on his own, as if he’s being bound by some invisible force. He looked like he’s trying to get up but completely lost his strength.

Duskdune Shura hid underneath his cloak, shielding his facial expression. He kept lobbing werewolves after werewolves toward Garen, like they were cargo unworthy of cautiousness. At the same time, he’s swiftly retreating from the battlefield area.

Thud! Thud! Thud!

Garen kept swatting werewolves aside, growling, trying to give chase, but at critical moments another werewolf would appear in his path, significantly slowing him down. In addition to that, he was already slightly slower than Duskdune Shura. It wasn’t long before Duskdune Shura completely disappeared into the darkness.

"Grr!" Garen hit a tree with his palm out of frustration. The trunk crackled, and without a warning, wooden slag started pouring out as though it was sand. A white notch appeared on the thick tree trunk where Garen hit it, and it started to lean toward the other direction and fell with a loud bang.

Most of the Thukk Tribe was hurt in Garen’s pursuit of Duskdune Shura. As werewolves, they have accelerated healing, so by now, some of the lightly wound had already healed. Silently, they retreated to the far end of the woods, taking the elder werewolf and the bodies of the other werewolves with them.

At some point during the chaos, Celine and Su Lin sneaked beside Joseph’s party, stayed till the aftermath of the battle.

Gawking at Garen from afar, Su Lin smiled wryly. "Garen is even stronger than before, he wasn’t that fast just a while ago."

"He’s a monster!" Celine is speechless.

"Duskdune Shura seemed to have acknowledged Garen’s capability as a fighter; none of them used their full power though. Who would win if they did, I wonder?" Su Lin shook his head.

Joseph and his companions dared not move, in case they were found out by the two newcomers. They were so shocked at overhearing Su Lin, Joseph even swallowed his saliva.

"If this isn’t their full power, what is?"

Joseph lightly kneaded the water pouch they brought, questioning the truth of the world for the first time.

"Didn’t granddad say it was impossible for humans to fight the evil creatures without Holy Water? Was I hallucinating or has the world gone mad?"

"You three have been observing for a while, didn’t you? Don’t you want to come out and say hi?" Su Lin turned toward Joseph unexpectedly with a knowing smile.

Most citizens from Sin Gerro and some smaller countries around it commonly use the Confederation language, barring some minute differences in accents and dialects. To be more precise, the Confederation language is the lingua franca of the whole Stonecliff Continent.

Joseph finally stood up, forcing a smile to his face. Johnson and Annie followed.

Once Garen accepted the fact that he wouldn’t be able to keep up with Duskdune Shura, he unwillingly turned back heading toward Su Lin.

He wasn’t expecting to keep Duskdune Shura down anyway, he just wanted to test his improvement in his fighting ability.

As he thought, if he weren’t using the first and second stages of Body Hardening Technique, instead relying only on his normal state to fight Duskdune Shura, he would have been at a disadvantage, but not hurt. Red Jade Palm made up for the weakness in his fighting technique. Even if he couldn’t use the more precise skills during the fight, he was starting to get a grasp on the technique used against him.

Frankly speaking, if he decided to kill Garen, Duskdune Shura would not be able to get away unscathed.

Duskdune Shura was also aware of this fact, which is why he left as soon as possible.

More importantly, Garen finally confirmed that the Golden Sword Throne was indeed with Duskdune Shura, as well as the many potential uses the Antique of Tragedy has! Garen completely verified that in this battle.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Translator’s Notes

1 猎魔人 lit. people who hunt demons/magic depending on context. I’d say this is about Demon Hunters

Chapter 143: Coincidence 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen restrained his overflowing Bravery and returned to Su Lin with haste.

"He’s truly a Master, that Duskdune Shura, even at my current level, I still can’t beat him." He sighed, "Oh right, what were those monsters called? Werewolves?"

"They are. Have you seen them around?" Joseph answered timidly. His two companions were so intimidated by Garen’s show of power, they subconsciously took a step back.

Garen quickly scanned through the three strangers slightly warily. He was going to question them when Su Lin interrupted and introduced them.

"They were going to launch a sneak attack on the werewolves’ altar to prevent them from completing the hunting ritual. These people were innocent."

"Werewolves? They really are werewolves?" Garen’s eyebrows furrowed. Now that he knows werewolves exist, it would be a sensible opinion to conclude that vampires and other evil creatures exist as well. If vampires exist, what could be next? Holy churches like in those fantasy novels and movies on Earth?

A series of thoughts came to him almost simultaneously. Back on Earth, he has had his fair share of movies consumption.

"What? Have you met them before?" Joseph was slightly taken aback by Garen’s seeming nonchalance. He still held himself quite well against Garen compared to his other two companions.

"Nah, I’ve only heard about them. Let’s look for a place to talk, I need some answers from you guys." Garen noticed the people in black cloaks heading toward them. "Actually, maybe it’s better for me to ask them."

The black cloaked leader took off the hood, revealing a middle-aged lady with scars on her face.

"Brave fighter friends, we are of the Jiu Gu Clan1 from nearby forest. May we have the honor to invite you for a brief conversation someplace else?"

Everyone, including Su Lin, Celine, as well as Joseph and his companions turned to Garen, who raised his eyebrows out of curiosity. "Lead the way."

The leader nodded, "Please, this way."

　　*****************

Half an hour later, in a manor near the pine woods.

In a dimly lit room with a minibar, the scarred lady stood behind the redwood bar counter, expertly mixing cocktails with a shaker.

Garen’s group and Joseph’s group took their own spots in front of the counter, some of them standing and some sitting. Joseph and his companions sat separately from Garen, talking to a young and pretty woman.

The flames in the fireplace crackled, sending warmth to every corners of the room.

"In other words, you don’t know anything about any non-human races other than the werewolves?" Garen asked with a slight disappointment.

"Exactly that." The middle-aged woman nodded, "Call me Yarmdo, by the way. Our clan has been in a feud with the werewolves for a really long time. Most of the time clashes only happen within the Sin Gerro area. I’m not sure about other places though. Within these woods, according to our correspondence with the other gathering spots of our clan, there have only been werewolves. The other creatures probably only exist in mythology…" Yarmdo the clan leader looked at Garen with intrigue.

Garen nodded, unsure of how to respond.

He assumed vampires, dark sorcerers, or holy churches exist, like those stories he had heard on Earth. He didn’t know there were only two forces fighting against each other.

One side of that is the werewolves who hunts humans for food. The other side is the Demon Hunter clan, fated to put up resistance against the werewolves.

Both sides have been in a feud for so long, no one remembered what fuelled the initial battle that became the current racial war.

Sensing no response from Garen, Yarmdo continued.

"The Jiu Gu Clan were divided into three subclans, each fighting a werewolf tribe at different places. But the werewolves are powerful. The ones that we encountered today were only a really small pack. They were having a hunting ritual, which is their counterpart for coming of age ceremonies, so those were mostly underage werewolves. Even so, we were having a hard time defeating them."

Yarmdo stared at Garen earnestly, and glanced toward Su Lin and the Joseph trio.

"If you would allow me, I’d like to formally invite you to join our Demon Hunters clan with my utmost sincerity."

"I’m really sorry, but we were only passersby to this country, pursuing a wanted criminal. We can’t possibly stay to help with your battles." Su Lin noticed a slight frown on Garen’s face and immediately understood his concerns. In addition, their original plan did not include stopping a god-knows-how-long feud. He stepped in to reject Yarmdo’s proposition.

"Without our means of concealment, the werewolves will hunt you down. Only by laying low in here can you get rid of the scent they track with." Yarmdo explained, "All those werewolves Mr. Garen killed had left him with their scents. If he returns to the woods now, the werewolves will be able to track it and send much stronger adult hunters after him."

She looked into Garen’s eyes directly.

"Mr. Garen, I know you are capable, but you are only one person. The werewolves are strong beyond your imagination. The have two High Elders, not the kind you met today, who are truly at the prime of their hunting years. Their strength is far beyond your standard werewolves, and they also have the Wolf King Worthman. Our clan had been oppressed for far too long because of those werewolves. Right now, they are hiding in the human society, we can’t even track them if they don’t show up during certain times. They have acclimated to the human society so well that all of them are masters in assassination."

"I’m truly sorry, we really have our own mission, so it’s really impossible for us to stay here longer than necessary." Garen shook his head.

"A mission? Do you mind telling us about it? Maybe we can help with the information you need." Yarmdo knew she wouldn’t be able to convince Garen right now, no one would offer help with nothing to gain.

"Do you know about the Golden Sword Throne?"

"Golden Sword Throne?" Yarmdo shook her head, "It’s my first time hearing about it."

"What about the Dahl Falls?" Garen asked

Yarmdo’s eyes widened. "Dahl Falls?"

"You know about the place?" Garen wasn’t expecting a reaction like that.

"Yes, um… That’s the hunting ground of the High Elder Vitar. Please wait a moment, I’ll go get a map. That place is hard to get to for normal people." Yarmdo swiftly poured out the cocktails into several shot glasses and moved them over to Garen’s trio. She left the room with vigor.

Garen and the other two took the cocktails. Su Lin took a whiff but didn’t drink, Celine on the other hand sipped it slowly.

"It was not bad." Celine commented, slightly bored.

Garen walked over to the walls, inspecting the weapons and armors hanging on the blackstone wall.

These are tools the Demon Hunters employ to fight against the werewolves.

"In the movies on Earth, demon hunters2 would normally use silverware to fight werewolves, apparently silver suppresses their ability to heal. I wonder if it’s the same here."

He recalled the little information he had while removing a black crossbow to examine.

The crossbow was black all-around and has a T-shaped body. The grip was wrapped with a yellowing white cloth, giving it a rough finish. Through the cloth Garen can feel the coolness of the crossbow wood. It was not loaded.

Garen turned it over to look at the bottom part. There was some symbols engraved on the foregrip that Garen is not able to recognize.

"That’s the Ancient Endorian language. According to hearsays, these Ancient Endorian scripts have the ability to summon mystical forces, so a lot of religious texts would make a reference to it." Su Lin explained softly.

Garen nodded and put the crossbow back on the wall.

The other weapons on the wall are mostly strongbows and firearms, there’s no sign of any silverware at all.

Garen sighed regretfully. From the looks of it, the werewolves here were not weakened by silver.

He had always been interested in these mythological creatures, but right now, his main mission was to recover the Golden Sword Throne from Duskdune Shura. When he was extended the invitation to join the Demon Hunters, he had thought about it, since Yarmdo was being nice. Considering the long history with the clan, he might even get a good treasure with Potential.

One by one, Garen started examining the items on the wall. Of all nine items, most are decorative, there was none that he can find Potential in.

"What do you think of these weapons?" Yarmdo was back with a map made of sheepskin leather.

"They were alright. They should be pretty powerful, combining firearms and ancient knowledge."

"They would be decent if they were used against humans," Yarmdo shrugged. "But they don’t seem to do a lot on werewolves. Even High Elders would be too much for us to handle, not to mention the Wolf King Worthman. Fortunately for us, they had some infighting problem and got hurt, that should set them back a few years to heal."

"Don’t werewolves heal fast?" Celine interrupted.

"Not when it’s hurt with the claws by one of their kind." Yarmdo explained.

Garen nodded.

"I was wondering if your clan collected any antiques from all these years battling the werewolves. I mean, I had some experience appraising antiques, and am interested with what you have. Is it okay if I take a look?"

Sensing Yarmdo’s confusion, Garen added, "Anything from old equipments, trinkets, to things taken from the werewolves for keepsake will do."

"Of course. Sometimes we do loot the werewolves we kill for keepsakes. Sort of like a collection. We have a lot of those." Yarmdo agreed without hesitation.

"This is a map of the areas nearby, think of it as an appreciation for helping us with the wolf pack just now," She held the map out toward Garen.

"Mr. Garen, it is my duty to warn you, even though you are stronger than any of us, you shouldn’t underestimate the capabilities of the High Elders. If there’s anything we can do to help, just come to us Jiu Gu Demon Hunters."

"Thanks." Garen knew this was an attempt to gain his favor, but he played along just to be nice. At least he’ll have the locals’ help.

Checking the map, Garen learned about the situation in the nearby Pinehill City from Yarmdo. After receiving a bagful of trinkets, Garen’s trio was eager to start chasing after Duskdune Shura to the Dahl Falls.

On the other hand, the other three, Joseph, Johnson, and Annie, built a solid connection with the charming young Demon Hunter, and were not planning to leave anytime soon, especially when they’ve just experienced a bloodshed. Without a proper ability to protect themselves, they severely lack security for their safety. Therefore they’d decided to stay the night instead, waiting to be sent home by the Demon Hunters in the morning.

Joseph stared at Garen’s silhouette in the night and pondered. "Don’t they feel just a tiny bit of fear against the werewolves? The leader killed so many of them, the werewolves must be huning for him everywhere."

"No idea, but they were much stronger than we are, maybe that was the source of their confidence. The leader probably as strong as my grandmother," The young Demon Hunter admired, "I wish I could be as strong as that someday."

"What were they thinking, leaving so late?" Annie asked, whispering, "However strong they are, they are only three people, can they even fight against so many werewolves at once?

"Who knows." Joseph shrugged. Gawking at the three leaving shadows, a curiosity grew inside him.

He shut his eyes and started to listen carefully.

In the darkness, an image of the outer world slowly emerged in his sight. He zoomed in toward the departing trio, and focused on Garen alone.

"I want… to hear his past… his thoughts…" Joseph concentrated on his intention.

Boom!

A deafening toot blared as if it was right beside him. A gigantic red-eyed white mammoth appeared beside Garen, roaring loudly.

Joseph shuddered in fear, his connection with the Garen severed.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. 久古一族, lit. Long-standing Ancient Family

2. Here the term “demon hunter” is not specific to this story, so the term is not capitalized.

Chapter 144: Coincidence 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Night time.

In the woods.

Garen stopped advancing. He frowned and checked out the area.

"What is it?" Su Lin asked in puzzlement.

"I think someone’s spying on us." Perplexed himself, Garen answered with uncertainty, "Let’s go. We have to catch up with Duskdune Shura. Celine, can you lead the way, please?"

Celine nodded and started pacing.

All of them are able fighters, even if Su Lin, as the physically weakest person in the group, may not be able to beat Grandmasters of Combat, but he definitely can hold his own weight against normal combat experts. And with Celine, even Garen wasn’t completely sure what her trump card is, given her many many talents.

Within the group, Celine was leading the path, Garen was cross-referencing the map with the environment with Su Lin’s flashlight, adjusting their directions whenever needed so they won’t run into a dead end.

After leaving the manor, the trio followed the shortest path, heading straight to the redwood forest outside of Pinehill City.

Right after they have left the woods, a few brown wolves slowly emerged from the woods and smelled the grass patch.

"They’re out from the Demon Hunters’ area." A brown wolf growled in perfect Yalu language with a Pinehill accent.

"They certainly ran pretty fast. Continue after them. The High Elder gave his order, no matter who they are, if they ruined the hunting ritual, they must pay the price with their lives!" A larger wolf replied with ferocity.

The brown wolves disappeared into the wilderness, heading directly opposite from the one Garen picked.

A person with black cloak stepped out of the woods, his hand still holding an emptied small vial, he obviously helped Garen redirect the pursuing werewolves.

*****************

Garen was holding the sack with one hand and taking out the trinkets one by one.

A white necklace made of wolf teeth, a werewolf claw, a pair of wolfskin gloves, a wooden wolf sculpture, a nude sculpture of half beautiful woman, half wolf…

Garen speechlessly threw that away.

"Okay, gross." Su Lin is as speechless as Garen.

Garen pulled out a wolf penis next…

"Okay, why do I even bother hoping for good things anymore…" Su Lin covered his face with his palm. Some things are better not seen.

Again, Garen threw it away and started digging through the sack. At least this one is less inappropriate. It’s a stone slab drawing of a giant wolf. Garen perused it with the flashlight.

Every body part of the giant wolf was annotated by lines.

"Would be nicer steamed… Needs pepper…" Once Garen made out the words, he rolled his eyes and flung the stone slab as hard as he could. There wasn’t much left in the sack.

"No wonder they bagged it with a black sack instead of a translucent one, it’s so embarrassing!" Su Lin teased.

"I’m bored anyway, might as well go through it for fun." Garen shook his head as he suddenly touched something chilly. A strong gust of energy flowed in through his index finger.

Garen shuddered and went wide-eyed.

It’s an Antique of Tragedy! It’s full of Potential energy!

This Potential flow only sustained for a few seconds before dying down and disappearing.

His grabbed the item, it felt like a box, and fished it out of the sack. At the same time he glanced at his Potential Point at the bottom of his field of view.

‘Potential 105%’

"I got another stat point!" Garen felt a rush of euphoria. He had just earned a point not long ago, he wouldn’t have expected to earn another point so soon after. "No wonder they always said to go out more!" Without hesitation, he added it to his Agility.

With the extra 0.3 in Agility, Garen’s body felt so much lighter, he can feel the changes in his body. His brain produced a cool breeze toward every nook and corner of his body, lightening his movements.

He raised his arm, it felt much lighter than usual.

Right now his Agility stat is 1.82, Potential Point is down to 5%.

"My speed earlier was still slightly slower than Duskdune Shura, but now I’m confident to be as fast as he is!" Garen inspected the changes within his body with satisfaction. While the breeze from his brain stopped after a while, his body felt as if he’s floating, like he had dropped off a heavy load.

Keeping the box that gave him Potential in his pocket, Garen touched the two remaining items. No response. He lobbed them aside.

"What’s that?" Su Lin noticed the box Garen had kept.

"Not sure. I think it’s a jewelry box." Garen took the box out and examined it again. He shined the flashlight at it, revealing patterns that look like scribbles children made.

"The craftsmanship is bad, but it feels like treasure of some sort."

"Better than nothing."

"True." Garen smiled playfully and threw the box to Su Lin, "Take it, I think you’ll find it interesting."

"Sure," Su Lin caught it. He opened the box, it didn’t make any sound, "It doesn’t look like a jewelry box," Su Lin pondered, "There was nothing in there."

"The treasure is the box itself, so it doesn’t matter what’s inside." Garen shrugged nonchalantly.

The pair didn’t say anything more, and chased after Celine.　　

Celine paced speedily while sniffing, occasionally she would make a turn. The trees got progressively shorter and more concentrated.

The three shuttled through the woods, noticing the gradual reddening of the woods. The leaves on the ground were either yellow or pale red.

Moving a little further, even the leaves on the branches turned red. At this point, only rarely would they see some dark yellow among a layer of red leaf litter. The rising sun slowly scorched the eastern clouds, burning through it, and blessed the woods with beams of morning ray.

************

The spot where Garen cast aside the black sack.

Several brown-furred werewolves leapt out of the trees, landing beside the discarded sack.

A werewolf grabbed the bag and sniffed.

"They got away again! Humans are so cunning."

"I refuse to believe that I can’t catch up to them! Those damned foodbastard, how dare they stop the hunting ritual of the Thukk Tribe!" Another werewolf grunted. "According to where teams One and Two, they seemed to be heading toward the Dahl Falls!"

"Very likely. If these outsiders dared to even step foot in High Elder’s hunting ground, there’s only a certain death for them. What good is being strong alone, we can mob them to death! Gather all the hunters nearby! We’re swarming them at Dahl Falls! They will not be spared!"

************

In the Redleaf Woods.

Garen was speeding away from Dahl Falls.

"Celine, are you sure this is the way to the Falls?" Garen raised his suspicion.

"Trust me, it is!" Celine replied calmly.

"But why do something feels wrong?"

"Well my nose was filled with too many smells and I can smell very well now, but my direction is definitely correct!" Celine announced proudly.

"Okay." Garen decided to trust Celine, she lead them straight to Duskdune Shura after all. Compared to the map, he trusted Celine’s olfactory sense better.

Su Lin only shrugged, expressing his indifference.

The trio disappeared into the woods.

**************

Two hours later…

In the woods surrounding Dahl Falls.

"How are they not here yet?"

"No idea, but patience is key. According to their paths earlier, they are no doubt heading this way." Two brown-furred werewolves conversed softly in the bush.

"Tell the others to be patient too, they will appear sooner or later, this is after all their destination."

***************

Two hours later…

Garen and the other two stared at the muddy marsh in front of them, speechless.

"What is this place?"

"I think… we are lost…"

Su Lin’s eyes twitched.

"It’s not my fault! It’s Duskdune Shura! It has to be him, he was worried the werewolves might catch up to him, so he used some sort of powder to lure them away! I got duped!" Celine protested. As soon as she realized they were lost, she had a possible explanation.

"So what do we do now?" Garen asked Su Lin, defeated.

"We look at the map, find ourselves." Su Lin shrugged.

***************

Three hours later…

Dahl Falls.

"Leader, how are they not here yet?"

The leading brown-furred werewolf thought really hard. He froze as realization washed over him. Slapping his knee, he groaned, "Fuck"

"What is it, leader?" The werewolf beside him asked, worried.

"It’s a trap! They must have tricked us, leading us here to Dahl Falls while they escaped the other direction!"

"So what do we do n-"

"Everyone go after them, now! We have to catch those cunning bastards!" The lead werewolf sprung up.

In just a minute, a huge swarm of werewolves dashed out of their hiding place, surging toward the opposite direction of the path to the Dahl Falls.

Not long after they were gone, in the hidden path of the woods near the Falls, three people appeared.

"Finally… I can hear the Falls…" Celine exhaled feebly, "That sly fox Duskdune Shura, he anticipated our every move…"

"Not only us," Garen examined the pawprints left by the werewolves, "It’s too much of a coincidence, these werewolves only left a moment ago."

"This is not a coincidence." Su Lin frowned, "He figured out how Celine tracked him. This is a setup, he lured the werewolves away so we would go in alone. He doesn’t want to expose the secret in here!"

"How do you know?" Garen asked, baffled.

"Precisely because there’s too much of a coincidence, Duskdune Shura used something to lure those wolves away." Su Lin explained with a serious look on his face.

Chapter 145: Twist of Fate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen scowled, looking around cautiously. "Looks like he did set this whole thing up to make sure we enter. What is he trying to achieve?"

"Your guess is as good as mine." Su Lin shrugged, "Let’s go then. The Falls is right in front, let’s find out how he planned to usher us, shall we?"

Garen nodded, the three of them slowly approaching a tiny waterfall within their sight.

The waterfall was like a quadrilateral white silk embedded in the middle of a vast green made of grassy fields and pine forests, on its right was a ruins full of oval white stones.

Grayish-white stone houses splattered all over the ruins. Destroyed walls and thriving weeds formed a harmonious concerto of gray, white, and green.

The trio walked past the waterfalls to slowly make their way up to the ruins. Garen replaced Su Lin as the group’s pathfinder.

He looked around, none of the three-story houses were spared from the destruction. All the windows lead to separate pockets of gloomy lifelessness.

"This used to be a small town… from decades ago, it seems." Garen muttered, "You can tell by the weathering of the structures and the density of the weeds."

"That’s right, more specifically, about fifty to sixty years ago." Su Lin pointed out.

Garen peered at him, "You can tell?"

"Don’t underestimate me. I’m a genius with five university degrees!" Su Lin beamed.

"Now that we’re here, what’s next? Duskdune Shura wouldn’t leave us hanging if he went through all that trouble to lead us here." Celine interrupted the banter, "Let’s split up to look for clues?"

"Not necessary." Garen turned toward a small alley between two houses on his left. The alley was dim and muted leading to the unknown. The only things visible at the other end of that alley were sinopia-colored boulders and mossy grass.

"Can you smell anything?" Garen inquired from Celine.

"Nuh-uh, still too mixed up to tell." Celine shook her head.

"This layout… it looks like the Ancient Endorian’s. A town that was only abandoned several decades ago, using Ancient Endorian infrastructure? Smells fishy." Garen mused.

"Duskdune Shura lead us here, so it must be one of his schemes," Celine speculated, "Do you think the secrets of Golden Sword Throne is hidden in here?"

"Beats me." Garen was not convinced, "What has Golden Sword Throne, from the Nabudas Empire of the Fivestar Continent got to do with Ancient Endorian civilization of the Stonecliff Continent?"

"Let’s search for more clues." Su Lin suggested.

"Like you said, the infrastructure here is similar to the Ancient Endorian’s. If it really is connected to the Ancient Endorians, we’ll need to look at the layout of the whole town." Garen recalled. "I need more information to identify the important areas in the town. Can you two do me a favor by counting the number of buildings in town, as well as finding a pattern of their distribution?"

"Sure, let’s split up." Su Lin nodded, "Be safe, Celine."

Celine retorted, "I can easily beat two of you, Su Lin. You’re the physical weak link, remember?"

Speechless, Su Lin partitioned the town into two parts, and went in different ways with Celine to check out the geography of their areas.

Garen stayed back to scrutinize the details of the infrastructure.

He pressed him palm gently against the wall, against the weird grayish-white moss. They feel damp, and slightly cooling.

Returning to the ruins, it was pin-droppingly silent now that both Celine and Su Lin have gone far.

Garen strolled torpidly. "If it’s following the Ancient Endorian layout…" He recalled the knowledge about ancient architecture he learned from the old man Gregor, deep in thought. "Maybe… over there!"

He sauntered along the path between houses and circled the ruins from outside until he arrived at a clearing with a collapsed metal fence. It was filled with platinum gray rubble. Weeds with different shades of green sprouted between the rocks, filling the area with a barren tranquillity.

Garen entered the clearing through an opening, stumbling ever so slightly every now and then.

The stones on the ground were extraordinarily smooth, only some crumbled and some fallen.

Garon took another few steps, as if to triangulate the clearing, and finally stopped beside a crooked gray stone.

Before he could crouch down, he hesitated and glanced toward the town ruins.

Both Su Lin and Celine were hustling toward him.

Celine was the first to arrive, and reported, "There were twelve buildings here."

"It’s a triangle, a very proper triangle. Isn’t that spooky?" Su Lin continued, clearly in discomfort.

Garen nodded, his eyes glazed as a donut, and stood there motionlessly.

A few minutes passed before he finally recovered.

"I get it now." He looked down in search for something. Not long after, he stood in a tiny clear space devoid of rocks and rubbles.

He crouched and started grazing the ground. Finding something, he pull it free of the grass.

Snap!

In Garen’s palm there was a black metallic ring, attached to something before being pulled free.

"According to the Ancient Endorian style," Garen tried evoking his knowledge. It’s only after the old man Gregor’s death that he realize that the knowledge the old man gave him were all hidden secrets that no one will ever find in bookstores. Those are the knowledge no other appraiser will find out on their own.

He perused the very fine script on the ring, stood up, walked for about ten paces, and stood still.

"This was a graveyard." Garen whispered to Su Lin and Celine. "Follow me." Both of them were already heading toward him as he said that.

The trio arrived at the edge of the graveyard, beneath a tree.

Grazing the ground once again, Garen dug out some dirt, exposing a rectangular stone tablet with words engraved on it.

‘Eyham Vent, May Your Spirit Rest In Eternal Peace. 2867.3.1’

"This is someone’s tomb from Year 2867, we are in Year 2987, this was buried 120 years ago!" Su Lin frowned disapprovingly. "What on earth are you doing Garen?"

"This is the key to this riddle," Garen held both sides of the tablet, "I wanna open it." He forcefully lifted the tablet and set it aside.

Garen peered into the casket. It wasn’t a human remains as they thought it was, but a hole leading deep into the earth. Chilly air and odor poured out of the dark rectangular hole. It smelled like rotten eggs.

"Wow, you’re good at this appraisal thing!" Su Lin whistled, "You found the ruins of an ancient civilization!"

"Meh, this is just a traditional tomb from a long time ago, they used to store the deceased in a tomb cellar like this." Garen explained, unamused. "A long time ago, it was also very popular in the Stonecliff Continent. People believed that even after death, the souls would still need to perform daily routines, so they would base their tombs on a cellar for the living, they even have living rooms, bedrooms, and storage rooms."

"Tsk, I thought there was a huge discovery," Su Lin said dejectedly and pulled out his flashlight, "Lemme see."

He stood in front of the hole and shined his flashlight into it, causing some of the mud and dirt to fall in. Su Lin cautiously leaned over and looked down into the hole.

Srrrt!

From within the hole, a black thread shot unexpectedly toward Su Lin’s face.

"Watch out!" It was too late for Garen to block it due to its speed. It was a black thorn with three sharp edges, spinning at high speed aiming for Su Lin’s forehead.

Garen tried to block it with his own body, but it was too late.

Gah!

Su Lin stumbled backward and fell sitting on the ground. His hands were covering his face, panting heavily.

"What… what on earth!" Even his speech slurred. Just that instant he thought he was going to die.

Having realized that Su Lin avoided a death trap, both Garen and Celine sighed in relief.

Releasing his hands, a red scar emerged beneath Su Lin’s right eye, adding a sense of allure to his already charming face.

"Thank goodness I had a hunch and evaded, or else I’d be dead by now." He was still trembling, the red scar beneath his eye slowly faded away.

"As long as you’re okay. What’s that under your eye?" Garen inquired.

"It’s a Cryptic Secret Technique that I learned, it has a little side effect, so I can’t use it so often." Su Lin smiled wryly. "It’s just the beginning! I can’t believe they made me use my trump card already."

"Cryptic Secret Technique? It’s the kind that simplifies some of the application method in some Secret Techniques for normal fighters. A lot of stronger non-Martial Adept fighters will learn a little at some point." Sensing Garen’s confusion, Celine explained. "Of course, these sort of Secret Methods are less powerful than the full version, and most of them will have some sort of side effects."

Comprehending, Garen nodded, "Alright, if I’m correct, this tomb should have a lot of Ancient Endorian secrets. I think Duskdune Shura lead us here to make us solve the mystery of the Ancient Endors."

He raised his arm toward the black hole and felt a cool draft from inside the cave.

"This is not just a normal tomb, it probably have other entrances. Usually a tomb would only have one entrance."

"You’re saying this is an underground pass?" Celine’s eyes widened with glee.

"Very likely." Garen tossed a stone into the cave, and swung his arm on top of the entrance. After confirming that there’s no further traps, he declared, "Okay, it’s safe now. The poisonous gas should have dissipated about now."

"Are we going in?"

"We have to. If my assumption is correct, this entrance will have a Testament of the Dead who entered the Ancient Endorian ruins." Garen replied. "It’s the law of the Ancient Endor."

The three people carefully shined the flashlight into the cave again, revealing a silvery gray staircase which extends downward.

On the right side of the staircase, there was a white stone pillar, with oval red stone in an exquisite stone bowl. The stone is as huge as a fist, with carvings of symbols and fine patterns.

"That’s the one, I’ll recover it." Garen carefully stepped onto the stone staircase, advanced toward the pillar, and reached for the stone bowl.

Ding ding!

Two clear dings echoed as something struck the back of his palm, two thorns like the one that attacked Su Lin shot down from above, hitting the back of Garen’s hand and made a golden spark.

"What a force!" Garen focused and continued reaching his hand over to grab the bowl.

Pssst!

Garen withdrew his hand by instinct, his index finger started to smoke, releasing a odor of burnt skin.

He looked at his finger, the pulp of it was charred, as if the whole area has been broiled with high temperature.

Chapter 146: Twist of Fate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What is that? How’s your hand?" Su Lin turned his attention toward Garen at the same time with Celine.

"Some kind of strong acid…" Garen shook his head to indicate that he’s okay, then exited through the entrance. "Didn’t think this Testament of the Dead would be so hard to recover…"

Garen’s face scrunched up and turned to the west side of the town. Celine and Su Lin stood up at the same time, facing the same direction.

"Duskdune Shura. He’s here." Celine sniffed the air and murmured.

"They’re not trying to hide. Here they are." Garen stated calmly. "Take care of yourselves."

Two silhouettes with black mantle appeared from the pine forest in the west. They stopped after arriving at the outskirts of the graveyard, silently observing Garen and the others.

"Duskdune Shura," Garen stepped up and asked, "Care to tell me your true intention? What secrets exactly does the Golden Sword Throne hold?"

He can sense the immense Bravery these two people possess. Duskdune Shura is, without a doubt, a powerful force, but what’s surprising is the other person also has power comparable to him. Garen didn’t have a good feeling about that.

Now that his speed has vastly increased, he wouldn’t have any problem protecting himself, but Celine and Su Lin would be in trouble. If the opponent really wants to harm them...

Synchronized, Duskdune Shura and the other person took off their hoods, exposing their facial features.

Duskdune Shura still looks the same with his time-ravaged features and wrinkles. The other person, however, looks pretty, but expressionless.

"A woman?" Su Lin looked confused, "No, he’s just androgynous."

Garen studied the new person. He looks just like the Ice Queen, the only things that gave him away are his Adam’s apple and flat chest. He had a rapier at his waist, and his snowy white hair was kept short, his eyes in the shade of lava.

"I am known as the Flamingo." The man said to Garen nonchalantly.

"Flamingo?" Su Lin and Celine gave each other a look, it doesn’t sound like a name, more a nickname.

"Duskdune Shura said you are qualified to enter the ruins, so he gave you the exact location." Flamingo explained calmly. "I do, however, require to do a little test on your qualification."

"Test? How?" Garen eyed him suspiciously.

"Defend yourself from me for one attack." Flamingo slowly pulled on his rapier.

A black shine came quickly.

Clang!

Before he finished his sentence, Flamingo appeared before Garen, his black rapier hacked at Garen rising forearms.

Like an electric saw cutting metal, sparks flew and the sound of metal grinding clanged!

Both Flamingo and Garen faced each other, slightly surprised at each other’s power.

Flamingo suddenly smirked.

Zing!

The rapier bent and bounced away.

"Rend!"

A black shine.

Bang!

The spot Garen was standing on now has two deep trenches. His right arm was protecting his chest, his left was pushing Su Lin standing beside him away. He himself was pushed a whole two meters back by that sudden attack.

Garen saw very clearly that in the split second, the black rapier had slashed him five consecutive times at the exact same spot. This is about the same level of control as Andrela’s Secret Sword Technique. Moreover, this guy’s as strong as an ox!

"My turn!" Garen’s face darkened with rage. He was readying his attacks when he suddenly lost his enemy.

"Not bad," Flamingo lightly landed beside Duskdune Shura. The black rapier was back in its sheath without anyone noticing. "He definitely qualified."

Duskdune Shura shot a glance at Garen.

"Thanks for this time, you’re the only one with some free time after all."

"Don’t sweat it," Flamingo said, "I owed you that much."

Flamingo bounded forward, dashing toward Garen again, the golden-redness in his eyes becoming more intense.

He isn’t extraordinarily fast, but somehow has a weird tempo to his movement, like the pumping of the heart. With every beat, his body would blur out just enough.

"Step aside!" Garen grunted. He guessed his intention and stepped aside to unblock the entrance to the tomb. Su Lin and Celine evaded as well.

Flamingo no longer acknowledged any of the trio, he jumped and disappeared into the tomb, like a bird in a swoop.

A shadow, Duskdune Shura, darted after Flamingo, and disappeared into the darkness as well.

A third mass disappeared. The Testament of the Dead. Garen felt a slight moroseness he couldn’t put into words.

"Flamingo… Another Master like Duskdune Shura… Celine, any idea who he is?"

Celine’s face was dark with seriousness, she nodded. "I recognized him. One of the top Grandmasters of Combat from the previous era, same as Duskdune Shura. Him, Duskdune Shura, and White Bird Holy Fist, the three of them were the strongest fighters in the whole Confederate, no one were able to surpass them. The strange thing is, he’s almost seventy years old, how does he still look so young? Even the Essence Locking Art couldn’t produce such ridiculous effect!"

"Another old geezer." Su Lin had no words. "I heard Duskdune Shura joined a secret group, the Immortal Palace Alliance. That guy isn’t one of them, is he?"

"It is possible." Celine confirmed, "I’ve heard of the Immortal Palace Alliance, there were five of them, every single one of them were abnormally strong."

"Garen, what do you think? Are you confident?" Su Lin turned his attention toward a brooding Garen.

"What he used… what he did, is not only martial arts…" Garen was deep in thought. "And his Bravery is as strong as Duskdune Shura."

"Not only martial arts? What are we even doing here?" Su Lin exclaimed. The two of them followed Garen here to track Duskdune Shura, but they never planned to fight Duskdune Shura directly! Duskdune Shura even had a helper this time!

"Don’t be rash to go inside." Garen shook his head. "We’ll wait for the Slash Brigade to arrive! If Duskdune Shura wanted to kill me, he’ll have a severe price to pay, but since he has a helper of the same level, I have no idea how it would turn out. We’re not here to court death."

"Then we should wait. We’ll look for a hiding place." Celine suggested, "This is the Werewolves’ area, I can find a way to avoid detection, but I need some place clandestine."

"What about the houses in town? We can stay a night over there." Su Lin proposed. "I think the Slash Brigade should be here soon enough."

"I’m fine with that." Garen agreed. He does not fear Duskdune Shura, but it would be tricky with Flamingo on the playing board.

"What do they want anyway? What’s the secret behind the Golden Sword Throne? What Flamingo did just now is definitely not martial arts!"

"Celine, does the Neptune Fist have any record on it?" Su Lin looked to Celine for answer. As the last successor of a powerful martial arts school, Celine has the most authority.

"I think so, but I can’t recall anything right now, sorry." Celine frowned, "Let’s find a place to rest. I might know what they are looking for."

"Oh?" That caught Garen’s attention.

With Flamingo’s help, his hope of getting his hands on the Golden Sword Throne is even slimmer than before. He could only hope for the Slash Brigade’s arrival, and look for opportunities when a fight breaks out.

Now that the two insanely strong people were down there, he dare not be so reckless to go in alone even though there may be Antiques of Tragedy in there.

The trio quickly left the spot, leaving behind the open tomb, and found a three-storied building for the night.

The floor, the walls, the handrail of the staircase, everywhere was covered with chalk and dust, as if it was lined with a furry gray carpet.

They swiftly cleaned up one of the least damaged room in the top floor, prepared the flint and tinder, made fire, heated up the deep fried pancakes, and cooked a meat mushroom soup.

While they are dining, the three of them started discussing about the tomb.

Garon sat quietly while listening to Su Lin and Celine’s analyses and guessworks, letting them take control of the tactic discussion.

He sat on the ground, looking into the fire while deep in his thoughts.

"Celine, tell me honestly, monsters like Duskdune Shura and Flamingo, how many are there in the Confederation?" Su Lin sounds as if he’s arguing with Celine.

"I counted, including the people from Immortal Palace Alliance, not counting people who wield firearms, not more than four." Celine replied softly.

"‘Not more than four’, but two were here for the Golden Sword Throne."

"Flamingo, Duskdune Shura, Palosa, these three are from the same era, they must know something between them, about the Golden Sword Throne. That’s why they’re here together, I suspect they’re all from Immortal Palace Alliance." Celine was unusually calm.

"Not necessarily true, Maybe they’re just good friends. My father’s case shook the whole Confederation, half the higher ups probably already knew about it, it’s not that hard to find out. That Flamingo dude must have gotten some news from somewhere before coming. I propose that we leave immediately, if we stayed here it’s only gonna get more dangerous." Su Lin frowned.

"You wouldn’t know, but Grandmasters of Combat like Duskdune Shura and Flamingo, once they approved of Garen, they will not reject his participation. Moreover, people of their stature and their pursuit of the ultimate, they have their own pride, it is impossible for them to jointly attack a weaker person!" Celine reasoned. "So we’re actually really safe."

"It’s true that I don’t know about their pride. What I do know, is if they actually joined forces, we’re dead!" Su Lin disagreed strongly, "I won’t bet my life on other people’s pride!"

Celine bit her lower lips, it’s obvious she’s hesitant to leave, but she couldn’t find a better reason to convince Su Lin of otherwise.

After a good ten minutes of silence, she spoke again.

"In Neptune Fist, there’s an ancient folio with the record of a secret treasure of Ancient Endorian civilization."

"Did you just recalled that, or are you finally willing to share that with us?" Su Lin crossed his arm in front of his chest, not feeling the urge to touch any of the food. He looks upset at Celine’s secrecy.

"Secret treasure of Ancient Endor?" Garen lifted his gaze toward Celine.

Chapter 147: Weird 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Celine nodded her head

"Yes," she said as she bit her lip, as if she was still uncertain.

However as she made up her mind, her expression started to relax.

"Whatever I’ve told you here, please don’t spread it. Regardless if they are your friends or relatives, you mustn’t tell anyone anything. Can you do that?" Celine asked sternly.

Garen and Su Lin both looked a little shocked upon hearing that.

"Is it really that serious?" Garen asked softly.

"Of course," Celine nodded, both her eyes still looking weirdly serious.

"Alright, no problem," Su Lin nodded in agreement.

"I also have no issue with it. Alright, now would you please tell us what is the matter?" Garen too felt something was wrong with the way Celine was acting.

"Actually... Duskdune Shura is probably here because of this. The Golden Sword Throne is supposed to be a key, a key whose presence can only denote danger and opportunity."

Celine started to recount from memory,

"This world of ours is incredibly big, bigger than anyone can ever imagine. Even if a man were to take a modern day jet plane, fill it with infinite amounts of fuel, he will still not be able to fly to the end of the ocean. Therefore sometimes it is possible to find some inexplicable places not previously known to anyone before. Found at random, most of these places tend to have existed for a very long time, and within these ruins: sometimes one would find artifacts from millennia ago, or even phenomena not explainable using conventional logic.."

"Artifacts from millennia ago? So what exactly does this have to do with the Golden Sword Throne? Just tell us already," Garen frowned.

Celine nodded,"Alright, I’ll skip the unimportant introductions and get down to it. The Golden Sword Throne, is from a mobile ancient ruin that the Ancient Endorian and Nabudas Empire have both explored before. The Golden Sword Throne is actually a relic key retrieved from within the ruin."

"What is within those ruins?" Garen asked directly.

"The legendary Blood of Secrets, some say it is the key to immortality, others say it gives tremendeous power. Nobody really knows or agrees on its true nature, but one thing is for sure: this item is incredibly valuable," Celine explained, "The locations of these ancient ruins are usually very hard to predict and pin-point. The times in which they appear are also not set. If it isn’t for the Golden Sword Throne, it would be next to impossible to open the entrance to the site."

"What you mean by that is..."

Celine nodded again, "Exactly, there are all kinds of ancient ruins, and each of their contents are vastly different from the other, it’s as if every ruin contains traces of the existence of a different civilization from the others. However one thing is for sure, each and everyone of them contain their fair shares of dangers and opportunities. Each ancient ruin contains a plethora of items of different values, we call these items ‘Secret Treasures’. The ancient ruin in which the Golden Sword Throne used to reside, was found and explored by the Ancient Endorians a long time ago, only to be explored by the Nabudas Empire shortly after as well. It is believed that the ancient ruins still exist, in fact there is even the possibility that those two great civilizations might have left some souvenirs in there during their time within. But for whatever it is worth, because of their explorations, the Golden Sword Throne became known to be related to the Blood of Secrets. In fact, since then, Ancient Endorian Ruins and the Golden Sword Throne practically became the pronouns for the Blood of Secrets."

The trio fell silent after, as Garen and Su Lin tried to swallow and digest what Celine just told them.

The bonfire continued to burn, as it slowly got smaller and smaller. The room’s illumination also started to get darker, the stars in the sky outside the window also started to become visible, as if they’d just woken up.

Celine looked at the both of them,

"Well? Do you still plan to leave?"

The both of them were still silent.

"There might be lethal dangers inside the ancient ruins, but there could also be opportunity. Some say that the ancient ruins hold strange weaponry and armors. You might even find mysterious animals in there. Some people even suspect that these ancient ruins are what’s left of a dead civilization,"

Celine added.

Garen stood up, and looked outside.

"Let’s wait till the Slash Brigade gets here. I suspect that Duskdune Shura baited us here for something malicious. The Slash Brigadewill definitely find us here eventually, maybe even the werewolves will find us."

"Just count the hours, those werewolves have probably already made out our tracks." Su Lin nodded, "They might just show up anytime now."

The trio then fell silent once more. After they finished eating, they started searching the house for some broken furniture to pile up against the windows. This way, the light from the bonfire would not be visible outside. Then they all fell asleep around the bonfire.

Not sure how long after...

BANG

Garen opened his eyes, half awake, he looked at the bonfire in front of him. He thought he had heard something.

BANG.

The bonfire made a small crackle again, small sparks flew up from underneath it. The bonfire was long out, the only light one could make from it was the soft red glow of hot charcoal.

As for Su Lin and Celine: one of them was dead asleep against the wall, while the other had made a small bed out of some stacked clothes on the floor, she too was dead asleep. Her face illuminated a faint red by the embers.

Garen was the only one awake.

He got up quietly, and went around the furniture, where he then stood beside the window and looked down.

Icy cold winds blew from the jungle outside, and with the winds came sounds from far far away.

Garen tried to look faraway, to the presumed source of the sounds.

Beyond the black ocean of trees, there were some specks of yellow light moving about. Now and then, one would be able to make out the weak banging of gunshots and wolves howling.

"Someone’s coming…" Garen frowned, and sprinted back to the bonfire to wake Celine and Su Lin up

"Wake up! Someone is coming, stop sleeping!"

Both already well prepared mentally, Su Lin and Celine darted up awake. Without even saying anything, they both cleared their heads, found their water bottles and took a gulp, then went to the window together.

Celine sniffed the air carefully.

"There’s the scent of werewolf, and also the scent of humans. There is also the scent of blood and gunpowder. Looks like they must have started fighting"

"Can you tell what kind of blood it is?" Garen asked softly.

"What do you think my nose is? That I would be able to tell where the blood came from?" Celine rolled her eyes at Garen.

"Leave that to me," Su Lin took out small telescope from her bag and pulled it to look at the source of the speckles of light.

Immediately, her face turned into a whole new shade of seriousness.

"It’s the Slash Brigade!" They’re fighting with the local werewolves! It seems to be quite a big fight!"

"Let me see," Garen took the telescope from her and took a look for himself.

Within the telescope’s sights, he saw dozens of werewolf corpses littered about the light, while the Slash Brigade ran alongside the source of the light. Many amongst them looked like there were injured, obviously from being surrounded and then attacked by the werewolves. There was also Beo in the group. That usually stern cold blue haired genius, it seemed like for once he was looking absolutely miserable, and he definitely looked like he was having a tough time fighting the ambush of werewolves from every direction around him.

"It’s the Slash Brigade, they’ve finally gotten in over their heads, they actually walked directly into the hunting area of werewolves. It doesn’t seem like they even thought of approaching it with some sort of strategy or tact, they just overconfidently walked right into it!" Garen shook his head, "no surprise that they would come into conflict with the local werewolves."

"Should we go help them?" Su Lin asked.

"What do you think?" Garen shook his head again, "If it were the werewolves that we encountered earlier, there wouldn’t be any need for our intervention, but from what I see here, these werewolves are way more powerful than the ones before."

"You mean they might be in serious trouble then? Sure we don’t want to go help?" Su Lin took the telescope and observed the scene once more.

"Not necessarily, they will eventually enter the ancient ruins. The Slash Brigade probably just made a mistake, they’ll catch up soon enough, I doubt werewolves would be able to slow them down at all." Garen decided, "When they resume their journey, we will enter right behind them."

"Made up your mind on entering?" Celine didn’t seem convinced.

"Mm, I have decided. With the Slash Brigade leading the way, we will be much safer," Garen nodded with certainty.

"I better not go." Su Lin thought, and shook her head, "my presence will just slow you both down. Better if I just wait here until you both made it out and then rendezvous with the Slash Brigade after."

"That works too, who knows what dangers await us within. We might not be able to take care of you amongst all of that," Garen nodded in agreement.

"Then let’s wait." Celine said softly.

The trio continued standing beside the window, staring into the distance as the small speckles of light grew brighter as the came closer in their direction.

Slightly over ten minutes, the lights arrived at the outskirts of the village. Everyone in the squad looked like a mess, only three were left, one was missing. In this small squad, two of them were holding torches. It seemed, for now, they had repelled the werewolves.

One of the three who remained cursed the werewolves aloud, while another was using the bark on a tree near him to rub off the blood from his machete.

Under the observation of Garen’s trio, the Slash Brigade went straight for the entrance to the tomb.

Very quickly, they found the already opened entrance to the tomb, they hesitated for a second, and then one by one the Slash Brigade disappeared into the entrance along with their lights.

Obviously, they had known about this entrance all along judging by the way they found it without any delays.

"Let’s go."

Garen turned and led the way down into the tomb entrance. Celine jumped, and landed right beside him, following him in.

"Please help watch over the entrance for us, just find something to cover it up."

"No problem," Su Lin answered quickly.

Garen led Celine back to the side of the tomb entrance once more, this time without hesitating, they both went down the stairs.

The rocky stairs were long and deep, leading down to a rock corridor that was definitely not a tomb. The corridor was long, dark and tight, every ten steps or so there were opposing holders for torches on the walls.

Garen turned on his flashlight and shone the way ahead. The corridor seemed to lead downwards endlessly, towards an unknown destination.

"Celine, pay attention to the scent of the Slash Brigade in front of us, make sure we don’t get too close to them or else they might find out we’re tailing them," Garen noted.

"No problem, just leave it to me." Celine nodded, "But why don’t we just rendezvous with them?"

"In these ancient ruins where there might be some secret treasures, we cannot trust anyone," Garen shook his head in disagreement.

"I thought you were planning to catch up with them." Celine looked at Garen as she continued to walk.

The duo walked and stopped now and then to make sure there weren’t any traps. Sometimes they would find steel needles stuck to the ground, obviously from traps triggered by the group in front of them.

The most well known symbol of Ancient Endorian culture, is their ability to connect earth and hell with their infinite stairs. The duo walked for over half an hour before they finally reached a brown door. It was ajar, and from the dust prints on the floor, one could easily make out a fresh set of footprints.

What was intriguing, was that there were two line of texts carved onto the walls around the door.

Garen leaned closer and shined it with his flashlight carefully.

"Be careful of sprites."

He read it softly, the walls were full of Endorian words, he could only roughly make out these few.

"What does it mean?"

Ra

Chapter 148: Weird 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Celine shook her head, she didn’t understand what it meant.

"Let’s go, for whatever it’s worth, the folks upfront have already cleared the way by going ahead," Garen walked into the door.

Behind the door was a room about the size of a small house’s living area. The walls of the room were decorated with carvings of weird faces, some crying, some in fear, some stern faces etc.

All around the walls of the entire room were filled with these stone faces. It was as if they had protruded out from within the walls and were trying to escape, hundreds, if not thousands of them.

Celine couldn’t help but inch closer to Garen as they walked carefully towards a pair of massive stone doors on the opposite side of the room.

The right door was ajar, obviously someone had already walked into it.

As the pair walked into the door.

SHHHHHHAAAAA

Tens of metal needles suddenly shot out from every direction in the corridor beyond, blocking the way forward.

Garen pulled Celine and took a step back.

SHHHAAAAAAA

The needles shrank back into the floors and walls, once again revealing the dark and seemingly endless corridor.

"Be careful, it looks very dangerous," Celine reminded, "I smell a horrible stench coming our way."

"A stench?" Garen was stunned hearing that, and he started paying a lot more attention to the walls on both sides of the corridor.

On each side of the wall was a small hole about the size of a fist. From within each of those holes, a wormlike creature that glowed a dark green hue started to climb out. When both wormlike creatures finally made their way out, they revealed locust-like wings from their body and started flying; then only the duo could make out their full appearance.

These weren’t just worms, they were little girl-like things that had dark green skins covered in smooth insect scales. While they had a slender and potentially attractive body shape, their faces were a total turn off as they looked incredibly sly and evil, not to mention the horrible stench.

The worm-girls flapped their wings rapidly, and made insect like noises. They were headed straight for Garen and Celine. As they got closer, they opened their mouths to conjure some sort of an evil smile, revealing a set of saw-like teeth.

"Sprites!" Celine took two steps backwards, hoping to pull away from them, "these must be the legendary sprite, be careful! They have very sharp teeth!" She slowly pulled out her belt, her gaze never straying away from the two sprites.

"Sprites?" Garen was at a loss for words, these abominations looked absolutely hideous, and yet they still had such cute names, surely their appearances did their names no justice.

"Garen you focus on protecting me! Sprites especially like eating little girls, they’ll definitely focus all their attacks on me!" Celine yelled in fear.

"Ha?" Garen only just noticed, the two sprites only paid attention to Celine with their gazes of greed and lust.

WHOOSH

The two sprites suddenly pranced on Celine. They didn’t even bother with Garen, they just circumnavigated him by flying around his left and right.

SLAP!

Garen reached out his right hand and very swiftly caught one of the sprites. With his left hand, he flicked the other sprite with his finger, sending it on a collision course with the wall.

Grabbing the sprite felt just like grabbing a typical beetle. Their body had no warmth whatsoever.

"Just like a typical insect, so weak," Garen frowned.

"Be very careful, sprites have a really resilient body structure, the Neptune Fist have records about them in their books, documenting how they’re very hard to kill!" Celine quickly reminded, "no matter if you burn, drown or stab, whatever you do, you will never be able to completely get rid of them!"

"Wow, that’s something," Garen’s frown grew deeper.

On the other side, the sprite that had been struck to the wall got back on its feet and was now back in the air. This time, it was onto Garen with deadly speed.

SLAP!

Garen swung his free hand and slapped that sprite to the wall, then he squashed it against the wall to be sure.

BANG!

The part of the wall which met his hand sank in around his palm, a great amount of dust fell from that spot and around the corridor.

As Garen lifted his palm off the wall, the sprite underneath was unscathed, looking only a little dizzy.

"They’re really strong indeed!" Garen finally realised.

KA CHA!

He suddenly felt a sharp pain on his right hand, and quickly let go of the sprite he was clenching in it.

As he pulled his palm back, he saw a small wound cut open by the teeth of the sprite. They definitely had some really sharp teeth, seeing how they were able to bite through his tough skin with ease.

"Let’s just run! Head straight towards the needles!" Celine drew her belt in one quick motion, whipping the now free sprite, sending it into a dizzy spell like its other half.

Garen followed closely behind Celine, running towards the spot where the needles protruded earlier.

SHHAAAAAAA

The needles protruded from every part of the walls and floors again, but this time, Garen mustered his might and kicked right into one of them. With a loud snap, it broke into half, revealing a small space for the two of them to run through, and away from the sprites.

They sprinted for a while, encountering many junctions along the way, but each time Celine wouldn’t even hesitate, she would sniff the air for a split second, then continue forwards.

After a long run, and a few more flights of stairs, they were finally stopped by a massive black arched door measuring at least 10 meters in height. Like the other doors from before, it was also ajar, revealing a spacious black stone hall within.

The black stone hall was brightly illuminated, in its centre, there was a black altar with a silver double-edged sword stuck into it.

The double-edged sword was about the width of a palm, and on it there were carvings of fist sized symbols. On its hilt were two sprites smiling and hugging each other carved into it in perfect uniformity.

Suddenly they heard some low hums and loud banging noises coming from within the hall.

BANG!!!

A massive living thing was thrown against the arch of the door, shaking the ground around the hall as it landed, and raining more dust onto its inhabitants from the ceiling.

When the dust cleared, Garen and Celine finally make out what the massive thing was.

It was actually a giant sprite towering over 5 meters in height!

It looked just like the sprites from before, greenish body, with full breasts and a slender body. All across its naked skin was covered in tough green insect scales, its mouth filled with sawlike teeth and a face that was insidious beyond belief.

SHHHHHHHH

The giant sprite roared, and got back on its feet almost immediately.

Garen and Celine hastily ran into the door.

Within the hall, Duskdune Shura and Flamingo were standing calmly on one side of the altar, Flamingo wielded the black sword, and was fending off combined attacks from Beo and another person.

The three of them were engaged in an intense fight, making sounds like a hurricane had struck.

BANG!!!

Beo was sent flying to the wall after being slashed by Flamingo, as he slowly slid off the wall, he started puking blood, looks like he was injured pretty badly.

Flamingo swung his sword around casually, and a silver circle of light appeared in front of him.

CLANG! CLANG! CLANG!

Another bearded man dressed in military fatigues wielding a short axe stood in front of the silver curve, his body suddenly shook violently, small red spots suddenly appeared underneath his skin, as if he was having a bad case of goosebumps.

"Crack!"

Flamingo rose his sword and slashed it downwards.

BANG!

Another low hum, and the bearded man too was sent flying backwards. He rolled on the ground for a while before finally ceasing and lying flat, his axe flew around and landed in the side of his head with a loud crack.

Garen and Celine also noticed a woman in a suit sitting against the wall in the hall. Her face was incredibly pale, and her chest was pierced through by a dagger, pinning her against the wall as her blood dripped into a puddle on the floor.

Yet despite this, she was still alive, and still struggling to pull the dagger out of her chest.

As Garen and Celine entered, everyone ceased in their steps and took notice of them.

SHHHHHHH!!

The giant sprite flapped her massive wings, with a strong gush of wind she pranced towards Flamingo. She waved about her fingers which were tipped with incredibly sharp nails, almost dagger-like.

CLANG!!

Flamingo’s eyes glew a golden red, the sword in his hand didn’t even move, but in front of her a silver cross appeared in response to the sprite’s attack.

A bright spark bursted between the cross and the giant sprite, sending the giant sprite and Beo flying backwards to the wall again. As they hit the wall, cracks in the stone wall were left in their wake.

The giant sprite was now dizzy, and was unable to get back on her feet.

Flamingo grimaced, and swung his sword in a circular motion with one hand, turning his gaze to Garen and Celine. He had obviously just easily fended off the attacks of Beo’s squad, and along with it, conveniently took down a grumpy giant sprite.

Garen noticed that from the beginning till now, Flamingo had not even bothered to take off his black cloak, he’s been fighting with only one hand this whole time. In other words, these skilled warriors paired with a legendary being are so powerful that normal folks don’t even deserve their need to be serious in fighting them.

"Take care of yourself," Garen said softly to Celine before striding confidently towards Flamingo.

"What’s up? Are you here for the Sword of the Sprites and the Blood of Secrets too?" Flamingo looked at Garen doubtfully, "The Blood of Secrets requires a certain brewing process to work. So even if you get it, it’ll be useless to you. Only members of the Immortal Palace Alliance have the recipe, therefore only if you join us would you be allowed to use enjoy the Blood of Secrets."

Garen shook his head, "I’ve only just heard about the Blood of Secrets, I honestly have no full picture of what’s going on here." He looked around at everyone in the hall, Beo and gang were either knocked out or heavily injured.

"Then why did you come in?" Flamingo was now intrigued, "You should know that only grave danger awaits you here right?"

"Of course," Garen nodded, "My objective is simple, and since you’re a member of the Immortal Palace Alliance, could you please tell me where is Sylphalan?"

Duskdun Shura and Flamingo stood stunned, they exchanged looks and didn’t utter a word. Flamingo’s originally calm face also suddenly turned distressed.

"Syl...phalan….what business do you have with him?" Flamingo was silent for a while, then said this.

Garen didn’t reply, he merely stared at him silently. He knew these two definitely knew the location of Sylphalan. After the many rounds of fighting the group, while Duskdune Shura and Flamingo looked absolutely unscathed, they must have at least suffered some damage or at least exhausted their energy. Hence Garen was confident that if he tried, he could at least inflict heavy damage on them should a fight erupt. Not to mention compared to Beo, right now Garen was closest in terms of skill level to the two of them.

"Screw it, Flamingo." Duskdune Shura suddenly spoke, he slowly walked up to the altar and lightly pulled out the Sword of the Sprites.

SHHHH…..

With a soft sound, the Sword of the Sprites was slowly pulled out from the altar.

"We’ve achieved our objective for this time, you can have the sword. There isn’t what I want here. Let’s go."

Duskdune Shura turned around and left straight through the door.

Chapter 149: Secret Sword 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Flamingo frowned for a bit.

"Hmm, alright. What about the Blood of Secrets."

Duskdune Shura turned the Sword of the Sprites around, and softly popped open the tip of the hilt. Turns out the tip of the hilt hid a small little container, and within it poured out a miniscule amount of dark red blood.

Duskdune Shura skillfully poured the blood into a glass bottle he had in his other hand.

"Here it is. Let’s go, I don’t think this is enough for us to make one portion."

"That will depend on how pure the blood is." Flamingo shrugged, and suddenly swung his sword around his back, hitting the now recovered giant sprite, sending her flying once more, and half fainting again.

"Have the sword!" Duskdune Shura threw the Sword of the Sprites to Flamingo.

Catching the Sword of the Sprites, Flamingo threw away his original weapon and stroked its length with his hand.

"Worlds Will Moan, Sprites Begone!"

HUUMMMMM

The runes on the Sword of the Sprites started glowing along the path his hand stroked. One by one they glowed a bright red until the entire sword was glowing and shaking, making the sound of a low hum and transforming into a bright red longsword.

The red glow from the sword was so bright it illuminated the surroundings of Flamingo until even Flamingo himself was a bright red.

"This is….!!" Garen took a few steps back, his face now filled with rare fear. He had seen great warriors like Duskdune Shura, and he has also met skilled swordsmen like the Eight-Arm Dragon King. Heck, he’s even met powerful werewolves that were only known to legends; yet now, for once, he was afraid.

Flamingo brandished the sword in his hand like a magical light show, it was of such magnificence that Garen couldn’t help but skip a breath now and then. The sight, was truly one to behold, almost like magic!

Flamingo grimaced, and raised the sword high up.

"End!"

The red light suddenly reached a scorching brightness, Flamingo lightly swung it.

SLASH!!!

A bright red curve formed from that swing, and it started to fly towards the giant sprite. The sprite seemed like she was trying to escape, but she simply wouldn’t move, and could only watch in despair as the red curve came close and slashed through her waist.

Without a sound, the sprite started falling into two pieces separated between the waistline, and fell onto the ground. The parts where her waist used to be was now two clean cuts, smooth like polished metal.

The red curve also dimmed out and disappeared after the slash.

The Sword of the Sprites in Flamingo’s hand also dimmed out. His face looked like he was incredibly tired, it seems that the sword consumes a great amount of energy to wield.

Celine was now completely stunned, she could only stare at the Sword of the Sprites with silent alert.

"Should we still try to pick a fight?" She whispered to Garen

He hesitated, and observed the duo before responding in doubt.

"This is not right."

He walked up and blocked the exit of the duo.

"What? Do you want to fight us?" Flamingo looked at Garen doubtfully. Flamingo didn’t look as chill as he was before, his fight with Beo’s Slash Brigade trio earlier definitely injured him internally. He’s not a user of hard Qi, and had obviously been injured by a good amount of heavy firepower. Not to mention he had just used his remaining energy to use the Sword of the Sprites to rid the giant sprite, he must be heavily injured now.

Garen took a look at the Sword of the Sprites in Flamingo’s hand, he was definitely still heavy hearted.

"Well, you seem to have sustained some pretty heavy injuries, so I will not fight you. Duskdune Shura, my request is simple, tell me what’s the use of the blood and give me the Golden Sword Throne, it is the relic key for this area."

Duskdune Shura’s old face made no expression, "Nice observation skills, I’m surprised you could tell we’re heavily injured."

"Just give it to me, I would rather not take advantage of your situation now, but consider this time as a bad miscalculation in your strategy. I’m not sure why you wanted to bait us in here, but this does not affect my need to achieve my final objective." Garen stepped up, his eyes slightly drooping, his body emitted a surge of intimidating energy. He was adjusting his stance and summoning his hardening Qi, he wasn’t sure if the Sword of the Sprites in the hands of Flamingo could cut him, but he was willing to try.

Should a fight break out, for sure both sides would end up heavily injured. Garen might be unscathed for now, but he was still outnumbered, so even though the both of them are heavily injured, he still doesn’t stand a healthy chance.

Duskdune Shura started laughing.

"I’ll let you win this time." He straight took out the palm sized Golden Sword Throne and threw it at Garen, "What a pity, if it wasn’t for those rascals messing up my setup outside, perhaps we could have…...Ah screw it, let’s not talk about it. We will meet again, goodbye."

"Goodbye." Garen caught the Golden Sword Throne, and smiled for abit. He gave way and watched as the two of them left in a single file.

"Let’s follow them out," Garen turned around and told Celine.

Celine nodded in agreement.

The two of them turned around to look at everyone around the room, after a short moment of hesitation, Garen lifted a member of the Slash Brigade in each of his hands, and took quick steps to follow up with Duskdune Shura and Flamingo.

"Be careful, if I’m not wrong, coming in may have been easy, going out is most likely going to be tougher." Celine reminded Garen.

Garen nodded, and at this moment Beo and the bearded man in his arms started to come to.

"That rascal Duskdune Shura, I WILL KILL HIM ONE DAY!" The bearded man moaned softly as he slowly awoke.

"You better take care of yourself first," Garen said, "So many of you versus the two of them, not to mention you even had a giant sprite on your side, yet they still managed to leave in one piece."

"Let go of me!" the bearded man yelled, "Who do you think you are? Do you even know how powerful Duskdune Shura and Flamingo are?!"

"What’s wrong with you? Garen saved you, and yet you don’t even thank him!" Celine glared at him sternly.

"I could’ve easily made it out with or without his help!" the bearded man groaned. He struggled out of Garen’s grasp and took a few clumsy steps away before finally standing straight. Despite his face looking a little pale, he seemed to have regained his mobility.

Garen looked at him with slight, but he couldn’t give a damn, and continued walking until they reached the needle barriers where they encountered the sprites earlier.

Now they could only see the corpses of the two sprites, their bodies nicely sliced through the waist like the giant sprite earlier.

Garen knelt down beside the corpses and gently picked up one half of a sprite’s corpse.

As he touched it, the corpse instantly disintegrated into black dust all over the floor, leaving only its wings. Each sprite had two pairs of locust like wings, Garen thought for a moment, and decided to take two pairs for himself, pocketing it, he quickly stood up and left.

By this time, the bearded man was nowhere to be found.

"This ancient ruin doesn’t look dangerous at all!" Garen said to himself as he rushed out.

Celine jumped and hung onto his shoulders.

"The biggest problem with the sprites’ ruins is the giant sprite, but since Duskdun Shura and Flamingo took care of that for us, we should be set. If you tried coming alone it might’ve been a different story."

"So why did you come here? Don’t tell me it’s because of pure curiousity."

"Nothing much really, it’s just that I’ve read about the ancient ruins for the longest time, and I really didn’t want to miss the opportunity to see one for myself. If I didn’t come, I would’ve never seen things like the sprites, and not to mention that weird magic work of Flamingo’s new sword."

"You’re right, if you hadn’t seen it for yourself, who would’ve believed that Flamingo would gain abilities like that?" Garen felt a little grateful as well.

The two of them continued to rush ahead, the corridor seemed to pass behind them, as their talking didn’t slow them down at all.

"But why aren’t the others anyhow interested in the sprites?" Garen was baffled, "And why did they leave so quickly?"

Suddenly his eyes opened wider than before, as if he just had an epiphany, and Celine too did the same, they both looked at each other.

"THE RUINS MUST BE A TRAP!" Celine yelled.

Without another thought or word, the duo sped up and sprinted even faster towards the exit.

With Beo in one hand, and the Golden Sword Throne in the other, Garen felt a cold breeze coming from the Golden Sword Throne, it made him feel incredibly uneasy. The process of which he obtained the relic key was way too easy, from Duskdune Shura fighting with the Slash Brigade, to all the traps and obstacles being removed by them, plus ending up with being able to pick up the Golden Sword Throne without the slightest effort. It was all too fishy. The members of the Immortal Alliance are never this friendly, it seemed like they were intentionally giving the relic key to Garen.

"I hope nothing bad happens."

Very soon, Celine and Garen made it to the very first ghost faced living room.

WHOOSH

Just as they entered, they saw Duskdune Shura and Flamingo leaping to evade a massive blade’s slash.

Flamingo held onto the glowing Sword of the Sprites firmly as it glowed a bright red, and he stared sternly at the other side of the living room. It wasn’t just him, but there was Duskdune Shura, the bearded man, and some strangers of unknown origins.

Everyone was spread apart, staring at a shadow in the middle of the living room.

"Five more minutes until the ancient ruins collapses! We do not have time, Garen! Quickly come help! Or else we might all not make it out!" Duskdune Shura was the first to notice Garen’s trio arrive.

"What’s going on?!" Garen turned his gaze to the shadowed figure in the middle, then he was stunned.

That being was about the height of a human, with green scales all over and the looks of a sprite. Except that this one didn’t have any wings, and was wielding a green equivalent of the Sword of the Sprites.

By the looks of everyone, it seems like this was a truly intimidating fellow.

As if he could make out the puzzled look on Garen’s face, Duskdune Shura explained, "Originally I was confident I would be able to fight these damned sprites, except we got injured by those rascals earlier, now we can only face this ourselves..."

CLANG!!!

Duskdune Shura took a backstep, evading the slash from the sprite, the sword landed on the ground, leaving marks where it meets the ground.

BANG BANG!

After two loud gunshots, the sprite got shot in the head, and its body disintegrated into many little sprites, flying about, and attacking whoever they find in their path.

Garen tried to keep his calm, these little sprites’ sharp teeth can easily bite through his hardened skin, if he doesn’t pay attention he might lose it.

"Now I’ve achieved my objective, I’ve acquired the Golden Sword Throne, there’s no need for me to be involved in this; I should find a way out as soon as possible"

He turned his gaze to where the exit stairs would’ve been. What was weird, was that there was no door now, it was as if the exit never existed in the first place.

During this short time, Duskdune Shura swept his palm and hit two sprites in front of him, Flamingo followed in sync and slashed them into four clean pieces. Their actions drew the attention of most sprites.

The bearded man on the other hand swung his dagger around blocking the attacks of the sprites. His face was a pale white, his arms were also numb from the continuous attacks, but suddenly he had an epiphany, and pulled out a black grenade.

"Fuck this! If I’m dying, we’re all dying together!" He pulled out the safety ring and threw the grenade to the middle of the room.

Duskdune Shura and Flamingo rapidly retreated to the corner of the room, Flamingo’s Sword of the Sprites kept drawing new red curves in the air, slicing every sprite around him, and making some sort of a half circle defense line between the two of them.

The two of them noticed the bearded man’s action, but they stood unfazed, and only smirked.

Instead it was the trio that just got in that were shocked, one of them quickly took out his gun and aimed it at the bearded man, but it was too late.

"You’re insane!" Celine was the first to notice this, and quickly ducked to hide behind Garen.

Using a grenade in a crowded and tight room like this, even the shockwave alone will be able to cause serious damage to everyone. The bearded man intends to bring everyone down with him!

"Stay safe now! Duck!" Garen too saw the grenade, he took a deep breath and expanded his entire body, before he reached his maximum expansion, he pulled Beo and Celine behind him.

Chapter 150: Secret Sword 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

RUMBLE!!

A loud crash.

A massive fireball blew up inside the living room, red light illuminated everywhere and everything in an instance. Hot air from the fireball gushed out in every direction.

Garen could only feel the red light as he tightly shut his eyelids, but his ears rung from the shockwave, so he couldn’t hear anything. He could only feel a numbness in his head as immense heat wrapped his body and burned him in every exposed spot of skin.

"I’m hurt!!!"

He couldn’t spare time to think, so he started rolling on the ground.

When he opened his eyes once more, half of his clothes were still slightly on fire, the smokes from embers on his shirt were rising from as they sought to burn it all.

He quickly ripped his shirt off and stepped on it to put out the embers.

Smoke filled the living room, nobody could see anything clearly. There were two spots on the ground that were still visibly on fire.

"Are you alright?" He turned around to check on Celine and Beo. Save for the dust filled face, Celine looked pretty alright, while Beo was shook awake by the shockwave and stood up with a loud moan.

"I’m alright! That madman! How could he use a grenade in a place like this! While he may not cherish his life, I cherish mine!" Celine said while spitting out dust and dirt from her mouth.

Garen scrunched up his face as he suddenly heard the sound of low rustles coming from the living room.

He looked about the room trying to determine the source and saw everyone as the smoke started to clear.

Duskdune Shura and Flamingo were still standing right where they were before, unscathed and untouched by the explosion.

The trio that just came in were in a worst state, all of them were bleeding from their ears, one of them lost a chunk of flesh on his right arm, whilst all three of them were all still on fire and desperately trying to put it out.

The bearded man, strangely, was also barely injured, he climbed up and looked at everyone coldly.

At this moment they realised the rustling sound was coming from the ground.

A large amount of sprites burnt to black were on the ground, not dead. In fact despite being charred, they got up almost immediately into the air and regrouped into the form of a man sized sprite.

"Everyone be careful! If we don’t deal with this fucker we’ll never get out!" Duskdune Shura belowed with a serious tone.

"No wonder you baited all these warriors here!" One of the trio, who was a blonde girl, yelled back angrily.

In this moment, the sprite seemed to be fearful of Duskdune Shura and Flamingo, it turned around and instead tried to kill everyone else. This asshole was not afraid of guns or swords, its body was hard beyond belief and even if one were to slice through, it’ll just dispersed and reassemble. This was true immortality!

The bearded man had just thrown out a grenade, and was obviously the number one target for the sprite. The sprite ran straight for him, without even much effort it sliced the bearded man’s dagger in half. It was only when he cowardly ducked and rolled on the floor was he able to evade their attack.

"If I survive this, I will remember this day where you saved my life."

Beo unsheathed his sword and ran towards the sprite to help the bearded man.

Garen evaluated the situation of his own body, while his skin suffered some light burns, he wasn’t hurt too bad that it would affect his ability to fight.

"What now? Even grenades can’t touch this fucker!" Celine asked him softly from behind him.

"No rush." Garen shook his head, "For now it is no threat to us, let’s just observe the situation."

The sprite was definitely powerful, while it didn’t pose a threat to Garen for now, he still had to be careful.

"Garen, are you not going to do anything?" Duskdune Shura noticed his inaction, "If we don’t kill it, none of us are getting out!"

Garen squinted his eyes in intimidation and took a sweep looking around the room, "If even you folks can’t handle him, how will I stand a chance?"

""As long as we can chop off the Sword of the Sprites from the hand of this sprite, its ability to regenerate will be impeded. We need you to help suppress it, I’m carrying the Blood of Secrets. If I get taken down and this asshole gets its hands on it then it’ll be impossible to defeat." Duskdune Shura responded with a stern face.

"Alright," Garen wasn’t sure if he was lying or not, but one thing was for sure: they were all stuck here without an exit, and if he’s right then this could be a way out. Plus, Garen had long wanted to test the abilities of this fellow.

He stepped up, staring at the human like sprite.

The sprite seemed to have sensed something, it stopped in its steps and turned around, it clenched and unclenched its mouthful of sharp teeth, staring in intimation at Garen behind it.

"Watch out!" Celine yelled from behind Garen.

Garen nodded.

BANG!

There was a light shook of the ground as the humanlike sprite ran towards Garen, the air around it made a loud hum as it passed through the living room.

WHOOOSH

The loud tear shook the whole room.

Garen dashed right at it, he put his five fingers in his right arm together like a blade and pointed it straight at the head of the sprite. He was mustering such strength that the veins on the pack of his palm protruded like steel cables.

"THROW ! !"

Garen’s hand blade turned and became a palm facing the incoming Sword of the Sprites wielded by the charging humanlike sprite.

BANG!!

The two of them crashed into each other, the sprite was lifted into the air within a split second and thrown back like a kite on a draft, the great force plus the shockwave made it impossible to disintegrate into little sprites.

"Do it now!"

Duskdune Shura made low growl, and took a step back.

A red line flew from his back and it welcomed the backwards flying sprite coming in his direction.

SLASH!

The body of the sprite was instantly sliced into half, spinning towards the wall on the right.

Ah!!!

The sprite made one last moan in pain, before disintegrating into millions of specks of dust.

With a loud clang, Flamingo sheathed his sword and pulled out the Green Sword of the Sprites from the wall.

Garen meanwhile was breathing deep breaths on the other side of the room.

"Alright, let’s go."

He led the way headed in the direction of Duskdune Shura and Flamingo, as the wall behind the duo opened to reveal the exit staircase.

Celine leaped and hung onto Garen’s shoulders.

Beo, the bearded man, and the other three were shocked beyond belief.

A monster they had no logical way of defeating, was completely annihilated within a few seconds. Everyone who was able to make it this far was the best of the best, or else they wouldn’t have been able to survive till now, however after seeing what happened just now, they were all shook.

That sprite had fought them all, they were very aware of just how powerful it was, and yet Garen had only used one palm technique and he sent it flying across the room, in fact he was able to do it with such skill that it didn’t disintegrate. Not to mention the way Flamingo cleaned up the end with a slash of his sword, it was of a whole different level.

"You have become much more powerful," Duskdune Shura said to Garen who was walking beside him now.

"It’s just that I became quicker," Garen admitted timidly as he headed straight for the exit, "This time I’ll let you go, but next time I will defeat you head on!"

"I look forward to seeing you try," Duskdune Shura grimaced.

Flamingo looked at Garen with suspicion, thinking of something nobody knew. From the moment Garen mentioned Sylphalan, Flamingo has been acting weird, in fact he seemed to have been less cocky since then.

After this whole expedition, Garen felt pretty fulfilled. He had achieved half of his objectives, firstly was the acquisition of the Golden Sword Throne, second was that he was able to indirectly fight Duskdune Shura. Sadly Duskdune Shura was heavily injured this time, so it wasn’t a fair fight, and even if he wasn’t, he was still covered by Flamingo. With the two of them present, Garen had zero confidence in being able to hold up in a fair fight.

**************

Outside the tomb

Packs upon packs of Werewolves started surrounding the entrance to the tomb. Everywhere around the forest was filled with large wolves and Werewolves. Their leader, a tall and buff werewolf with black mane that looked like a lion’s mane, stared at the tomb’s entrance with his brows tightly held together, thinking of something.

Not far away, in the village and between the houses, Su Lin had somehow started walking with Joseph and were trying to sneakily observe the spot surrounded by the Werewolves.

"How’s the situation like?" Su Lin asked Joseph softly.

"Can’t tell, it’s too far."

Joseph shook his head, "The wolf kind lost so many of their members, they definitely won’t let this go easily, this is a matter of vengeance for them so they seem to have brought a large number and surrounded the perimeter."

"What an annoyance. We don’t even know when Garen and the group are coming out," Sulin said as she frowned, "The Immortal Palace Alliance members are just here for the Blood of Secrets, but the Slash Brigade wants to kill Duskdune Shura plus some unknown objective of theirs. What does this have to do with Garen? Did he go in just so he could fight Duskdune Shura? Not to mention Celine..."

Su Lin really couldn’t figure out why Garen went in. As for the still mysterious Celine, he even had less of an idea.

Although it looked like Garen was here to settle a score with Duskdune Shura, but in reality it seemed like he had other intentions, and Su Lin knew of this.

Garen that rascal, he went from a mortal to gradually growing his strength level by level, and then gaining respect in the martial arts communities. After which within a short time he started defeating greater and greater opponents, becoming stronger and stronger until he fought Andrela and became affirmed as the champion of the 12 Gates of the South, then recognized by the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate as their official Sky Warrior, he was certainly an incredible force.

He had seen Garen from his early days, and had been there for him every step of the way. In fact, he even managed to get Garen to owe him two favors. This time Garen had invited him to help pursue Duskdune Shura, but by the way things were looking right now, he was just baffled.

"Whatever it is, just don’t get in trouble!" Su Lin muttered to himself in worry.

"They’ve come out!" Joseph exclaimed softly.

Su Lin quickly turned to look at the tomb entrance, the sky was slowly lighting up, and he could almost make out the situation.

At the entrance of the tomb, Garen carried Celine and walked out slowly. He had some burn marks on his, but his expression still looked like he was pretty chill, obviously everything was alright.

As he noticed the surrounding Werewolves, he expression sank, and he just stood there silently.

Very soon, another two more people protruded from the tomb entrance, it was Duskdune Shura and Flamingo, one behind the other, walking out calmly. Their mere presence created a ruckus in the Werewolves.

The leader of the pack howled with his head in the air.

Ahhhooooo~~~~!

The sound was one of despair and anger, it looked at Duskdune Shura and Flamingo with a deadly glare, as if it was about to explode anytime now.

A large pack of Werewolves prepared to prance on the two of them, the deep growls and howls of the Werewolves filled the air, it sounded and looked like there were hundreds upon hundreds of them.

Garen squinted at the two of them standing beside him, and took a step away so he at least had some distance.

"Looks like their issue with the Werewolves are much larger than mine..." He lifted the side of his lip in a sly smile, looking right at Duskdune Shura.

If given the chance, Garen definitely wouldn’t give up the opportunity to kill Duskdune Shura. Although he didn’t have any sort of deadly vendetta against him, but Duskdune Shura did try to kill him once, and Su Lin also wanted Duskdune Shura dead for something else.

Not to mention, he was incredibly interested in the vial of Blood of Secrets being held by Duskdune Shura.

Long, despaired howls welcomed the sunrise, Duskdune Shura could feel Garen’s uneasy and unfriendly glare from behind him.

"Well this is tricky." He knew that if he gave Garen the right opportunity, Garen wouldn’t even think twice about ending his life.

"Flamingo, looks like I’m going to need your help to keep these Werewolves busy. I didn’t expect that amongst the Werewolves there would someone who would be unaffected by my tricks," Duskdune Shura said to Flamingo under his breath.

"You sure you can take on the one behind you? In the state that you’re in?" Flamingo frowned in response.

"Even if I can’t, I must!" Duskdune Shura smiled slightly, "I have not felt exhiliration like this for many many years."

"I’ll leave the Werewolves to you." His face resumed its usual demeanor.

"Leave them to me." Flamingo unsheathed his longsword, welcoming the arrival of the Werewolves.

Duskdune Shura turned around and faced Garen.

"By the looks of it you’re not going to give up this opportunity are you?"

"I’m glad you understand." Garen smiled.

RUMBLE!!

Both of them took off in a flash, leaving a crater in their wake. Two shadows dashed towards the woods one behind the other.

"Today will be the day of your death!" Garen increased the velocity of his feet, and sped up with a loud bang.

Chapter 151: The Chase 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"They’ve started fighting!" Joseph said,"Su Lin, those two freaks are fighting!"

"One of them is my friend…," Su Lin corrected him,"could you please not call him a freak?"

"Oh...I’m sorry, I was too excited."

The two of them could see Duskdune Shura leading with Garen in the chase as they dashed into the formation of the Werewolves. Like two bulldozers, where they hit the formation, Werewolves were sent flying. Even someone far far away could hear the sunken footsteps.

Very quickly, they disappeared into the shadows.

Soon, a small group of people emerged from the tomb entrance. First off it was the three strangers who had just entered, then there was the bearded man and Beo, everyone in this group looked like a pile of mess.

Upon seeing what had transpired outside the entrance, the group quickly ran to stand with Celine, in anticipation of an attack from the Werewolves.

What was interesting however, was that only a few Werewolves attacked them, while the majority instead were headed towards Flamingo.

At this moment, Flamingo was attracting everyone’s attention.

He seemed to be chanting something, and as he did, he would stroke his sword ever so softly, and wherever his fingers touched the sword, it would glow in red. In total, nine runes started glowing bright, lava red.

*************************************

Bang!!

Garen and Duskdune Shura’s arms hit each others, some bits of loose cloth was sent flying.

The both of their arms kept colliding, as the fought furiously, letting out sounds like thunder each time their arms collided. As they fought like a hurricane, they slowly pushed their way out of the Werewolves’ formation as well.

"You cannot kill me," Duskdune Shura suddenly produced a hand knife technique with his right hand, which was blocked just in time by Garen.

"How can you be so sure if you don’t let me try?" Garen smiled.

Pow!!

The both them retreated away from each other, creating a small distance between them.

"First Dan!"

Garen put his foot down, and the ground shook violently, his body suddenly expanded. He gestured his right hand into a hand knife and went straight towards Duskdune Shura.

Bang!!

His hand knife hit a tree instead, littering wood shavings all over the floor. The tree shook slightly, and the top of it started slanting by a bit.

Duskdune Shura had evaded his attack by moving to the side, his face was hit by one of the bigger splinters, and it was obvious he was hurting a little from it. This made his expression change.

"Increase in speed seems to have also increase your strength. If that’s the case..."

He too put his down onto the floor, drawing a weird curve shape with it, he was neither quick nor slow, but just fast enough to evade Garen’s second hand knife attack.

He turned around, and revealed his right palm, which by now had some sort of a black mark on it in the shape of a V, like someone had painted it on with ink.

"The first Dragon’s Gate!"

Bang!

Garen’s face dropped, he thought he had evaded it.

He was certain he had seen himself evade it early, but still somehow he got struck. He felt a his right waist going numb, just like the time he first got hit by a palm technique.

"Fuck!" Garen didn’t want to believe in this witchcraft, so he returned with another palm,"I refuse to believe you hit me!"

Since he couldn’t evade it anyways, he decided to repay pain with pain, and released his fury onto Duskdune Shura.

However, he only managed to hit the seems of his clothes.

"Second Dragon’s Gate!"

Again it came, when he heard Duskdune Shura’s voice, Garen hastily retreated.

"Serial Swing Form!"

Both of his palms rapidly drew up a circle.

However, once more, Garen saw his Serial Swing Form hit nothing but air!

Just as he was about thit Duskdune Shura’s arm, his opponent suddenly twirled downwards, and sneakily evaded the collision, then lightly slapped Garen’s stomach.

Pow !!

"What is happening?!" His pupils dilated, he could only feel numbness in his waist and nothing else, his internal energies were also starting to get messed up.

"Third Dragon’s Gate!" Duskdune Shura announced, with a quick turn of his feet, he was suddenly behind Garen, with his back against him, he hit Garen’s tailbone with his right palm.

"Second Dan! Rush Form!"

Garen scrunched up his face, his body expanded even more now as it started turning into a sinister green and black colour. He rushed forward with his shoulders, aiming directly for his opponent’s chest.

But that weird, sinister feeling from earlier came back once more. Duskdune Shura evaded Garen’s attack with a simple turn of his feet, and hit Garen in his tailbone again.

Bang!

Garen staggered forward a few steps, where his foot had stepped on, he raise grass and wood shavings into the air, creating an opportunity for him to pull his distance away from his opponent.

The two of them now once again stood facing each other in the same distance as before.

"Final Hit!" Duskdune Shura rushed towards Garen, his body now turned into a black shadow, his arms were like electric from an eel, the speed much much faster than the previous three hits.

"Bring it on!!" Garen bellowed, sounds of a python hissing suddenly started appearing around him, he tried to block with both of his arms.

But they were no good, the opponent’s palms easily slipped past his Red Jade Palm’s protection, and made their way towards Garen’s chest.

"Double Shots Form!"

At this moment, Garen focused himself, both of his palms shot out like lightning and went straight for Duskdune Shura’s chest. The breeze around them shifted from a soft blow to a loud tear in the sky.

Since he couldn’t evade it anyways, might as well stop trying to evade and just return pain with pain.

"It’s useless," Duskdune Shura, barely flinched, and continued forward.

Bang!

Duskdune Shura somehow evaded Garen’s attack again, he now landed both his palms on Garen’s chest. As the force and shockwave settled into Garen’s chest, he paused for a moment, then he was sent flying backwards.

Sensing the response from his palms, it wasn’t enough! Duskdune Shura focused his sights on Garen.

Without a moment of hesitation, Duskdune Shura jumped up in a split second and was suddenly flying in parallel with Garen’s backwards flying body!

"Go back down onto the ground!"

His gestured to elbow Garen with his left hand, as it expanded and turned black, like a concrete pillar it hit Garen in the abdomen.

Boom!

Garen was sent straight to the ground, forming a crater around where he landed.

"The Fifth Dragon’s Gate! It is finished." Duskdune Shura lifted his right palm.

Garen was not done.

[I refuse to believe I can’t hit you!]

"Red Jade Palm!"

Bang !

The pine forest was filled with the sound of strong winds rushing through them, in between the leaves rustling and trees moving, there were still the occasional tweet from a bird or two.

Everything seem to have sunk into silence in a sudden, leaves from the pine trees fell like rain.

Meanwhile in the crater.

Garen and Duskdune Shura’s right palms met each other, but neither were moving.

Suddenly, both of their bodies started shaking violently, the vibrations were being sent back and forth each other’s bodies, this was a highly advanced technique of defensive vibration only mastered by the greatest warriors.

Duskdune Shura’s face paled, he suddenly took three steps backwards.

Bang, bang bang, each step he made left obvious footprints in the ground.

The edge of his lips opened slightly to let out a small streak of blood.

"Fuck me…."

Garen slowly got up, his face now forming a sly smile.

"How is this possible?!" Duskdune Shura’s eye opened wide in disbelief. "How could you... how could you still move?!"

After being hit by his first four out of seven Dragon Gates, no matter how strong one’s Body Hardening was, it would still require at least ten plus minutes to get up, let alone move like this! He simply couldn’t comprehend what was transpiring before his eyes.

"It’s quite disappointing," Garen moved his body like nothing had hit him,"in reality you only managed to seal two of your palms. My second Dan can manipulate all of my inner energies, creating a high speed metabolism to tackle arteries that are sealed. Plus a little bit of assistance from some blood boiling. Not to mention, you didn’t use enough energy..."

Garen pulled the remaining cloth on his upper body with one hand, revealing his statuelike muscular upper body.

With his long purple hair casually draped over the shoulder of his muscular body, Garen’s both eyes suddenly glowed a bright red.

"This…...is the real ‘finishing’"

Bang!

Before his last word dropped, Garen made a strong stomp on the crater, and dashed towards Dushdune Shura in a split second.

The both of them collided into each other, their arms exchanging attacks, releasing loud bangs over and over again.

Duskdune Shura was visibly moving backwards, as he tried hard to defend against Garen’s endless attacks.

Ka Cha!

One of the pine trees was chopped by Garen’s hand knife, like a thin bamboo tree’s stem being sliced, it fell onto the next pine tree.

The both of them fought while moving about the pine tree forest, as they moved further and deeper into the forest.

"Red Jade!"

Garen’s two palms suddenly glowed red, and moved in parallel towards Duskdune Shura.

With a loud bang, Duskdune Shura’s both arms tried to block the attack but he was still pushed back for ten plus steps. By the end of those ten steps, he spat out some blood.

With his back against a nearby pine tree, Duskdune Shura could only feel a strong burning sensation from the parts of his arms where he had used to block Garen’s attacks. As he lifted them up close to inspect, he noticed that they had started to form blisters like they had been burned by fire.

"This is...Firestream Fist??!! You...you...were able to master hardening techniques and still perfect this level of Second Secret Techniques!!??" Duskdune Shura’s face was filled with disbelief.

Garen smiled a little.

"You were actually able to recognise it," since the opponent had mistook his Red Jade Palm for Firestream Fist, he decided to play along. It was true that Red Jade Palm had absorbed the attributes of Firestream Fist and Dark Iron Palm, in fact it was an enhanced version of both.

"Again!"

"Red Jade, Single Shot Form!"

Garen dashed forward, his right palm extended.

His entire right palm glowed red, releasing a great amount of heat, like iron burned to red, it aimed straight for his opponent’s chest.

"Dragon Overturns Ocean Technique!!" Duskdune Shura yelled at the top of his voice, his face flashed a bright red, obviously showing he had used some sort of secret technique to trigger a hidden ability.

A low rumble started ringing in Garen’s head, as if a massive masculine lion had appeared in front of him and was about to prance on him.

"Bravery Repression technique? I know that too!" Garen scoffed, suddenly a strong aura of courage appeared around him, the formless energy concentrated to form a massive white elephant charging towards the lion.

Bang!! Both apparitions disappeared at the same time.

Duskdune Shura fell backwards like a kite that just had its string cut, his mouth still spitting a massive amount of blood mid air, as his face turned a deadly pale.

Da! Da! Da! Da!

A string of gunshots echoed, a massive amount of bullets landed on Garen, creating a ton of sparks, forcing him to take a few steps back. This machine gun’s bullet felt weird, it was incredibly strong, and even when it hit the body of Garen it felt like a string of needles had stabbed him.

"Run!" A sound came out of nowhere.

While Garen was still suppressed by the machine gun, Duskdune Shura immediately made a roll as soon as he landed and got back on his feet to run towards the depth of the pine forest.

When the gunshots finally stopped, Garen got back to his senses and noticed Duskdune Shura had ran, he quickly made chase.

"Running away already? You aren’t even done letting me experience all the forms of Seven Dragon Gate!"

With one running and the other chasing, the both of them ran even further away from the Werewolves’ formation, the elevation around them increased, it seemed they were headed uphill.

Chapter 152: The Chase 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was hard to determine how much time had passed beneath the blazing sun. Garen, who had just increased his speed, was slightly faster than Duskdune Shura’s secret method. Their journey eventually took them to the edge of a sheer cliff.

At this point, they were so far away from their initial location that it was impossible to tell just how far they’d traversed.

The cliff shot up from the earth below, a face of white contrasted against a surface of dense, dark green pine trees densely clumped together.

Both of them stood firmly on the rocks found in between those pine trees.

Duskdune Shura was standing up above cliff with Garen just below him.

"Not running away anymore?"

Duskdune Shura wiped a blood stain off his cheek.

"Do you want the Blood of Eternal Life?"

Garen was taken aback at the sudden comment.

Duskdune Shura laughed and said.

"You and I both stand at the edge of body hardening technique. In this world, how many others are there just like us? Why must you fight me?"

"You almost killed my friend’s family, as well as I. This is my reason." Garen shook his head as he explained. "We hold no grudges against each other. Perhaps we can even be friends in another world. If only…"

"Yes… If only…" Duskdune Shura sighed in accordance with him. He then raised an arm and revealed the blisters that covered all over his hands. It was the effect of the Red Jade Palm. "Have you met Palosa?"

"What about him?"

"The current you reminds me of him in the past." Duskdune Shura brought past memories to mind. "Palosa was like you before he became the Saint of Fist Technique, undefeated among the younger generation. He was not much weaker than the Grandmaster of combat of the older generations as well. Unfortunately…"

"Unfortunately what?" Garen stared at him calmly.

"Unfortunately you’re not as magnanimous as he is."

Garen’s eyes narrowed.

"Are you implying that I’m taking advantage of your injury? Isn’t it logical to make good use of an opportunity presented before you?"

"You’ll never surpass him." Duskdune Shura said with a gentle smile, pointing his toe and leaping backwards, landing on the very edge of the cliff.

"It’s plain logic to grab hold of any means to an end. If that were not the case wouldn’t have become what you are today.." Garen followed him closely upward. "That was your friend was it not? I’ll send him to your way once I’ve finished dealing with you."

"You don’t understand." Duskdune Shura shook his head slowly. "That is the difference between you and I."

His head tilted to look at the vast blue sky.

"The undefeated and the unconquerable. No one is a match for him as long as he lives, be it the top of this generation or the next. I look forward to our next encounter."

He smiled and fell backwards, disappearing beyond the edge of the cliff.

Garen, in shock, swiftly rushed to the top, his gaze following the sheer drop.

His eyes met Duskdune Shura gripping his black sword with both hands, blade sliding down embedded into the cliff wall. A deep gash followed his wake as he screeched downward.

There was another black knife further down the cliff. Mimicking his previous action, Duskdune Shura swiftly went down the sheer cliff of a few hundred meters. Two jet black horses met them on the cliff floor.

The person in a black coat on one of the horses looked up and stared at Garen.

Garen could see his opponent’s face from afar.

It was the face of a beautiful woman, an eyepatch covering one of her two eyes.

"King Charlotte the third… " Garen muttered. "It must be you in the forest just now. Unfortunately, you’re too late. How much can Duskdune Shura recover with his current age?"

Duskdune Shura had heat injected into his body by his Red Jade Palm. In a further aggravation of his injury, he did not have the time to treat his wound as he was being pursued for an extended period of time. It would definitely leave a mark for someone his age.

Garen started toward the way back, as he knew it would be pointless to keep up the pursuit.

He needed to get back to Celine and Su Lin immediately. Although the werewolf clan’s target was Flamingo and not them, there was no guarantee that they would escape the crossfire unscathed.

Garen put his hand into his pocket and fiddled with the Golden Sword Throne along the way back. This item the size of a pen holder was unharmed during the intense battle as he was keeping an eye out to ensure it was kept out of the way.

Garen’s mind flowed like a pleasant, incessant breeze into his mind.

His attention was on the attribution table, which was shaded in maroon while on the journey back.

His attribute points kept increasing at a steady pace. Although it was not as fast as the time he touched the Antique of Tragedy, it was still a considerable rate.

After the intense battle with Duskdune Shura, his potential stats were at 200%

‘Strength 2.66, Agility 1.82, Vitality 2.15, Intelligence 1.53, Potential 214%.’

"It looks like I wasn’t even strong enough to keep a heavily injured Duskdune Shura. He must have been horrifyingly strong in his prime. He is indeed the best in his generation." Garen felt a twinge of helplessness in his stomach.

"Should I increase my attributes first or my secret technique?" He hesitated. He currently had two secret techniques, the Mammoth Secret Technique and the Red Jade Palm. The remaining secret techniques had been absorbed by the two primary techniques for an enhancing effect.

"With the Red Jade Palm, I can barely manage to injure Duskdune Shura if used as a surprise attack. However, even so the damage isn’t heavy enough to determine the battle’s outcome. It could be used as a normal combat technique with an additional effect. If I can amplify the Red Jade Palm, its effect should be much stronger than the Mammoth; the only problem being that the remaining training lies with Celine. It might be troublesome if she finds out that I mastered the Red Jade Palm in such a short amount of time."

Garen hesitated.

He felt the limitless flow of energy emanate from the Golden Sword Throne.

"Whatever. I should stabilize my injury first. I definitely had some internal injury from Duskdune Shura’s last punch after he sealed me with two of his Seven Dragon Gate punches.

He quickly focused his vision onto Vitality in his attribution stat.

0.3 points of Vitality were added instantly, jumping from 2.15 to 2.45.

His whole body temporarily numbed. He started feeling an itch within his bones and a cold breeze flowing out from his brain onto his whole body. It felt as comfortable as taking a cold bath in a hot sunny day. The internal injury he had on the palm of his hand quickly faded as well.

"There are a few points left." Garen felt the increasing flow of potential flowing but didn’t use it after some deliberation.

There was no difference between adding the attributes and improving the body’s potential in the long term. He will definitely become stronger and stronger in the future. He would be extremely powerful even in his normal state.

Increasing the skill level of a secret technique grants the practitioner an immediate boost in strength. However, the power of the secret technique is not limitless, and once capped would be very difficult to increase any further in the long run. Though secret techniques could be combined to achieve an even greater effect, realistically, the power level was fixed, and one would be less than powerless when stripped of his secret technique.

The main point was that with good innate talent, one was able to surpass a majority of fighters, no matter the secret technique. The foundation of one’s body surpasses that of any secret technique.

The increment of the secret technique might improve the body’s quality but it could be limited as it was still dependent on the prowess of the secret technique itself. It would only see a dramatic increase in its early stages.

One was preparing for the long run, one was preparing for what was ahead.

"I’ll think about this once I collect more points." Garen resisted his impulse in using the attribute points as he sprinted into the Pinehill forest.

Soon, the grave of the ancient ruins behind the abandoned village crept up from the horizon. The innumerable corpses of the werewolf clan began to come into view.

The leader of the werewolf with the black mane could be seen hanging above a big pine tree with a silver sword nailed into its body.

The landscape was showered with blood; the ground a blend of crimson and grass green.

Blood was prevalent across the scene. Werewolf corpses were strewn across the ground, Some beheaded, corpses still. Yet others were split into half from head to toe, and some were cut clean from the waist. The ways that the werewolves died rivaled their many corpses.

Death reigned the field.

Garen felt like he was stepping onto a thick wet carpet as he trudged onwards. His boots would ripple with the sound of water as his feet made contact. It was none other than the sound of blood.

The smell of it was so strong that Garen furrowed as he walked past through the sea of corpses to the entrance of the grave.

It looked like it had been caved in; the entrance was blocked with gravel.

"Su Lin!!"

Garen shouted.

"Celine!!"

His shouting continued as he walked towards the village’s houses.

"Su Lin, Celine! Are you guys dead yet?!"

Soon, Garen went back to the building that they were hiding in. It was completely silent inside. He trotted towards the staircase and went upstairs.

He went up to the second floor, and then the third floor and finally to the room they were all initially hiding.

The door creaked as he opened it.

On the ground laid three bodies. Celine and Su Lin were among them. There was another young man who seemed like the policeman that he met from the Demon Hunters.

All three of them were supine; whether they had any injuries was a mystery.

Garen knelt down to examine them closer. They were merely unconscious, and apart from torn garments, there were no physical injuries at all.

He was relieved to see they were unharmed. He walked to the far end of the room and begin kindling a fire with several pieces of wooden furniture and a piece of flint he had in his bag.

He used a metal can to boil some water as the fire burned.

He sat silent, waiting for the trio to come to.

After a while, with a painful expression on her face, Celine was the first one to moan as she slowly got up from the ground.

The first thing this fellow checked was her shirt when she got up.

She had the same white tee shirt and jeans as Garen, except it was torned and holes could be seen everywhere.

"When did you return?" Celine looked at Garen who was sitting in the corner.

"Not long ago." Garen poured out the hot water into a paper cup and blew gently as he waited for the water to cool down. "We’ll wait for the other one to wake up and leave. The werewolves will never stop now that so many of their kind had died. We better not get caught up in this."

He noticed a few fresh cuts from Celine’s shirt and asked, "You fought?"

Celine rolled her eyes. "Of course I did! Those two would be dead otherwise! That sword wielding Flamingo person is too strong…"

Traces of fear still lingered as she recalled her fight.

"His sword technique was inhuman!! There were red beams coming out from his sword as he simply waved the sword around. The red beams cut down whatever was in its path! It was horrible." Celine caressed a singe mark on her supposedly white belt.

"This was where I managed to block Flamingo’s sword strike. We were lucky he did not use that crazy sword technique often and used ordinary sword techniques most of the time."

Chapter 153: The Journey Back 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What of the werewolf clan?" Garen asked as he drank the hot water he had poured"What of the werewolf clan?" Garen asked as he drank the hot water he had poured out a while ago.

"A lot of them died. In the end there was a white werewolf with claws that were a meter long, which looked like some sort of a weapon. He fought with Flamingo, but the both of them took it somewhere else not long after. I used up my remaining energy bringing these two here after that and passed out. I don't know what happened after that"

She gave the two fainted men a few quick presses as if she was trying to relieve their dizziness. She then got up and sat beside Garen.

"Oh right. The white werewolf was really strong! He was standing toe to toe with Flamingo. He should be the leader of the werewolf clan. I’ve heard that highly skilled werewolves are going after Flamingo as he had killed an important figure in the clan."

"Flamingo was heavily injured." Garen shook his head, "The white werewolf might have noticed this and didn’t want to retreat because it would be hard to have his revenge if Flamingo fled."

At this moment, Su Lin and Joseph were slowly coming to.

"Alright let’s go. This place is reeks with blood and will definitely attract a lot of people. We should leave immediately." Garen calmly said as he stood up.

"Where are we going?" Celine jumped and landed her small, dollish body on Garen’s shoulder.

"Please stop sitting on my shoulder all the time." Garen frowned.

Celine’s pants were tattered, and exposing a good half of her hips and buttocks. It felt completely different when she sat onto her shoulder with her bare skin touching him.

He would have felt nothing if she really had been a young girl. This girl however obviously wasn’t; and on top of that she had an amazingly hot body when transformed.

"Don’t tell me you’re interested in this young girl’s body?" Celine smiled slyly. "I might be able to satisfy that.. since it’s you we’re talking about~~"

"I see you’re still talkative even when heavily injured." Garen shook his shoulder and Celine almost fell down as she weakly moaned in pain. She had a severe internal injury, so severe that she had trouble balancing herself.

"My body is weak and small, please be gentle with it, now~~" Celine quickly balanced herself and spoke in a weak voice.

"Keep this up and I will throw you off my shoulder." Garen was tired of her fussing and started to pack up his things. Celine decided to hold her tongue from then.

Su Lin and Joseph were still lying on the ground, still disorientated. Garen walked towards the duo and scooped them both up with one hand, and proceeded to leave the room thereafter

Both of them were clearly confused, it was as if they weren't fully conscious.

"Hey! What the-" Su Lin struggled drunkenly as he tried to release himself from Garen. However he couldn’t move an inch under Garen’s clamped hand.

Garen ignored their writhing and quickly went down stairs, as he looked at the grave’s direction that was bathed in fresh blood.

"We should get ourselves a souvenir since we’re already here."

""What kind of souvenir are you looking for?" Celine asked curiously.

Garen didn’t reply her. He walked back to the battlefield filled with werewolf corpses and stood in front of the black werewolf leader.

The black werewolf was nailed onto the tree with his chest wide open, revealing solid, black muscles.

Garen put down both of them and reached his hand out towards the black werewolf’s right claw and pulled it. With a click, the black werewolf’s claw was torn from the body. Garen carefully put it away on his person.

"A sharp claw from the black wolf and the sprite’s wings. I should find a collection room to store these things. Not everyone comes across these everyday." Garen smiled. "Let’s go."

At this moment, almost sober, Su Lin and Joseph saw again the desolate, blood soaked scene, limbs and body parts strewn everywhere. Both of their faces went pale, even though they had just seen it awhile ago.

"Let’s go to the nearest city from here, Pinehill City. Duskdune Shura managed to escape. How are the people from Slash doing?" Garen asked as he lead the way.

"The Slash team should be heading back now. They took the opportunity to escape amidst the werewolf clan’s fight against Flamingo. They ran faster than us." Celine said, her voice slightly down "So, we just head back?"

"Do you have a better idea?" Garen replied coldly. He climbed one of the village’s buildings and looked toward the horizon, trying to figure out which way was the way back.

"I really don’t get why we came here in the first place." Celine said helplessly.

Su Lin smiled wryly as he looked at Joseph who was just beside him.

"What do you plan to do now?"

Joseph mimicked the smile on his own lips.

His original plan last night had been to disrupt the werewolf clan’s hunting ceremony and end it for good. Never in his dreams did he expect to be involved in this strange incident. He felt like he became a main character after being an observer for the past twenty years.

"Let’s talk about it when we go back. My family and friends are all in Pinehill City. No matter how powerful the werewolf clan is, I doubt they would attack the city when the Demon Hunters and garrison are on the watch.

"You never know." Su Lin shrugged his shoulder. "It’s impossible to distinguish between a normal human and a werewolf before they transform. No one would be able to expect their ambush from within the city. In either case, we need to head back now. Come to the federation when you get the chance. Don’t go bailing out on me now!"

"I know. I know."

They walked into Pinehill forest. through Dahl the Falls in the direction of Pinehill City. Celine was in charge of looking out for danger from their surroundings.

Garen was silent all the way through as he felt the endless flow of energy enter his body.

They managed to arrive Jiu Gu Clan’s territory in dusk.

The clan’s female leader greeted them with much hospitality as she let them rest after the long journey.

However, they kept pressing on shortly after, arriving at a hotel in Pinehill City sometime after 9pm.

**********

The next day, dawn.

Garen was sitting on a sofa on the second floor of the hotel, which was beside a small red table. On top of it was a cup of black coffee.

Garen had sat on the sofa after a shower. He then poured a cup black coffee for himself and knocked it back swiftly.

Knock knock.

"Come in; it’s unlocked."

The door slowly opened as Celine, in her white pyjamas, came into the room rubbing her eyes and yawning at the same time.

"Where is Su Lin?"

"He went to the telegraph station early in the morning to arrange a flight for us from the Federation. Right now’s a good show of just how important he is. We would have had to take a flight from the nearest big city away Pinehill City if it were not for him, but with him around, we leave this place whenever we want."

Garen drank his warm, bitter coffee again. The concentrated aroma of the coffee dissolved across the room it disappeared past his lips.

There was a T-junction just outside of the hotel, pointing at Pinehill City. The sun was still in slumber, and yet a blend of horses and carriages rang through the streets.

"We met sprites and demon hunters yesterday, and right after that is a normal day. It felt like I was in a dream." Garen shook his head as he spoke.

"Do you feel uncomfortable seeing normal people with special abilities everywhere?" Celine pulled a stool in front of Garen and sat down on it.

"I can manage that, but that Joseph from yesterday had a strange look on his face when he returned. It felt like he had got a new life or something." Garen recalled that man’s strange expression the day before.

"Looks like the clan of werewolves have somethi.ng restraining them from revealing their identities to ordinary people. But what could it be." Celine was slightly curious.

"That’s not our business in any case. Duskdune Shura was heavily wounded by me, and he won’t be at his peak anymore, even if he recovers. But even that might not be the case, what with that Blood of Eternal Life he was talking about.." Garen didn’t know what it was.

"Don’t worry so much about it. We didn’t come here specifically to kill Duskdune Shura." Celine curled her lips. "That’s the Federation’s job. All we need to do is stand by the sidelines and wish them luck."

"That’s true. Well, whatever. That’s the end of that."

"Indeed it is." Su Lin barged into the room. He was dressed in a white shirt with a black windbreaker and black trousers, carrying good amounts of swagger with his eye catching red hair that complemented his handsome face and golden earring on one of his ears.

What’s even more shameless is the cologne he had on. It’s strong smell invaded the room as he entered.

"What do you think about Suya’s number thirteen blue demon aroma series I just got from the perfume store?" Su Lin asked with a charming smile on his face. He could have seduced many a girl with that.

"It’s disgusting." Celine replied as she immediately covered her nose.

"No way…" Su Lin’s expression immediately disappeared. "Alright alright. I’ve received news a while ago; we’ll end the Duskdune Shura operation here, as another international criminal was involved in it: Flamingo. Flamingo’s threat level is one step higher than Duskdune Shura’s, and this incident had shocked the whole International Police Joint Organization. They’ve sent a team to investigate this matter yesterday, and confirmed that Duskdune Shura was heavily injured, whereas Flamingo sustained minor injuries. The pair was confirmed to have accomplices with them.

"Does that mean the International Police Joint Organization is going to handle this situation for good?" Garen whispered.

"Yes, our Slash team from the Federation will only provide support for them. Our focus now has shifted beyond just Duskdune Shura, but also an even more dangerous criminal, Flamingo." Su Lin answered solemnly. "You may not know this, but Flamingo is that guy with that sword that emitted red beams. He was involved in a major crime in the Republic of the Tulip a long time ago, where he murdered three generals, twelve field officers and almost the whole army’s upper echelon in a single night. The Republic of Tulip has been trying to kill him for the past thirteen years, but to no avail."

"That ferocious!" Celine was shocked. "The Republic of the Tulip is the country with the strongest military in the world, and they still couldn’t do anything about him?"

"Nothing. Rumors say that he once destroyed five tanks with just his sword." Su Lin shook his head.

"Tch…" Celine was speechless, but suddenly turned her head and looked at Garen.

Garen then shook his head. "Even I can’t penetrate through a tank’s steel armor. It’s much easier for him since he uses a sword."

"Both of you are monsters. Although you’re weaker than him, you’re not that far off." Celine started to laugh. "Well, I’m counting on you to protect me, then. You are Erudas’ mentor, surely you wouldn’t let him die while you watch from the sidelines."

"Speaking of which what have you done? What’s the connection between Erudas and the Poker Organization? Are you planning drag me into this without any rhyme or reason? That’s not happening" Garen said as he scowled.

"It’s not a big deal, really. I foiled one of the Poker Organization’s plans in Weisman and saved Erudas. They have been trying to kill us ever since. That’s it." Celine summarised.

"I will deal with the Poker Organization. I haven’t repaid them for attacking us yet." Su Lin started sneering. "Be it from the organization or a household’s point of view, their actions are obviously blatant provocation."

He paused.

"I have already arranged for a direct flight back to the Federation in the afternoon. At least we didn’t go home without gaining something; we have learnt about demon hunters and the like."

"Then we shall take a good rest and leave in the afternoon." Celine took up the coffee pot and drank directly from it. Garen wanted to stop her but wasn’t able to in time.

"Would you like some?" Celine asked innocently as she deliberately licked the coffee pot with her tongue.

"Forget it. Go ahead..." Garen gave up on the idea of having another cup of coffee.

"It’s an indirect kiss you know~~~" Celine tempted him.

"Not interested…" Garen stood up and walked to the window and lfet her to her own devices.

"Oh right Garen, The federation started their exam yesterday." Su Lin butted in, seemingly out of nowhere.

"Exam?" Garen was slightly stunned. "That fast…"

"Yeah, and we’ve known each other for nearly two years…" Su Lin nodded his head.

Garen was staring at the intersection street below and didn’t reply.

The Federation exam was equivalent to the college entrance examination which was one of the main examinations for college students who were keen on entering university. His sister, Ying Er was participating in the exam today.

"We should be able to get back in time. Don’t worry about it, I’ve arranged for the fastest airplane we have." Su Lin walked over and patted his shoulder.

Chapter 154: The Journey Back 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen shook his head and smiled wryly. "I can’t believe I’ve forgotten about this…"

Su Lin didn’t say another word. He stood there beside him and watched the intersection traffic below the building together.

The room gradually became quiet, only the sound of Celine blowing at the coffee pot could be heard.

A long while later.

"What do you plan to do once you go back?" Celine asked the two of them from behind. "Su Lin, if you can help me sort out the Poker Incident and help me recover my body, I promise I will help you twofold, no matter what it is."

"Are you serious?" Su Lin swiftly turned around and asked her. He knew exactly how strong Celine was. Although she was not as strong as Garen, she was not that far behind. He estimated that she was as strong as Yoda.

"Of course."

"Alright. I’ll arrange for everything once we get back." Su Lin nodded.

"My injury is very tricky to handle, and I’ll need to borrow your father’s authority." Celine was being serious, which was a rare in itself.

"Don’t worry about it." Su Lin smiled.

Garen knew everything about Su Lin, as both of them were members of the Golden Hoop*. Su Lin was actually the general manager of the Golden Hoop group of the southern region. He even had the final say in the decision of the examination tasks. Garen smiled once he heard him, as Su Lin could probably solve the whole thing by just making use of the Golden Hoop’s resources.

*Refer to Translator's Note

"Speaking of which, what should I do with my examination task…"

He looked at Su Lin. His mind couldn’t escape the issue; his entrance to the Golden Hoop would concern his power and authority, and was the only way for him to not rely on Su Lin in this aspect. It would also have benefits for his dojo, obtain protection for his family members, not to mention a fixed amount of salary annually as well.

"It’s alright. You’ve been a great help to me this time round, so I’ll just accept this incident as the examination task instead." Su Lin replied readily. "You should wear the golden ring at all times for ease of recognition once you have officially joined us."

"No problem." Garen nodded.

Celine didn’t ask any questions, though the two hadn’t seemed to plan to hide it.

The three of them were shooting the breeze inside the room. Su Lin’s perfume was scathingly criticised by the other two, and Garen avoided mentioning the Golden Sword Throne at all, as if he had already forgotten about it.

However, Garen understood that Su Lin had deliberately chose not to mention the Golden Sword Throne as he had already figured out that Garen really needed it.

"The item is in my care. Is it alright if I return it to you a year later?" Garen initiated the topic. He estimated that he needed a year to absorb all the potential from the Golden Sword Throne.

"You decide on that, since you’re the one who fought for it. That thing is no longer important anyway, it was only meant to be a research object for the officials." Su Lin shrugged his shoulder since he didn’t care much about it.

They chatted a bit more, and before they ran out of time, Garen went out to an art shop and bought gifts for his sister, parents and uncle.

Sin Gerro produces a myriad of ores and gems. Garen picked a blue jade gem for each of his parents, as there was a lasting superstition that it had properties that relaxed one’s body. He picked a amethyst corsage for his sister for its minimal design and elegance.

As for his uncle, he went with a model of a wooden ship with two masts. The work towards the model was detailed and of high quality, which set him back twenty-something thousands dollars. After that, he simply bought a bunch of snacks as souvenirs for everyone remaining.

The three of them then gathered back at the hotel in the afternoon and headed straight to the airbase nearby via a shuttle carriage.

It took them only 8 hours to get back, even though it took them close to 2 days when they came rushing to Sin Gerro. They laid over twice and finally arrived at the Huaishan City Airbase in Galantia Province.

Garen got down from the airplane, while Celine and Su Lin continued their journey to their manor in Harmony City, since he still needed to heal Celine and sort out her incident with the Poker Organization.

Garen arranged for himself military transport and went back to the city area.

It was already 10pm when he arrived home.

*******************

The clouds swallowed the moon, leaving behind a pitch black sky. The whole of Huaishan City gradually settled down into peace and quiet.

A black carriage slowed down near the front of a residential area in the bluetree district and came to a stop.

It was marked with a black bird, its wings spread wide. It was the emblem of the flag marking it as a military carriage.

The driver was a young female soldier. She went to the back and knocked on the carriage frame after she had halted the two black horses.

"We have arrived sir."

"Oh. We have?"

Garen carried his baggages of varying sizes and got down from the carriage.

"Thank you very much, Sergeant Anli."

"It’s nothing. I shall pardon myself now."

"Right."

The carriage took a U-turn and rushed off where it came from, and soon disappeared into the darkness of the unlit street. The faint light of the horse carriage was the lone visible thing in the distance.

Garen turned around and walked towards the gate, and saw a drunk, bald security guard sleeping soundly on a chair in the security booth.

He walked along the familiar community area and he could occasionally still spot a few homeless men snoring just beside the walls under the yellow street light. There were also people who were busy commuting to their night shift job.

He walked towards the building into the staircase and started climbing up a floor at a time. Occasional arguments from within apartments and music leaked out of the walls as he climbed. He stood at his house’s front door after reaching the fourth floor.

A nameplate could be seen hanging at the side of the copper red metal door stating: Eisen Lombard - Jody Vania.

Garen rummaged through his person for his house key and realized that it had already dropped at some unknown location during his journey.

Knock Knock Knock.

He had decided to knock on the door instead.

"Coming! Just a minute!" His sister Ying Er’s voice came from inside the house.

Then came the rapid footsteps.

The door was opened after a period of silence.

"Brother!" Ying Er obviously had seen Garen through the door’s peephole as she embraced him the moment she opened the door. She was hanging onto him by the neck. "When did you come back?"

"I came here the moment I got down from the car. Alright, don’t mess around anymore, I’m still holding my luggages." Garen’s big and strong body was the size of two or three Ying Ers. It didn’t matter to him at all that she was freely hanging herself by his neck.

It was just that her body had started developing, and he could feel the tenderness of her still developing, petite breasts as they squeezed against his body.

With Ying Er hanging onto him, Garen took off his flip flops and entered, closing the door behind him4.

"Where’s mum and dad?" Garen asked as he placed the luggages at one corner of the living room.

"Mum and dad got promoted to the management level in the company. The situation is a little bit tense lately and dad says that the rubber industry will be impacted by it. There is a sudden surge in order to and from the military, and both of them are busy dealing with it."

Ying Er was unusually hyperactive and it took her a while to get off Garen.

"Brother, didn’t you enrol in Mantra University? Where do you find the time to come back? I heard that there’s still quite some time before the holidays." Ying Er asked curiously.

"I finished my courses early and I didn’t have anything better to do afterwards. So I decided to apply for a school leave. Don’t worry about it."

"Is university exciting?"

"It’s alright…"

Both of them were sitting on the sofa as they started having a conversation. Ying Er was saddened when Garen asked her about the college entrance examination.

"It’s finished. I flunked my first mathematics paper…" The little estrangement she felt with Garen over a long time apart was gradually washed away. Ying Er frowned when the examination topic was brought up.

"If only I was admitted under the university’s recommendation like you were…"

"Recommendation… Uh…" Garen almost forgot how he was admitted into the university. He was recommended by the university because he had specialised knowledge in identifying antiques. However in actuality, everything was Su Lin’s arrangement and Garen was in the dark.

Ying Er kept the conversation flowing endlessly, as if she was getting more and more cheerful lately. She told Garen everything, big or small, after he left the house.

From Ying Er’s account, Garen had come to find out that there were more guests than the last time he came back. His parents were promoted and had befriended a few big shots of the industry. They even attended the city’s upper class banquet parties in certain occasions.

"How is my master doing?" Garen asked.

"Dojo Master Fei was getting better. Everyday, he is conscious for a short period of time. Mum, dad and I had visited Dojo Master Fei too." Ying Er answered readily. "Oh right brother. Dojo Master said that you should go and visit him once you returned as he had something to tell you."

"Oh?" Garen frowned a little bit. "I will visit him tomorrow then. I went overseas with my friends for a short trip before coming back here, and I’ve gifts for master and you guys."

"A gift?! I like the sound of that!" Ying Er swiftly ran towards the luggages. "Which one is mine which one is mine?"

"Let me get it for you." Garen walked there and handed out an oval shaped box which was wrapped in a black fur.

"This is for my dearest sister Ying Er." Garen smiled as he placed the box into Ying Er’s hand.

"Thank you brother!" Ying Er blushed as she tiptoed and gave her brother a good kiss on the face out of the blue. Garen couldn’t help but to feel stunned as the lady’s tender lips brought upon a faint body fragrance.

"Alright alright stop fooling around."

"You’re not that much older than me. Why are you behaving ahead of your age?" Ying Er wasn’t aware that Garen had become more and more matured as time passed. He wasn’t like his old self, where he would submit himself to her and let her bully him. It was a sudden ,unknowing change.

When Garen treated her like how other elders treated her, she couldn’t help but to feel annoyed.

"I wonder when you became like this." Ying Er pondered.

Garen looked at her acting mischievously and pulled her cheek with an outstretched hand.

"Where is your mind wandering? You should go check out the gift in your room."

"Stop pulling! No one would want me if I became fat!!" Ying Er quickly struggled. "I’ll hold you responsible if no one wants me!" She carried the small box and entered her room after she struggled out of Garen’s grip.

The living room quietened down and he could hear her sister’s faint humming in the bedroom.

Garen sat down on the sofa and closed his eyes, wiping his face with both of his hands.

"Su Lin’s matter regarding the Celestital Circle Gate Black Mark Association’s foreign aggression should be taken care of by now."

"It’s time to take care of the internal issues." A cold gaze radiated from his eyes.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

It is unsure whether the Garen is part of the Golden Hoop as the following few paragraphs suggest that he is not.

Chapter 155: Minor Changes 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The senior sister apprentice rebelled, the elder and second master were missing. The White Cloud Gate broke down because of one person’s rebellious intent. Garen had decided to resolve this issue once and for all, bearing to the fact that there was no more foreign aggression.

However, he had to check out the city’s mess before anything.

He could take it slow, since he had obtained the Golden Sword Throne. This meant that his strength would increase over time, and he could use this time to deal with his internal affairs.

Sitting on the sofa, Garen unconsciously recalled the words Duskdune Shura said at the cliff.

"The undefeated and the unconquerable. No one is a match for him as long as he lives, be it the top of this generation or the next." The words which were spoken by Duskdune Shura kept floating in his mind.

"What I lack…" Garen placed his palms together at his forehead and went into deep thought.

"Brother?"

"Ying Er’s voice came from ahead.

"How do I look?"

Ying Er was in a black dress with an exquisite purple flower brooch. The dress showcased her hourglass body as she spun in circles on one spot.

Garen raised his head up.

"Very beautiful." Garen laughed, "What paper are you having tomorrow?"

"Physics, and I’m very confident about it!" Ying Er smiled proudly.

"You should sleep early since you have to wake up early tomorrow. Have you showered?"

"All done!" Ying Er hummed as she hit her chest with the back of her hand. Although the exquisite purple flower brooch was not eye catching, it had a faint beauty about it. It was a perfect match for her.

"Go ahead and rest early." Garen pinched her cheek.

"Okay~~~" Ying Er went back to her bedroom with a sweet smile on her face.

Garen sat on the sofa alone and waited for his parents to come home, as he pondered on Duskdune Shura’s words in his head.

A short while later, the sound of a car engine came from below. The sound disappeared after a while, followed by the sound of ar doors closing.

After a few minutes, the sound of keys clinking behind the door.

Garen stood up and walked towards the door as his parents came in.

"Dad, mum."

"Garen?!!" Both of them were stunned and surprised.

"When did you come back?" Mother went closer and pinched Garen’s face with both her hands, "I think you’ve got thinner…"

Father Lombard was slightly butthurt as he saw Garen’s arms as thick as a leg and his strong, muscular chest.

"This guy grew at least 10cm! In which part is he supposed to be thin?! His chest and arms are all muscles!"

"Is that so?" Mother Vania became suspicious.

"Let’s come in and talk." Garen closed the door as he took the baggage from his parents hands and placed them in the living room.

"How’s life in university? Are you used to it? Do you need more money to support your lifestyle? And how is your relationship with the lecturers?" Mother immediately bombarded him with questions the moment she entered the house.

Since Garen hadn’t been to the university at all, he had no choice but to describe his university life on Earth. He couldn’t tell it in detail however as he did not want to be seen through.

His parents finally let him go after he fed them a bunch of nonsense.

Garen took the opportunity and asked about his master’s condition.

"Dojo Master Fei…" Father Lombard frowned. "Things don’t look good according to all of the experts from Yang Liu."

"What’s happened?" Garen was stunned as even the experts Federation’s Yang Liu City couldn’t do anything to improve the situation.

"You’ll understand when you see him tomorrow." Lombard shook his head. "It’s not something you can imagine if you don’t see it with your own eyes. Sigh… Dojo Master Fei was very wise… I hadn't expected this at all. We hadn’t known at all at first, but we now know that the dojo master of the white cloud is considered a very strong person in this city."

"Alright let’s not talk about this any further. Let our son visit Dojo Master Fei tomorrow since he gave his all to cultivate our son." Mother Vania butted in. "Oh right Garen. Are you and Mr. Bouvini’s daughter considered close friends? You should thank her father on behalf of us for helping your father out. If her father hadn’t lent a helping hand, your mother and I would not be promoted; it’s all thanks to him."

"Mikaela? Bouvini?" Garen understood. "Okay, I do know Bouvini. I got to know him before Master was in trouble. I’ll visit them after visiting master. Don’t worry about it."

"Alright. Speaking of which, we’ve met Mikaela before as well. Although she is not too beautiful, she is quite elegant. If you’re interested…." Mother Vania’s eyes were beaming with light as she talked about it.

"Eh, forget about it." Father butted in. "Mikaela is only ten years old. Isn’t it a little bit too soon…"

"Who says it’s too soon! It would be over if they engage earlier. What are you worried about? Even Mr. Bouvini pushed his intention to us. We’re just commoners, and there’s nothing that they can gain from us. Furthermore, there are a lot of twelve year olds getting married as well and they can go to the church in a year or two!"

Garen started breaking into cold sweat as he listened. Twelve years old! Getting married at this age was definitely too young even if it’s the tradition of this era. Garen couldn’t believe what his mum just said.

"Let’s be patient. I have to visit Mr. Bouvini in a few days, and there would be complications in giving birth since their daughter is too young."

Vania put off the idea of engagement after some persuasion from both father and son.

Being engaged to a 10 year old girl…

Garen was covered in goosebumps as he thought of it, since he was not a pedophile. In addition, the first person that appeared in his mind was Celine. Although both of them have the body of a young girl, Celine would be a better choice since she had a great body when she was grown up.

After a casual conversation with his parents, he passed them the gifts and went to take a shower. After wiping his body, he proceeded to change into his own clothes that he had brought.

As his body grew bigger in a short time span, all his clothes in the cupboard were too small for him. Fortunately, he thought of this beforehand and bought a few clothes while he was shopping for gifts.

He went into the room, turned off the light and laid on the bed.

The watch bell and the sound of a train departing could be faintly heard in the distance outside.

It was the new train tracks nearby.

Garen slowly closed his eyes and went into deep sleep.

He then woke up from his dream in the middle of the night.

Garen blinked a few times as he got up. He looked outside the window and saw pure darkness. It was still midnight.

He took off his blankets and sat by the bed wiping his face. He was restless, Duskdune Shura’s words still pervasively invading his mind..

He instinctively felt that Duskdune Shura did not say those words baselessly.

He wouldn’t have pursued the heavily injured Duskdune Shura if he had been completely unharmed.

"White Bird Holy Fist…" Garen muttered. He went back to bed after he took a deep breath, while the energy of Golden Sword Throne inside his pajamas kept flowing into his mind.

The root of his talent was located on his head, a special ability that only a small handful amount of people have. According to his own estimation, it would be rare to find a single digit amount of people among the billions on Earth who had similar abilities.

According to his speculation, this special ability was formed based on his spiritual structure, body structure, the arrangement of the nerves etc. No one would have the same special abilities, just like how there wouldn’t be two exact copies of a single leaf in nature. There would be a great difference for every small small deviation.

He still was not sure whether if it’s this special ability that allowed him to maintain this spiritual bridging, or if it was the bridging that caused him to obtain his special abilities.

"These questions are just dogs chasing their tails.." Garen thought as he focused his vision on his own attribution and skill panes.

‘’Strength 2.66. Agility 1.82. Vitality 2.45. Intelligence 1.53. Potential 1256%.

Secret Martial Art.----

Mammoth Variation: Explosive (Maximum Level), Epidermal Hardening Grade One (Iron Body), Blood Qi Stabilization Grade One (Boulder Martial Art).

Red jade Palm: Learned (Mastered Grade One), Burning Strengthen Grade One (Dark Crimson Technique), Vitality Enhancement Grade One (Dark Crimson Technique)’

"I have so many points already…" Garen was stunned as he realized going overseas was a worthwhile trip. The Golden Sword Throne had lived up to its name and it was worth the risk entering the ancient ruins.

He carefully felt for the rate of the potential flow from the Golden Sword Throne and even though it was much weaker than last time, he would still gain something every week which was much better than nothing compared to last time.

"12 points…" Garen had never obtained so many points at one go.

"Should I increase my attribution or max out my Secret Martial Art first?" He was in a dilemma.

With this many points, he could either push one of his Secret Martial Art to the limit, or pour everything into the attribution pane. Although it was limited to the user’s body limit, it should be enough to increase his attribution to an appalling height.

He remembered that he would kept spending all the points on attribution when he was still practising the Mammoth Secret Martial Art. He had at least spent 12 points on attribution and not only did it give him major special effects for his secret martial art, it also gave him a complete combat skills to face every complicated situation.

If he poured all his points into attribution and added nothing in his secret martial art*, it was estimated that it was highly likely that any normal martial artist with a powerful weapon could beat him down.

*Author probably reversed attribution and secret martial art.

"It’s unfortunate that there are pros and cons in increasing the level or martial arts… If only it could break the limits of the user’s body. I should just max out my attribution first."

Garen first focused his vision onto strength.

Unfortunately it had already reached its limit, as it wouldn’t budge. He then moved on to agility.

One point of attribution was converted into 0.3 and added onto it. Two points added. Three points added…

Agility increased steadily and stopped at 2.72. It had reached its limit.

Next up is Vitality.

It increased from 2.45 to 2.65, which was less than one attribution point. Garen had no choice but to add the remaining 0.1 point into intelligence.

He continued increasing his intelligence attribute.

It increased steadily from 1.63 to 1.93, 2.23 and finally hovered 2.53.

Just like that, all of his attribution had reached his body’s limit. He had 5 points left as he used up 7 points to max out his attribution.

The attribution pane had became larger as well as if it had been upgraded.

‘Strength 2.66, Agility 2.72, Vitality 2.65, Intelligence 2.53, Potential 556%.

Chapter 156: Minor Changes 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was too tired to continue racking his brain, and due to the huge increment to his attribution, especially agility and intelligence, he felt like his whole body was burning up, and he felt a pain which could be described similar to being penetrated by countless of needles in his muscle as they contracted. His vision was clouded as his felt his brain was on fire as well.

He was drowsy as if he was inside the hottest sauna in the world. The weird thing was that he was not sweating at all. His muscles were stronger than ever, and there was no major change in his body figure either. However, cackling noises came out from his body as his body figure started to become more and more symmetrical and streamlined.

Garen woke up after some time had passed.

Thy sky outside had already turned into a bright gray.

He laid on the bed with his eyes open and noticed his long dark purple hair had been untied, spreading over the pillow like black lines of silk, bright and flowy. The whole room was faintly covered in a funny smell.

Garen slowly got up and gently moved his body. A string of snapping from all over his joints could be heard as he shifted.

He opened the window to let in some fresh, cold air from outside after he got up from his bed.

His mind was as clear as if he had just chewed on a mint, and all his thoughts were as fast as the flash from an electric spark, having no delay at all.

"All the attributions are at its limit… and I’m left with 5 points. Now I need to figure out how to go beyond the limit." Garen’s mind was never this clear before.

"Going beyond the limits has always been the goal of every fighter. The White Bird Holy Fist, Palosa of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate is the strongest in this aspect. Perhaps I can learn something from him. I will visit the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate once I’ve dealt with my internal affairs."

Determined, he immediately walked towards his study desk and absentmindedly picked out a science textbook. He started experimenting the changes of his body, especially in the intelligence aspect.

After half an hour, he roughly had a clear idea of the effects of his maximised intelligence.

"Logical thinking is much clearer, memory capacity has increased dramatically, reasoning and analysis have become much stronger as well. The main effect of the intelligence attribute has on the body is the short-term memory. Usually, a normal person can only memorise five to seven lines of sentences in a short amount of time and this is without the effects of any enhancement in memorization. However, I currently…"

Garen opened a random page and scanned through its content. He then closed his eyes and he could clearly see the whole content that was in that page.

"10 lines… It’s a very strong effect! Furthermore, the contents from the short term memory can be converted into long term memory in an instant due to the fast reasoning speed. I can now remember and understand everything even if I skip the typical learning conditions." One page of information was quickly understood and stored into him as long term memory.

"There’s also the ability of calculation..."

Garen noticed that he could easily solve complicated mathematical questions with ease. Answers would simply float in his head as he immediately understood the question when he saw it.

He picked out a simple mathematical equation which contained four fundamental operations, with the exception of the equation being undetermined or divided by zero. His brain would immediately calculate the question as he glanced at it and he was able to calculate the last five digits of the answer every second. He managed to do so purely by brute force mental calculation, without any other instruments or techniques.

This ability could be improved tenfold if he did make use of some simple mathematical techniques.

"Intelligence mainly improves the reasoning, memory and calculation of the user. As for creativity… nothing much has changed." Garen understood that creativity was based on the amount of content in the memory and the frequency of the sparks that could be produced from as information colliding into each other.

"In short, I have a photographic memory and react faster than normal people. I can easily grasp the important points of a question and solve it with a strong logical reasoning. This is the effect of increasing the Intelligence." Garen concluded.

"Next up is Agility."

He moved his body for a while and pulled out a punch out of nowhere.

Bam!

A low pitched noise was cracked from the compressed air. His right knuckle was moving in and out swiftly like a snake.

"What amazing speed! This far surpasses Duskdune Shura’s attack speed! It’s even slightly faster than Andrela’s normal attack speed." Garen compared to his past opponent, Andrela, who was the fastest among them.

Andrela’s blink gave him a lasting impression. None of the grandmasters of combat were even close to his attack speed, including even Duskdune Shura or Flamingo. Although Andrela was not stronger than these two, he was the fastest in speed.

"Maybe if I were to compare it with Blink, I am still slightly behind. It must be the kind of secret art that heavily damages the opponent in a short amount of time."

Garen felt his body was more agile as he raised his hands and feet. He was sure that his body could react faster compared to last time. It was obvious that Agility had greatly increased his body’s speed.

Huff…

He gently exhaled.

"I am now…. Much stronger!"

He was at least twice as strong as his former self! He wasn’t physically stronger, but stronger in terms of speed and intelligence; this would allow him to make the best decision and react in the shortest amount of time.

"I have the confidence to go against Duskdune Shura even when he is in his prime now!" Garen assessed his current state and concluded that he was better than ever.

As he wore the dark red shirt and jeans that he had brought back, Garen suddenly realized a pendant was hanging by his neck.

It was a pendant shaped like an open book and it was as warm as the human body.

"The old man’s pendant…" He frowned as he walked towards the mirror and stood in front of it.

His dark purple hair which was at shoulder length was like lion’s mane when it was messy. His dark red eyes were sharp as a knife, exuding a sense of aggression. His simple facial features had become charming.

His body was as strong as ever, but was more symmetrical now. His dark red shirt was tighten by his muscle profile. Garen adjusted his gaze to give more gentleness and less aggression.

He tied his hair up into a pony tail with a black rubber band that he found. He immediately looked much less aggressive with these small touches.

After getting used to his body in the room post-attribution-increase, Garen soon heard footsteps coming from the living room.

As he opened the door, he saw his sister Ying Er busy wiping her face with a bread between her lips, as she chewed and tied her shoes by the doorstep.

"I’ll send you." Garen quickly washed his face and brushed his teeth in the washroom.

"It’s okay. I have to go now and the school bus is here to fetch me." Ying Er jabbered as she chewed her bread.

"It’s alright. I will go with you." Garen spitted the foam out of his mouth and quickly wiped his mouth clean as he walked towards the doorsteps. On his way he picked up the things that he brought back. "I have to go out as well. I’ll send you there."

"Alright then. It’s so rare for you to be so proactive." A hint of joy flashed in Ying Er’s eyes as she looked at her recently grown up brother Garen in fascination.

Garen was the brother that had belonged to her alone before. However, the current Garen was the brother that was no longer hers anymore, but he became better and more reliable than before. He was concerned about Garen regarding his sudden change but she eventually accepted it.

Two of them greeted their parents who just came out of their bedroom and went downstairs as they locked the door.

The other occupants downstairs were not awake yet as it was still early.

Ying Er walked at the front while Garen followed behind as both of them quickly walked down the stairs.

"There should be a lot of parents in the school bus. There will be some of my friends as well…" Ying Er couldn’t help herself but glanced at Garen. She looked like she wanted to continue speaking but had decided otherwise.

"I’m ok with that. What are you worried about?" Garren replied helplessly. "Let’s walk faster. You’ll be in trouble if you miss the school bus."

"Right, right." Ying er sped up as well.

Both of them walked out of the residential area coming out from the staircase, where a black bus waiting at the entrance. The words Shengying Nobles Academy were written on the side of the vehicle.

The girls on the bus were wearing the same outfit as his sister; a white, short sleeved shirt combined with a super short skirt and black pantyhose. On the other hand, the boys were wearing white shirts and black jeans paired with leather boots. The attire was the same as what Garen wore when he woke up in this world.

It was the same view when he first got up the school bus.

Garen covered his sister as they got up the bus. There was another guy in the Shengying Nobles Academy attire who got up the bus in this district area as well.

There were about at ten students in the bus. Their respective parents, or cousins were accompanying them.

"Ying Er! Here!" A female voice came from the back seat. It was a girl with a red ponytail hair with a middle age woman beside her. The young lady had her bag placed on the seat beside her.

"Xiao Ling!" Ying Er quickly went to the back of the car as she pulled Garen along.

""Good day President Ying Er." "Good Morning President Ying Er." "President."

Almost half of the students knew Ying Er as they stood up and greeted her with respect. Everyone looked curious as they saw Garen standing behind her.

"President?" Garen looked at his sister skeptically. This was when he realized his sister was not a timid and lovable little woman that she had portrayed in the house. She had a cool and confident aura around her with a soft and gentle smile.

With just a simple change, she looked sharper and faintly dominant.

He had to reassess his sister’s social standing.

Her waist length dark purple hair was silky smooth and there was no split ends at all. The freckles on her oval face had long disappeared, leaving behind white, tender skin and a sharp chin. Her dark red, crystal gaze was calm and confident, but cold at the same time.

She gradually evolved into an hourglass body figure, as well as a pair of long and slender legs. Although she was much shorter than he was, she was considered tall among people her age.

Ying Er stood out inside the bus.

Ying Er blushed as she noticed her brother’s gaze and felt shy in front of her peers. It was a rare scene.

"I became the President of the Bowmanship Club two years ago." Ying Er explained softly.

"That’s very unexpected." Garen shook his head. Judging from the student’s respect and admiration, it seemed like Ying Er had did well for the past two years.

The duo walked to the back of the bus and Ying Er sat beside Xiao Ling whereas Garen sat on an empty seat in front of her. He politely nodded at Xiao Ling’s mother as a greeting.

Conversations regarding his identity could faintly be heard among the students in the car.

As Garen looked out the window, he realized that Huaishan City had slightly changed within the past two years. A few new buildings had been built, and the familiar jewelry shop he always saw had now become a pie shop.

After a while, the bus stopped and four students came up with their parents.

One of them, a handsome boy with gold hair, scanned the bus with his eyes and stopped at Ying Er.

"President Ying Er!" He quickly walked towards her as he grinned. One of the female students naturally got up and gave up her seat to him.

"Nesari." Ying Er frowned slightly as she calmly smiled. "Are you not commuting via your personal car again?"

"The car is still being fixed." The golden haired boy sat beside her with admiration written all over his face.

Chapter 157: Traitor 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Your friend?" Having understood the boy’s intention toward Ying Er, Garen turned to her and asked.

"Yeah, he’s a classmate." Ying Er smiled at Garen apologetically, not wanting him to misunderstand.

Nesari did, however. He shot Garen a look steeping in jealousy. "And this is?"

Garen glanced at him. "So I heard you’re Ying Er’s friend? I don’t think friends of opposite sex should sit too close to each other, don’t you think so?" He subtly switched his gaze into a darker undertone, slowly piling a veil of intimidation onto the boy.

Nesari shuddered uncontrollably. His face paled abruptly and moved beyond paleness into shades of emerald. Struggling to speak, he find himself making creaky sounds, but no words came out, causing him to go into panic mode as his tears and snot dripped wildly. It was embarrassing to say the least.

"What have you don-" Nesari’s middle-aged bodyguard scowled and stood up, trying to block Nesari from Garen’s direct line-of-sight and to stand off against Garen.

"Yes, what are you trying to say?" Garen interrupted him.

The bodyguard couldn’t finish his sentence, as his heart jumped and he started sweating like a sinner in church. He felt goosebumps creep down his spine and torso. It felt as if he’s wobbling on the edge of a cliff, the fall happening at any second. His senses of danger and crisis seemed almost real.

"We… we’re sorry!" The bodyguard forced the words out and pulled Nesari out of his seat. They escaped to the front of the bus, not even attempting to look back.

Ying Er and another girl Xiao Ling stared at Garen curiously.

Garen shrugged.

"That kid decided to turn over a new leaf after our lovely talk."

"As if! Don’t bully people just because you know a little martial arts." Ying Er guessed the truth.

"Doesn’t matter, if the boys who want to be with you can’t get past me, how can I trust them to take care of you?" Garen smiled gently.

Ying Er blushed into a sakura pink and lowered her face.

Xiao Ling beside her curiously eyeballed them both one after the other.

All the other students in the bus stared at Garen in a gossipy manner, guessing the relationship between him and Ying Er. Soon, his identity as Ying Er’s brother surfaced. More and more student got on the bus on the way to school, and this incident spread like wildfire.

The strong-headed and cool Ying Er, as the president of the Bowmanship Club, was very eye catching, the difficulty of capturing her heart is unusually high. Furthermore, it was rumored that she has an obsessive admiration for her brother. Now that her brother finally appeared, people finally realized Ying Er’s strong-headedness is like a delicate dandelion when compared to Garen. When both of them sat together, it’s as if one is a boulder, the other is a flower.

Ying Er’s brother sat on his seat casually, but he gave out an air of a dangerous beast ready to attack. His imposing frame might as well be a blind, shielding Ying Er and everyone behind her.

Every time someone glanced at the back, his commanding figure would be the first one they gazed at before darting away in fear that he notices.

Xiao Ling leaned against Ying Er, she felt the suppression as much as the others do.

"Oh no oh no… Ying Er, your older brother looks too fierce, none of the guys who came in after us dared to even wave at the people in the back seats…"

"Really?" Ying Er looked confused, "My older brother is very mellow." She didn’t even noticed anything wrong, she only felt that everyone in the car were behaving really strangely.

Accompanied by the quirky atmosphere, the bus finally arrived at the examination hall, it was the school area of a vocational school.

After everyone alighted the bus at the examination hall, Garen waited outside the cordon as he watched his sister enter the hall. It was only after that he turned around and walked to the White Cloud Dojo.

Compared to Harmony City, Huaishan City is too small. Before half an hour was up, Garen already arrived at the entrance of White Cloud Dojo.

The clock tower at the side is still standing strong, the archway underneath it still receives countless pedestrians everyday.

The bakery opposite of the dojo is still there as well, with its bald owner crouching and writing the menu for the day on signboard.

At the entrance of the dojo, a pupil with yellow shirt was sweeping the ground before noticing Garen.

"Excuse me, who is it that you are looking for?" The male pupil looked about 15 or 16 years of age and was still quite new, he didn’t recognize Garen.

"First senior brother! First Senior Brother Garen!" A voice exclaimed behind Garen, stunning the pupil sweeping the ground.

The pupil abruptly snapped out of his trance and greeted Garen.

"Simon, it’s been a while." Garen turned around and saw a guy stepping out of a red car.

Simon kept a buzz cut and looked fit, it seemed he recovered quite well, one wouldn’t be able to tell which arm he even fractured.

Meeting Garen again, Simon was ecstatic, he hastily got in front and Garen and stood still.

"Welcome back!" He eagerly bowed at Garen.

"Where’s Corinne*?"

"She’s still at the hospital, we are taking turns to take care of Master." Simon scratched the back of his head. "In case Black Mark Association decided to harm him."

"Good job," Garen patted him on his back, "I’ll take over the situation now that I’m back.

"Yessir!" Simon looked like he had been relieved of a huge burden. Garen’s return gave him a huge boost of confidence. As of now, the whole of White Cloud Gate is supported by Garen’s fame alone, otherwise any sect would be able to challenge and kick the White Cloud Gate to the ground.

　　

In Garen’s absence, Simon and Corinne handled all the general affairs of White Cloud Gate, although the stress has constantly made them feel like they couldn’t breathe. If it wasn’t for the growing fame of their Senior Garen who even got invited as Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate‘s Sky Warrior, White Cloud Gate probably wouldn’t been able to last this long.

Even then, a lot of the peripheral forces of White Cloud Gate had broken away, preferring to go under under sects.

After all, having a strong fighting ability doesn’t equate to having strong managerial skills and resourcefulness. Garen is a young man who’s barely even 20 years old, no one was confident about his ability to manage the business. Some former business partners of White Cloud Gate thought of that before they decided to secede.

In short, White Cloud Gate was much weaker than what it used to be, but because of that, it’s also more refined and simpler, having been supported solely by Garen’s fame.

"Do you wanna talk in the dojo?" Simon produced the key to the dojo from his pocket.

"No need, let’s go to the hospital in your car. I wanna check on Master." Garen declined the offer.

"Okay."

They turned around and went in the red car.

Simon started the car, still rambling on about the current events from when Garen left.

"...and so I wanted to get even with Bouvini, but Corinne said he turned over to the light side, everyone makes mistakes after all. And about the thing with the governor, they were doing this civility spot check, the dojo’s business was affected as well. If it weren’t for Third Senior Brother Joshua’s contact through his father, the dojo would probably still be under seizure…"

Simon’s mouth was like a loose tap, spilling the news and gossips without stopping.

Garen, on the other hand, didn’t even need to talk. He only needed to respond once every so often so Simon to spill everything.

The two managed to recap almost everything recent during the drive.

"Oh right, the people from Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate came looking for you. I heard it’s about the division of jurisdiction areas."

"Jurisdiction areas?" Garen furrowed his brow, "Let’s talk about this another time."

From the side windows, a huge white building stood in the middle of a row of houses. A signboard, The Anning Mann Hospital.

　

The two mixed in with the crowd entering through the hospital gate. Simon lead Garen to the second floor with relative ease into a pale blue corridor with a peaceful and sterile atmosphere. Walking to the other end, Simon knocked softly on the door on the right and entered.

"How are you back here? Aren’t you supposed to open the dojo for the day?" A girl in the room stood up, surprised.

The girl is tall and had a sunkissed tan, she’s not gorgeous, but she’s surrounded by a heroic air. She had a luscious figure, with a well-endowed chest that bounces with her movements. She gave off an almost indescribable allure.

Her long black hair was tied into a ponytail, hanging behind her. Most obviously, a thin red scar lashed across Corinne’s right cheek, adding to her ferocity.

"Corinne, First Senior Brother is here!" Simon chuckled and stepped aside, letting Garen in.

"It’s been a long time." Garen entered the room and looked at Corinne by the bedside.

Corinne’s eyes reddened. She stood there stunned, and immediately covered her mouth, sobbing uncontrollably.

"You’ve done a great job…"

Garen understood the amount of stress the two had to endure since his absence. He approached Corinne and ruffled her hair, feeling slightly apologetic.

"Master… Master is…" Corinne was so upset, she couldn’t talk.

Garen saw the condition Fei Baiyun was in since he entered the room.

Fei Baiyun’s whole body was covered with a white blanket with only his head poking out, but even from his head Garen could tell he wasn’t doing well.

His body that used to be healthy is now skinny and bony, and looked like a skeleton wrapped under a layer of skin who’s sleeping on the bed.

Hearing the noise in the room, Fei Baiyun struggled to open his eyes. Seeing Garen at the side, a sign of excitement flashed in his eyes.

"Garen… you’re… back…"

"Master," Garen crouched at the side of the bed. He noticed Fei Baiyun’s ailing condition and felt slightly downcast. "I’m back."

"Good…" Fei Baiyun wrestled with the words, "You’ve grown… stronger…" He raised his scrawny arm toward Garen’s face.

Garen grabbed his arm promptly.

"Master was holding out for your return all this while. Now that you’re back to tie up the loose ends, he’ll be glad." Corinne stood beside Simon, her eyes still red from crying.

"If there’s… a chance, go to the East… That’s where White Cloud Gate’s... root lies…" Fei Baiyun uttered slowly and with a lot of pauses.

"Yes, Master." Garen nodded, his hands still clutching Fei Baiyun’s. "Rest, Master, don’t speak too much."

"I know my own condition… I don’t have much longer." Fei Baiyun’s speech started to become smoother, as if he’s experiencing a terminal lucidity*. "White Cloud Gate is now under your care. The Elders are gone, the two other… disciples I had were not… dependable. I didn’t think it would come down to my youngest disciple…"

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Used to be known as Collin. I decided to change the name to fit the character’s gender. Will be known as Corinne hereafter and future chapters.

2. Terminal lucidity. A moment of mental clarity shortly before death.

Chapter 158: Traitor 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What are you trying to say?" Garen didn’t show any sorrow in his eyes. Life and death, old age and sickness are normal for human being. He had already experienced it once in his past life, and after experiencing Old Man Gregor’s death, he only felt calmness this time.

Suddenly, Fei Baiyun grabbed his hand and started to tremble violently, as if he was hit by a bout of hysterics. Even the bed started to shake.

Trembling, he stuffed a Blackwood Ring into Garen’s palm.

"Master!"

"Doctor! Doctor!"

Worried, Corinne and Simon rushed outside to get a doctor.

　　

Fei Baiyun did not care much for his health, his gaze toward Garen was as sharp as a knife and as bright as the sun, and his hand gripped Garen’s with the strength of an iron plier.

"Rosetta… Find her… Kill her!"

Fei Baiyun forced out the sentence before he tremored fiercely and jerked backward. Eyes rolled back, he fell onto the bed. Dead.

Garen gently closed his eyelids with his palm and stood up.

"Don’t worry."

He looked at Master Fei Baiyun, who no longer have a pulse, feeling a dark calmness wash over him.

"I will avenge you."

When Corinne and Simon returned with a doctor, Fei Baiyun had completely flatlined with no possibility of resuscitation.

Corinne and Simon went silent, grieving. In the period when they took care of Fei Baiyun, it was hard, but whenever he’s conscious, he would give them nuggets of guidance which helped a lot.

"Any news about Rosetta recently?" Garen asked suddenly.

"First senior brother’s friend had news of First Senior Sister Rosetta.* She was spotted at the Swan Lake in Lake Shore West City." Corinne answered with her eyes reddened by grief.

"Let’s go, it’s time for White Cloud Gate to clear out the bad seeds."

Garen marched out of the hospital room, his face projecting a dense killing intent.

Simon and Corinne glanced at each other, and followed closely.

　　****************

The burial for the Founder of White Cloud Gate, Fei Baiyun, was held in modesty. There were only a few older visitors, including some master pugilists of yesteryear with better relationship with Fei Baiyun. The rest were comprised of Garen’s associates, Su Lin’s people, representatives of The Golden Hoop, Seven Moon Group, Circling Dance Gate and others.

At the burial ground, the sky gloomed, and the rain poured heavily.

The coffin was transported to Huaishan City Cemetery.

Garen was dressed in a black suit, he held an umbrella above him, watching the burial ceremony in silence.

The invited nuns from the monastery sang their requiem resoundingly while two strong men lowered the coffin slowly into the tomb. A bunch of white lilies were placed on top.

Rain clattered on the black umbrella.

Garen held a taut expression on his face, the free hand was inside his pocket, softly caressing the Blackwood Ring.

Corinne and Simon stood behind him, holding an umbrella each.

Third Senior Joshua was there as well. He looked remorseful. It was not clear when he arrived, but he stood there, wet, without the intention to get an umbrella. He looked at the coffin quietly.

"Third senior brother." Garen looked at Joshua.

Joshua nodded, took a step forward, took the shovel that was handed to him, and walked to the side of the tomb in the rain.

Shrrt!

He shoveled some dirt and slowly drizzled it onto the coffin.

Garen noticed Third Senior Brother Joshua’s left arm was slightly crooked, as if he was hurt. He also knew about the damage Joshua suffered in his absence, when he protected the White Cloud Gate, against the wishes of his family, and was surprised by a sneak attack during a fight with the Black Mark Association. It was still healing.

After the first shovel of dirt, the people around the tomb started filling up the hole shovel by shovel.

White Cloud Gate’s members watched in the rain, utterly silent. Farther away, there were the plump Bouvini and his gang, the branch manager, the main hall’s pupils, and some newly signed up disciples of Simon and Corinne.

Even farther away were the other guests who came for the funeral.

Garen watched as the dirt rained on the coffin, his heart calmer by the second.

"The airplane you wanted is ready," The representative from the Golden Hoop whispered behind Garen, "This is a public resource. On a separate note, your authority allows you to mobilize up to fifty men from any nearby army camps, as well as firepower below Grade C."

He passed an identity document to Garen.

"This is yours, please take care of it. Use public resources reasonably to strengthen your influence. Your strength will influence the strength of the Golden Loop."

The old man with a hooked nose bowed slightly to Garen before stepping aside. He placed a bouquet of white roses in front of the tomb, gave it a salute and left.

The other funeral guests would offer a word of comfort to Garen without exception.

Garen peeked at the identity document, it was a document secured with a piece of crystal. In the middle of the black hard cover, there was the national miniature bird emblem engraved.

Flipping open the cover, the inner pages were padded with black felt.

The page on the left was the national emblem and the logo of the National Security Division.

The page on the right was his half body shot, as well as a serial number: No. 9.

Keeping the identification hidden, Garen stood on the side, observing each guest as they pay their respects.

I wasn’t long before Su Lin’s people was up next.

She was a young and beautiful, yet cool-looking woman. She dressed like an office lady*, her long blonde hair flowing past her shoulders, her body curvy where it needs to be.

She approached Garen and shook his hand.

"The news you asked for. Rosetta is still at the Swan Lake."

"Thank you." Garen murmured.

"You’re welcome."

　　*********************

Lake Shore West City, several hundred kilometers from Huaishan City, Swan Lake.

The sun was setting, painting a dark golden shine on the irregularly-shaped, jade-colored lake.

Scattered around and in the lake were bunches of golden reeds and weeds, a few white swans lazed around on the surface of the lake.

At the bank by the shore, a man and a woman in police uniform squatted awkwardly, drinking the lake water with their palms. Their faces were muddy, their faces unrecognisable.

In the woods not far behind the two stood two other people in black cloaks. At the back of the cloaks, a white arc arching upwards were sewed in.

"How are we dividing for this mission?" One of the black cloaks was a woman.

"We get one half each. After that we’ll take another mission, I should be able to get what I wanted." The other cloaked figure is a man. "Of course, if you become my woman, I can give you half of what I own."

"This is the Lake Shore West City, your old nest. If anyone from the Crimson Sand Sword found out, you’ll run home crying." The woman teased, unamused.

"They won’t be able to catch me anyway. Better take care of your own problems. White Cloud Gate is not far from here. Sky Warrior Garen, tsk tsk, that’s an incredible title." The man retorted, unwilling to lose. "Maybe then you’ll even accept my offer, one night for every help."

"Hmph." The woman did not say anything more, "The stuff is on their hands?"

"Maybe they’re going to get it somewhere."

"Now if the Immortal Palace Alliance look the other way, every other people has been dealt with, no one would help them stop us Behemoth Gate." The woman spoke in a low voice. "Following them would lead straight to the thing."

"Anyone who tries to stop us, we’ll kill them." The man said unaffectedly.

Before he finished his sentence, the two police seemed to have drank enough. They stood up and took off speedily, anyone would know they’re trained in martial arts.

The two black cloaked figure immediately chased after them.

　　**********************

After Garen meted out some issues with White Cloud Gate, his return forced some of the less stable forces into hiding, the stress Corinne and Simon faced decreased dramatically.

He explained to his family about taking over the White Cloud Gate now that he is officially the new Master of White Cloud Gate. His family didn’t feel much of a difference, but they were curious how the youngest Garen could take over the dojo. They got the news later and didn’t show up at the funeral.

No matter what happened, Garen seemed less and less familiar to them. From not realizing the importance of White Cloud Gate, they slowly resorted to a stunned silence after learning about the guests at the funeral.

White Cloud Gate, more specifically Garen’s influence is far too much for them to handle, it surpasses the definition of a mere dojo caretaker.

Suddenly, they realized, like Garen’s uncle, couldn’t see through Garen at all.

But no matter what, after being exposed in the funeral, Garen’s name spread throughout the Huaishan City, becoming a fad of its own. Anyone who knows anything about the modest funeral talked about how it’s simple, but full of surprises.

Garen who was in the lead became famous overnight, even the Governor noticed and paid attention on this event, sending someone to deliver a wreath and a eulogy.

Following the funeral, anyone who paid attention would have known that Garen’s social network even extended beyond Huaishan City, as even influential organizations from nearby cities sent representatives to attend the funeral.

His network radially covered over half of the Galantia Province, even the powerful son of the Seven Moon Group, Rampas, came to grieve Fei Baiyun’s death after.

Because of the Seven Moon Group’s misdecision after Garen and Andrela’s battle, the board of directors unanimously voted to release the former chairman, Great Elder, from his duties, and elected Second Elder, Rampas’ father to succeed him. The Seven Moon Group’s reputation dropped significantly in the martial arts community. Fortunately, their businesses had a strong foundation and were not affected considerably.

The election of Rampas’ father elevated Rampas’ status, and as Rampas was already siding with White Cloud Gate, his naturally has to appear in person to grieve.

However, to the people who don’t know about the martial arts community, his appearance was more than shocking.

At this turn of event, Ying Er’s admiration to her brother only grew. Shengying Nobles Academy even listed Garen on their Wall of Fame, and even wanted to invite him to give a speech. However, this all happened during Garen’s flight to Lake Shore West City on the military plane.

Along with him, Garen brought Corinne, Simon, as well as Third Senior Brother Joshua. Aside from the core disciples whom Garen personally picked, two sharpshooters were arranged to take care of Joshua’s safety, one of whom reminded Garen of Yoda.

Who’s Yoda? He was the best gunman of the generation!

It just happened that he was planning to talk to these two about the level classification of marksmanship in the plane.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. Might be a typo, but the original text said 大师兄的朋友, which translates to first senior brother’s friend. But previous chapter had Simon call Garen first senior brother. Translator is as confused as you readers.

2. Office Lady, shorthanded “OL” in the original text. It supposedly refer to any business women who display one or more of the following attributes: intelligent, fashionable, professional, elegant, and has a high income. On the other hand, there appears to be some sort of OL fetish that some Chinese readers are into.

Chapter 159: Prodigy 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The buzzing of the aircraft echoed unceasingly in the cabin. On the side, a constant tapping signified the constant working of the telegram machine.

Garen sat on the starboard-side of the aircraft, wearing a golden earring on his left ear. It was snapped onto his earlobe, as the pins on it were not able to pierce his skin.

He touched the earring, it was engraved with a number 9 as an indication of his status in the Golden Loop. Whenever he accesses Golden Loop’s resources, he’d need to show the symbol before his subordinates can identify and follow his orders.

The aircraft wasn’t large, it’s only enough for a dozen people to fly in.

The pilots were two Golden Loop members in black, they also wore the golden earrings, but the numbers engraved on them were three digits.

Third Senior Brother Joshua sat beside Garen, both his bodyguards sandwiching him from his front and back, protecting him.

The other people from White Cloud Gate like Simon, Corinne and other core members sat at the back. Between the core members, two figures were extra noticeable.

A lady with a girly youthful appearance, Cynthia, wore a simple T-shirt and jeans. She let her hair down to her shoulder length and sat by the window, humming. Sitting beside her was Jack.

Both of them were beaten by Garen in Huaishan City when they were still Manuyllton’s lead captain.

When Garen was absent from the city, even though they didn’t join the dojo, they regularly interflowed with Simon and Corinne, even some pivotal information were provided by them.

Bringing them on this trip was to enlist their help to protect the newly formed core disciples of White Cloud Gate who had never seen firearms.

"Third senior brother, do you know anything about Gun Arts?" Garen turned toward Joshua. He had always been curious about Yoda’s discipline.

"Gun Arts?" Joshua frowned, "The Will Brothers my mum hired for me were experts in Gun Arts, it’ll be better if you ask them, I don’t know much about Gun Arts."

He paused, "Are you saying that traitor Rosetta may use Gun Arts against us?" His face darkened.

Garen looked at Joshua and knew, all his focus was set on seeking revenge from Rosetta, the First-senior-sister-turned-traitor. Everything he came across, he would associate it with vengeance, so Garen stopped asking. He turned to the sharpshooter who reminded him of Yoda.

The sharpshooter is a bald man with a deep tan complexion, he wore a pair of silver framed glasses which makes him look a little like a professor.

"I’m Morden Will, my friends call me Morden."

Garen nodded, "Okay then, Morden, about the Gun Arts, how do you manage to train yourself to such degree of skill? Skip the denial part, I can tell, you already attained a high level of expertise."

A look of surprise flashed in Morden’s eyes, he grinned.

"You have a good judgment, sir. Actually, I’ve had a breakthrough only recently, and it felt like I went in an unknown, uncharted territory. I didn’t know you could recognize it."

He contemplated for a while, looking for the right words.

"How do I say this? Gun Arts is actually similar to Martial Arts, the only difference is we lack the defense module, focusing instead on the attack and evasion modules."

"Can you describe what it was like when you train?" Garen’s curiosity was piqued.

"Of course," Morden paused. "In the beginning, we practiced with static targets. It’s those with bullseyes that are not moving. When we’re practicing, we also look for the guns that are most suitable to us. It could be standard issue guns or customized guns, the only thing is that it should fit you like a glove. After having found the gun you are most suited to, as well as achieving 90% accuracy with a static target, this is level one."

"Level two is next. It’s about getting used to the maximum firing range of your gun. If you’re able to keep half your accuracy while aiming at maximum firing range, and separately hit a moving target with 90% accuracy, you’ll be in level two."

"Level three is when you find what you’re best at. With the foundation you had in the previous two levels, you will develop your evasion skills, until you are able to avoid at least half of the bullets from gunners of level one and two. At the same time, you will learn about all the qualities of all firearms, the strength and weakness, bullet trajectories from all kinds of bullets, identifying bullet marks, the different usage of different gunpowders, you’ll learn it all. You will also have the ability to customize bullets and modify your guns.

In this level, your gun will become even more suitable to you, its abilities easier to wield and allows the gunner to excel." Morden had a sense of pride on his face. "I’m in this level. Even if there was a hail of bullets, as long as there aren’t any stray bullets or too many people, a level three gunner wouldn’t have too much of a danger. Of course, there will be degrees to which you are proficient in level three. Different firearms will produce different effects in different environments, in addition to the number of guns you’re dodging, your familiarity with the environment, and your willpower, tactics, reaction speed, all these can become a vital point to winning a battle.

"Just like Martial Arts, right? Is there a higher level?" Garen inquired calmly.

"There is," Morden nodded, "Level four, that is a legendary state. Controlling multiple guns at the same time, having 360-degrees vision with no blind spot, being able to swiftly attack enemies before they’ve even moved. This level, is when you can fight a Grandmaster of Combat head on. One of the strongest was a Gun Arts Master who appeared a long time ago - Yoda, the Eight-Arm Dragon King. It was said that he was able to use Gun Arts against a Grandmaster of Combat. Unbelievable."

"A Gun Arts Master who fought against a Grandmaster of Combat… That really was something." Garen nodded.

"You’re not a gunner, you wouldn’t understand." Morden shook his head, "The ability to fight a Grandmaster of Combat head on, it means that the gunner must be able to keep up with the speed of a Grandmaster of Combat. As you would know, a speed-focused Grandmaster of Combat can cross a dozen meters in a blink of an eye. Without the speed to match, your head would roll before you could set up your gun."

"In other words, the Eight-Arm Dragon King at least has the eyesight and the speed of a first rated Grandmaster of Combat? That Yoda is not a Grandmaster of Combat, how did he acquire an eyesight and reaction like that?

"He must have a series of secret training method." Morden admitted his ignorance on the subject. "This is only an example of a single person against a Grandmaster of Combat. Of course, Grandmasters of Combat are strong, but they still wouldn’t be ablt to take on multiple firearms by themselves. I think you should train for a little Gun Arts, combining that and your Martial Arts, you would be a lot stronger.

Everyone was silent for a moment.

Garen glanced at everyone around him.

　

"How long did it take for you to reach level three?"

"Three years if you’re talented, but everyone has different limits. The heights to which everyone can reach is different." Morden said with a cocky air. "If you’re not talented, then you’ll need time and loads of bullet. Usually about twice the time, at least six years."

"Are there a lot of level three gunners?"

"One in a thousand."

Garen was deep in thought, it’s not that the ratio was low, on the contrary, the ratio was too high.

If it only takes several level three gunners to mob a slower Grandmaster of Combat to death, there are a hundred and fifty thousand soldier in the Confederation, how many gunners would there be? Amongst those, how many are level four?

This is an unknown.

Garen can now understand how Duskdune Shura was hurt badly by the Slash Brigade.

This is the power of the government.

If there’s an unknown number of Gun Arts Experts in the Confederate Army, what about Martial Arts Experts? How many are there in the world?

A silence lingered in the cabin for a while. Everyone was plunged into a muted poignancy. This is the tragedy of Martial Arts.

Firearms are superior in destructive power, compared to Martial Arts which is difficult to master, firearms are far more common and easier to learn and use.

The rest of the journey was spent in silence and contemplation.

By the time the aircraft arrived at the Lake Shore West City, dusk has fallen.

The Golden Loop arranged for everyone to rest in a luxurious hotel, it even had a Practice Room for people to train their bodies.

　　******************

Thud!

Cynthia’s foot landed on Garen’s torso, dispersing a cloud of white dust. She tried disengaging, but her right leg was caught with a slap from Garen.

"The first thing you need to do when practicing Mammoth Secret Technique… is get used to beatings!" Calmly, Garen swung Cynthia’s leg to the side.

Bam!

Cynthia was flung across the room and crashed onto the wall.

She grunted. After regaining her balance by stepping backwards, Cynthia charged forward fiercely, a small blade shot out from below the sole of her foot, and kicked upward.

With a shwing, the blade grazed in front of Garen’s nose, missing by a mere inch. Slashing air, Cynthia was suddenly hit by a sense of dread. Sure enough, her inner thigh was met with a great force. Her whole body fell backward.

　

Thud!

She sprawled on the ground lined with a rubber mattress. Struggling to get up, but her body didn’t seem to obey.

She looked up to see a sneaking Jack being thrown beside her, landing heavily and unable to move.

Both of them were glistening with sweat and looked awkward, their clothing drenched.

Garen slowly approached them.

"Not bad, you’re so much stronger than you were before. With firearms, you should be able to take on fighters below the level of a Grandmaster of Combat."

Cynthia hadn’t given up trying to stand up, but her control over her body was minimal.

"Weren’t you worried that I will surpass you if you keep letting us do sneak attacks? I will still kill you!" She stared at Garen, her face lined with defiance. "You are only older than I am by a little. If you can become so strong within that time, I can too!"

"‘Under the same conditions, I will not lose to anybody!’" Garen stated matter-o-factly, "This was the words you once said, which is why I promised to give you the best conditions to train, even the supplements and resources… If you really can do it, then do it. I will be waiting for you to achieve that. But, as long as you have not reached that goal, you will be my subordinate.

"Rest well. We will depart tomorrow morning."

He strolled past the duo by their side and exited the room. The suffocating ambience that was permeating the training room disappeared alongside him.

Chapter 160: Prodigy 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Cynthia gasped loudly, and finally started to pant. Her sweat slowly dripped from her temples.

"Garen is becoming more monstrous day by day," Jack on her side expressed with a wry smile, "Even looking into his eyes would scare me. I didn’t even feel that when I faced a fort full of machine guns, let alone standing up to him like you did."

"He’s not that much older than me!" Cynthia squeezed her words out resentfully, "I can’t forget the way he forced me into desperation! No matter where, I will be number one! The assassination training camp, the intensive training camp, even in the company! We’re the same age, why does he get to be so much stronger!"

Recalling the speech she heard on the plane, her hope reignited.

"You heard the guy, as long as we reach level 4 in Gun Arts, there will be a chance for us to harm a Grandmaster of Combat. If I combined Martial Arts training with Gun Arts, my power will increase exponentially!"

"You…" Jack didn’t know what to say, so he laid on the floor, letting his sweat drip on the ground.

Lake Shore West City, Red Sand Sword Gate main branch.

An ancient oriental quartet yard, surrounded with brown walls and covered with cinnabar red roof.

In a wide wooden training hall, five people in red were lighting the incense at a drawn picture with utter respect.

The leader was the current Red Sand Sword Gate’s Master, a handsome man with his red hair hanging past his shoulders. After offering the incense, he caressed his sword by his waist, and turned around to face the four Elders by his side.

"Elders, the traitor is back."

Out of the four Elders with white hair, one immediately gnashed his teeth in anger.

"That traitor dared…!"

The other three Elders, two older men and an older lady, didn’t wear any expressions on their faces, the ambience of the room was extra heavy.

"Who will fight against him?" The Master gave each Elder a once-over.

The Elder who spoke earlier shut up.

Silence.

The four Elders didn’t dare to speak.

The Master sighed, "Don’t you all hate him to his bones? Now that he’s here, why are you quiet as a mouse?"

Again, silence.

The Master looked aside in disappointment, not knowing what to say.

"Master, Clark is too dangerous. I recommend we should kill him together, no need to follow whatever duel commandments." An elder murmured.

"Elder Kane is right. We should all join forces and utilize all the power we can get, we must keep this disgrace here!"

"I propose to have five of our finest disciples join the mission. We’ll also get the chairmen from the branches to help, us Elders will support from the sideline."

"We can set up an ambush with firearm squad."

Each of the Elders started to discuss with vigor.

"Stop," the Master beckoned helplessly. "What about Beo?"

"Still at bedrest. He was hurt quite badly in this mission with the Confederation." An Elder answered.

Clark. The disgrace and blemish of Red Sand Sword Gate.

He was the strongest prodigy Red Sand Sword Gate! With only three years, he managed to grow into a Grandmaster of Combat from someone who has no foundation.

He was revered as the Palosa of Red Sand Sword. His seniors and elders gave him full attention, determined to make him the best that he can. When his fame began to rise, Andrela was still in his fundamental studies.

Clark laid a strong foundation for Red Sand Sword Gate’s growing influence and power. He mastered the strongest Secret Martial Art of the Red Sand Sword Gate, the Red Silk Secret Sword Technique* and brought it beyond the limit to a new heights. With that, he surpassed his elders and became the strongest person in the whole of Red Sand Sword Gate!

He had led the disciples of Red Sand Sword Gate into conquest battles, no matter head-on attacks or ambushes, he was able to come out victorious. Clark’s fame had reached its peak in history by that point.

Regretfully, Clark, at his peak, hadn’t been able to go further, he can no longer see a better future if he stayed in the Red Sand Sword Gate.

The repetition of leading conquest and gaining fame was wearing Clark off. Finally, that weariness exploded. One day, five year ago, he defected.

Under the persuasion of the Behemoth Gate, he killed his master and his beloved senior sister. Anyone who tried to stop him, whom he loved, he killed them all.

That’s the motto of the Behemoth Gate - Unfeeling, Uncaring.

The first condition was to defect. The second, to kill someone they loved.

These are the conditions to joining the Behemoth Gate, there was no turning back.

Red Sand Sword Gate changed in a single night. Everyone who went after him were either killed or badly hurt. The whole sect fell off its throne and was eventually succeeded by the Celestial Circle Gate.

"No one was able to kill him." Recalling his own memory of chasing after Clark, an Elder’s face switched between helpless, sorrow, pain, and fear.

"That’s right." The Master also sighed, "He had already surpassed me, he only defected because he wanted to pursue a path to power. I have no idea how strong he has become."

"We can ask Celestial Circle Gate for Andrela’s help." An Elder advised.

"It’s too late, he won’t be able to make it in time. Moreover, Andrela is strong, but still not Clark’s opponent." The Master shook his head. "Even I wouldn’t be able to guarantee victory, let alone him. I know Clark, he’s the type of prodigy who would look for your weak spots, even the Secret Martial Art of Celestial Circle Gate has been cracked by him. Not to mention our own Secret Martial Art, he knew it like the back of his hands, he won’t have any problem dealing with it."

He paused. "After his disappearance, I thought he died. I didn’t expect… Never mind, mobilize every single captain, we’ll defend the main branch.

For a moment, the air in the training hall was unbelievably dense.

The next day.

Garen and his team split up to look for information. The Eighth Hoop was in charge of the Golden Hoop in this city, who is the pale man who invited Garen into the Golden Hoop then. After meeting with Garen, he agreed, with alacrity, to supply manpower to help looking for Rosetta’s whereabout.

All of a sudden, the gangsters on the streets, the hidden goons in various companies, even some bosses and workers in shops were all assembled by the Eighth Hoop.

At the same time, at the outskirts of Lake Shore West City.

Two black cloaks stood, hidden within the poplar woods. They watched the two police dashed into an area belonging to Red Sand Sword Gate. The ray of dawn spilled onto their cloaks, revealing its unique scale-like shine. The white arc symbol at their backs were also illuminated.

"As expected, they went to the branch of Red Sand Sword. This city is the old nest of Red Sand Sword Gate, they must be seeking protection from them." Rosetta peered at the buildings standing beside the lake from afar, and glanced at her companion with curiosity. "What do you plan to do now?"

The other black cloak pulled his hood off, revealing his short white hair, smooth face, and a pair of rare plum-colored eyes.

"Red Sand Sword Gate? That brings back memories." He said softly. "They look like they were delivering the thing to Red Sand Sword for its protection. Ah well, it’s been awhile I haven’t gone back to check them out. After so many years, I wonder if the Master is still as indecisive as before."

"You wanna go back?" Rosetta asked, bewildered. "There were so many masters in there, yet you still want to trespass?"

"I just wanna see if they’ve grown after all these years." Clark said expressionlessly.

He smiled and slowly shifted toward the entrance of the branch, not bothered to hide himself.

Rosetta hesitated, and followed.

"They were looking for something?" Garen frowned. He was seated opposite of the Eighth Hoop in a tea room, sipping black tea with music flowing through the record player on the table.

"Yes. They were not planning to hide their paths. Just an hour ago, the Red Sand Sword branch at the outskirts caught on fire, no one was spared. The dozen of martial artists and disciples were all killed." The Eighth Hoop sighed, "This former strongest prodigy, he’s not the strongest for nothing*."

"What were they looking for?"

"I hear it’s a scroll leaked from the Behemoth Gate about a Secret Martial Art. Behemoth Gate investigated with a lot of their members and found out there were a lot of copies everywhere. Right now, they were sending people to recover all those scrolls." The Eighth Hoop giggled and sipped his black tea.

"Behemoth Gate." Garen was deep in thought. "Can you locate them?"

"It’s difficult. However," The Eighth Hoop laughed, "I checked Clark’s details. He will definitely infiltrate Red Sand Sword’s main branch by tonight. You can go there."

Garen gave it a thought.

"Thanks."

He stood up and exited the tea room.

"No problem."

The Eighth Hoop smiled, looking at Garen’s back.

Red Sand Sword’s strongest prodigy in history, Grandmaster of Combat Clark, has now joined the Behemoth Gate for five years. So much stronger, to what end?

Garen, on the other hand, is a rising star, they called him Number One Youth Grandmaster of Combat of the South.

"Heh heh, this should be fun." The Eighth Hoop took the teapot and poured himself another cup of tea.

Garen left the tea room. Corinne, Simon, Cynthia, and Jack were all waiting on the streets.

"Are the core members ready?"

"I left Karina in the hotel." Corinne nodded.

"Okay on my side, everything’s ready." Simon nodded excitedly. "My disciple is proficient in arrangements like this!"

"Both of you will stay." Garen said calmly.

"What! Why?" Corinne exclaimed.

"There is no ‘why’." Garen turned toward the car.

"Calm down Corinne, he’s only looking out for us, it’s too dangerous." Simon started to console Corinne.

Cynthia and Jack followed Garen into the car, Cynthia even made a face at Corinne.

"Why can they follow?" Corinne whined.

"Because you’re weak." Cynthia started to hum.

"Let’s go." Garen ordered calmly.

"Yessir."

The chauffeur immediately started the engine and started driving.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

1. 红纱秘剑 was given a different character, silk, with the same sound as sand. Possibly a wordplay.

2. In the original text, the author used a saying to signify that Clark would do anything to succeed.

Chapter 161: Prodigy 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the car, Garen closed his eyes for a little.

"Clark…" He was not sure what Clark is like as an enemy.

"I heard he’s the strongest Grandmaster of Combat in Red Sand Sword’s history," Jack sitting in the navigator seat said. "Boss, I checked the info, before he defected to Behemoth Gate, this Clark had suppressed the Celestial Circle Gate by himself. When he defected, he took one of the core Martial Arts of the Red Sand Sword Gate. As of now, his power should be close to Duskdune Shura’s."

"Close to Duskdune Shura’s, which means he’s still weaker than him?" Garen stated calmly.

"Uh, yeah, sure." Jack nodded, "Duskdune Shura used to comment about this. He said among the younger generation, Clark was the only one who can elicit a sense of threat to him."

"Very high evaluation, however, he still put himself at a higher pedestal with that comment. Which would mean, it was only a sense of threat." Garen shook his head. "Very well, at least I can gauge how strong I’ve become."

"Boss is of course the strongest." Jack whistled.

About a kilometer from Red Sand Sword’s main branch, the car stopped in an obscure street.

Garen looked upon the upper regions of Red Sand Sword Gate. One of the Eighth Hoop’s men were there, waiting for Clark and Rosetta’s appearance.

The bright sky, ever so slowly, dimmed to a shady gloom. Rain drizzled down the street in the afternoon, casting the already vacant street into a chilly disuse.

The driver from Golden Hoop glanced at Garen through the rearview mirror.

"Sir, do you want anything to eat?

"I’ll go get some snacks." "I brought some beef jerky, spicy beef flavor, it’s nice." Both Cynthia and Jack had their plans.

Garen asked the driver for four hard boiled eggs as dinner.

Lake Shore West City was three times bigger than Huaishan City, but the population was only half of it, pretty sparse. It took the driver a while to find a place that sells hard boiled eggs, so he bought eight at once.

Having their dinner casually, the sky finally darkened completely.

Tick!

Above Red Sand Sword’s main branch, a white light clicked into existence like a glowing mushroom.

Garen’s eyes focused on the white light.

"They’re coming."

He exited the car, followed by Cynthia and Jack after they prepared their firearms.

"Hide yourself." Garen unhurriedly gave them an order, and hasted toward Red Sand Sword.

　　**************

Clink clank!

Two clashes of swords, Clark straighten up his body slowly, his fine sword retracting with the same pace.

At his side, two elder men stepped back respectively, their swords splitting into two. The two men were stunned.

"Double Sword Strike! You mastered the Double Sword Strike!"

One of them stuttered, his voice quivering as he spoke.

Red Sand Sword Gate Master stood in the middle of the courtyard of the main branch, accompanied by the elites in the Gate.

Clark smirked and glanced at the anxiety-ridden Red Sand Sword Gate members.

"Give me the thing, it’s not yours to keep."

His sight fell on the two police behind the Red Sand Sword Gate Master.

The two were as pale as ghosts, eyes drooping. After being on the run for such a long time, they damaged their bodies beyond what would be called "normal".

The situation in the courtyard was awkward, to say the least.

Clark and Rosetta were both surrounded, at least a dozen of Red Sand Sword Gate members were beaten to the ground, no one else dared to advance to attack, holding their ground.

Outside the Red Sand Sword courtyard, there was another circle of people in black uniform. These people were all dressed in black, but they weren’t from the same faction, differentiated by the crests they’re wearing. The white arcs, they were from the Behemoth Gate. The others were wearing black crosses, those people were from the Black Mark Association.

The people from the Black Mark Association were lead by two people, a middle-aged lady and a towering man. They stood side by side, observing the situation in the courtyard.

Red Sand Sword Gate Master scanned at the outer circle.

"Clark, you brought people from both Behemoth Gate and Black Mark Association, were you trying to threaten my sect?

The situation was truly unusual at this stage. Black Mark Association weren’t wholeheartedly trying to help Clark, they wanted the secret scroll too, coming as a separate entity on their own.

Aside from the Behemoth Gate, represented by Clark and Rosetta, the Celestial Circle Gate had alse had people dispatched after Red Sand Sword Gate informed them about their situation.

As long as anyone can thwart Clark’s advance, the secret scroll can be saved.

Red Sand Sword Gate Master was still wearing his confident smile on his face. Whether he is actually confident is another matter, he has to show enough confidence to assure the disciples in his sect.

He glanced at the two Elders not far from him. Both of them were bleeding from between their thumbs and index fingers, having hurt themselves by the countershock when they tried to sneak attack from behind.

Clark didn’t even turn behind, he only needed to brandish his sword to block the full strength attacks of them both combined.

"If we can’t sneak up on him, we’ll swarm him! I don’t believe he has the power to walk out of here unscathed." Gate Master* blinked and sneakily caught a glimpse of the people from Black Mark Association.

He pressed his thumb and little finger together and flicked.

A sudden, yet uniformed set of steps sounded. The four people in the forefront of Red Sand Sword Gate, together with the two who were hurt, all charged at Clark.

Gate Master waved his arm, throwing a black scroll a dozen meters into the air. That was the scroll Behemoth Gate wanted to destroy.

People from Black Mark Association started rushing for the scroll, as well as those from Behemoth Gate.

In the darkness, there were sounds of fabric being rustled by the wind, two other elites blitzed at the scroll.

All eyes were concentrated on the scroll in the air.

"King of Fist Leo!" "Sky Warrior Corbella!"

Some people in the crowd yelled in surprise.

They recognized the two Grandmasters of Combat.

One of the three Kings of Fist in Black Mark Association, Leo, and Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate’s Sky Warrior Corbella.

Bam!

Two massive Braveries clashed in mid-air, everyone felt as if a hammer hit them on their heads and started having vertigo.

They seem to be able to hear an eagle’s scream and a tiger’s roar.

With a heavy thud, both the fighters in the air fell backward.

King of Fist Leo fell into the Black Mark Association crowd, while Sky Warrior Corbella stumbled into the Red Sand Sword crowd.

"Attack!"

Red Sand Sword Gate Master roared. All the Red Sand Sword disciples and Elders, as well as elites from each branch lunged at the Behemoth Gate followers.

Some of them even brought out their guns and started shooting. However, untrained shooters cannot harm the extreme agile martial artists.

It really was quite a scene.

Some five people from Red Sand Sword Gate carried their submachine guns and shotguns, and opened fire at Clark wildly.

Intense clink-clanking sounded non-stop all over the battlefield.

Sparks enveloped Clark as his sword arm disappeared into thin air, forming a protective barrier with his sword to deflect every single bullet that had been shot his way.

The deflected bullets avoided followers of Behemoth Gate as if they’re conscience, and sped through the air toward disciples of Red Sand Sword Gate. Just a moment after, flocks of Red Sand Sword disciples were hit.

Bubbled within a barrier of sparks, Clark’s cheek glowed a sickly crimson.

"Fighters relying on firearms, Red Sand Sword Gate has really rotted to the core."

Seeing the ineffectiveness of firearms, Gate Master gritted his teeth and charged into the fight with the four Elders.

The five of them surrounded Clark, striking frantically with their swords, as though there were five fiery snakes circling him. The blades of the swords started heating up due to the friction between the metal and air. The swords, made with special materials, have extremely high heat conductivity. The swords soon became red from the heat, so much so that whenever they tapped on their opponent, they had the added effect of piercing and burn damages.

The swords strikes left behind red blurs like red sand pouring through the air. This is how Red Sand Sword got its name.

With five top fighters joined forces, even Clark was having troubles fighting them off. No one even dared to be near them within a dozen meters.

Six of them were in the same sect, they were so familiar with each other’s fighting styles, they have practically no secrets from each other in terms of their strengths and weaknesses. In this fight, one side will eventually win out of sheer power and groundwork.

On the other side of the battlefield, King of Fist Leo from Black Mark Association and Sky Warrior Corbella from Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate started fighting each other again. Like Red Sand Sword and Clark, both of them knew each other’s fighting styles so well, they were not able to tell if one is stronger than the other in such a short time.

The other less experienced fighters also battled against each other.

Rosetta fought against one of the four branch chairmen. They were both top fighters who are close to being Grandmasters of Combat. The branch chairman’s sword had less intense red blur, but the speed is still not a normal fighter can keep up to. This is a first grade Secret Martial Art, it’s what Red Sand Sword could become the leading sect once upon a time.

Even though Rosetta joined Behemoth Gate, her training for a stronger Secret Martial Art is still too little. If it wasn’t for her opponent constant distraction at the Gate Master’s direction, she had already lost.

"Tsk tsk… Rosetta, have you not already beaten your opponent?" A coquettish voice appeared behind Rosetta.

"Angela! Mind your own business!" Rosetta’s face darkened, becoming impatient, her Fist Technique disturbed by the interruption.

Tssss!

Her left shoulder was scraped by her opponent’s sword. A scalding sting pulsed from her shoulder.

Her opponent was already stronger than her, coupled with her natural disadvantage as a Fist Artist against a Swordsman who wields Red Sand Sword, a speed-focused Sword Art, even a slight distraction would cause a burnt mark on her skin.

"As expected, you were only paired up with Clark because of your junior brother, Sky Warrior Garen’s fame. The higher ups had such high hopes for you, but you were disappointing. You think you are good enough to match Lord Clark with your junk skills?"

The woman behind Rosetta was dressed flirtatiously with on her shapely physique. Her hair was short and pale green. A short spike in her hand danced around, poking bloodied holes into her enemies. To her, strolling past the elites of Red Sand Sword Gate was like taking a walk in the woods.

Rosetta gritted her teeth, trying hard to focus. When Garen became famous, the higher ups raised her to an impossibly high position, going on missions with Clark. Obviously, from being a normal member, her promotion to such a high position made other elites in the Behemoth Gate less than happy. Everyone thought she was basking in the light of Sky Warrior Garen.

As Sky Warrior Garen’s senior sister, her power could only be stronger than her junior brother. However, no matter how much effort she puts in, her strength only increased slowly. Sometimes, because of overtraining, her injuries even sets her back in strength.

Translator's Thoughts

J_Squared J_Squared

Gate Master refers to Red Sand Sword Gate Master, in case you’re confused. Same below unless specified otherwise.

Chapter 162: Prodigy 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Unless I said something wrong?" The girl smiled, "look at your opponent who fights without strength, sloppy movement and shows no intention of killing at all. They don’t even treat you like an opponent, they’re just fooling with you."

"Shut up!" Rosetta growled, but was immediately cut across the chest on the shirt by Crimson Sand Sword’s chief, leaving a black mark on her shirt.

"Look at your embarrassed face," the girl smiled, "I heard you’ve taught - before, and with this level you’ve actually produced a pro fighter, so how do you really teach it? Hmm… let me think, did you teach it in bed?"

"Angela, are you looking to die?!" Rosetta couldn’t resist her anger anymore, she turned her back as if desperately wanting to leave the opponent.

In the blink of an eye, a red light shimmered in front of her eyes. Chi chi chi! Three times consecutively and the clothes on Rosetta’s shoulders tore. If it wasn’t for her Hardening Technique, that move would’ve caused her life because she made the mistake of triggering her emotions.

"I said it right? Are you angered by that embarrassment?" Angela showed an innocent face with her hand under her chin. "You weren’t hurt badly? This is White Cloud Gate’s Mammoth Secret Hardening Technique? However, why does it look so weak when compared to other secret techniques?"

"Poor bastard, the day Clark gets bored of fooling with you would be the day you die." Suddenly her expression changed, showing a sinister smile. "You looked so cocky, I thought you had such strong powers, but turns out you're just a disappointment. This is your White Cloud Gate’s Mammoth Secret Hardening Technique?"

Rosetta boiled with anger, but the more she raged, the more she was suppressed by the opponent. Not only that, the injuries on her body also increased.

"Enough."

With a loud "chi", a red sword stabbed into the front side of Angela’s toe and for a moment, it left the floor burning in white smoke.

A red light flashed by, Angela’s opponent retreated with a soft hmm, hugging both hands while wrestling her way out.

Clark slowly walked in from the side.

"The higher authorities did not pair me up with Rosetta because of her abilities," he explained faintly.

Angela was slightly startled but finally understood everything.

At the moment, the situation was unfogging before her.

Clark already injured a bunch of pros from the Crimson Sand Sword. The remaining party was left surrounded, defending themselves with guns.

The Black Mark Association’s King of Fist Leo stared at Behemoth Gate, as members of Black Mark Association and the Behemoth Gate did battle with each other. Besides this was the Sky Warrior Corbella, who were standing with the Crimson Sand Sword.

That black scroll fell in the middle of the arena. However, it was left untouched; nobody had dared to reach for it for fear of being killed by the surrounding fighters. The King of Fist Leo gave it a shot, but was immediately attacked, leaving him with no choice but to retreat.

Clark was the only one walking slowly towards the scroll, flicked it upwards with his toes and caught it in his hands as it fell.

As he held the scroll...

Boom!

Suddenly, a great number of guns were focused at him, and with it, ten times the amount of extremely strong hidden weapons spun around at breakneck speed towards Clark. In it included a lot of grenades.

Everything erupted in a split second. The weapons rang in the same moment, leaving behind a single, unified, deafening boom.

At the same time, Clark’s surrounding lit up with piece of red sword shadow, an impossible armada of red lights burst at once.

As all the hidden weapons fired, a blanket of shadows was cast upon Clark’.

The arena was suddenly half empty, as if like bodies were rising and falling.

As everyone stared at the black figured shadow in the middle of the arena, they felt the same chill in their heart.

The Crimson Sand Sword sect’s five strongest Grandmasters of Combat all attacked at once, were all injured, and did not dare attack anymore. Now it did not matter how many fire weapons were aimed at them, he still did not feel half threatened.

No matter if it was Sky Warrior Corbella or King of Fist Leo, everyone stared at Clark with an unusually dignified look. They looked at each other, scarcely believing that he had come out unscathed after that exchange, still looking calm as ever.

"Any takers?" Clark asked softly while tossing the scroll.

The arena was silent. A hand trembled somewhere in the crowd.

Everyone around who opened fire including the hidden weapons experts were injured with the ricocheted bullets and weapons. They were all either injured or dead.

"The Crimson Sand Sword is now are all but rotten to the core…" Clarked sighed, "but it’s good. Let tonight be Crimson Sand Sword’s last memory. Such a rotten sword based sect has finally died by my hand."

He held his sword, walking slowly towards the present group members of Crimson Sand Sword.

"Clark!" Crimson Sand Sword’s chief shouted suddenly. "You don’t really think that is the secret scroll, do you? Still remember the King’s Cave?"

Clark squinted and held his steps, his eyes were locked on the body of two policemen who stood behind the Gate Master.

"What do you mean?"

The Gate Master of Crimson Sand Sword held his hand to his back and using his fingers, he drew a word on the hand of the small policeman: stall.

The male policeman Jia Ning finally understood. He knew now that the important moment has come. If they can’t force Clark to retreat, they all would have to die!

He summoned his courage and yelled. "The secret scrolled we retrieved in the King’s Cave was actually fake."

When he and his junior sister investigated that murder case, they were constantly chased after they got the secret scroll. It wasn’t easy as they stumbled back to the city, in fact they were almost killed by a hidden weapon in the police station.

"It’s a fake? So where’s the real one?" laughed Clark. The long sword in his hands gradually turned cold, returning to its original black colour. "Since you brought it up, then you should know it too, don’t you?"

"We’re not lying. Actually… Actually it is tied to a treasure map!" Jia Ning started panicking.

"Treasure map?" Clark frowned. He knew about this secret scroll. He was particularly interested in this scroll that was leaked within the sect, as to why so much attention was given to a Secret Scroll of Secret Technique that wasn’t considered strong. What secrets did it hide that would constitute the mobilization of a first class fighter like him?"

You need to know that to convince this level of Grandmaster of Combat to make a move, the resources that cost them was definitely not a small number.

"Why don’t you explain the origin of this treasure map?"

The small policeman Jia Ning tried his very best to calm down and maintain a confident front.

He just heard someone behind whispered to him that Clark’s Behemoth Gate’s members have an enemy that would rush over tonight, so all he needed to do was stall for a bit. Who knows, the situation might take a good turn.

This was the Gate Master’s meaning and arrangement.

Although he was panicking, but he still tried his best to slow down his heart beat.

"This treasure map is actually related to one of Behemoth Gate’s big secret!"

"Big secret?! You’re saying Behemoth Gate’s big secret?" A ridiculing smile appeared on Clark’s face.

"Chi"!

The fine sword on his left hand blurred for a moment. Suddenly, Crimson Sand Sword’s fist master groped his neck and fell sideways to the floor, showing a small piece of rock wedged in his neck where red blood was oozing out. The boxer struggled a few times and eventually, stopped moving.

"Tell me. If I find out that what you say is untrue, and that you were lying to me…" Clark easily drew a few sword shadows.

Everyone in the arena, including the Black Mark Association’s fist master and Holy Fist Gate’s Divine Marshal, did not seem to care. The him now is already headed towards becoming a pro fist master who’s at the pinnacle of the art. The average level of a Grandmaster of Combat does not even exist in his eyes anymore.

In here, he’s the strongest of all!

"Treasure… The Treasure Map is real!" Jia Ning shouted as beads of sweat formed on his forehead, "it is hidden in the secret scroll! Unless you assume that Behemoth Group would really waste all those resources on a Secret Scroll of Secret Technique that is not considered the best?"

Clark’s expression changed but that statement confirmed his initial doubt.

Seeing that Clark started to hesitate, Jia Ning quickly added.

"Hidden inside the treasure map is what was once the rare treasure that was buried by the Behemoth Gate! It can bring your martial arts to the next level! This was the secret I chanced upon in the King’s Cave!"

Clark frowned, though it wasn’t only him. Even the Black Mark Association and the Sky Warrior Corbella seem to be convinced.

Originally Behemoth Gate’s actions were a little suspicious, but with the small policeman’s stall, everybody started doubting.

"Where did you hear this from?" Clark asked.

Small policeman Jia Ning was scared by his aggressiveness that his head was full of sweat. Under intense pressure, he involuntarily wanted to speak the truth.

"I… I…"

Clark laughed, "Tell me, are you lying to me." He lifted his long sword, and slowly walked towards the direction of the Crimson Sand Sword group.

Boom!

At this time, a majestic transparent wave quickly flew in from the courtyard outside.

Moo! A huge elephant cry came from the courtyard.

Everyone in the courtyard felt their bodies sinking, as deep and huge as the sea being over the courtyard.

With a click, the courtyard was hit.

A strong, muscular shadow of a figure stood in front of the door.

The air surrounding his body seem to twist and move, as if a huge transparent mask was on him. A huge pressure, like waves was heavily pressed upon everybody in the courtyard.

At the same time, a faint sound of soldiers running came from the outside. Shortly, the Crimson Sand Sword sect was surrounded by rows of armed soldiers.

"We finally found you, Rosetta…" Garen slowly walked in through the main door, dressed in black leather shoes, expression cold as ever. His eyes quickly fell onto the girl behind Clark.

"Southern Twelve Gates’ most powerful ones, Garen Lombard… is finally here!" the Gate Master of Crimson Sand Sword let out a sigh of relief.

Clark turned his head to look at Garen. The relaxed smile he carried before vanished quickly.

"White Cloud Gate’s is here to cleanup, Behemoth Gate’s members stay, everyone else may leave," Garen’s voice echoed softly in the courtyard.

Rosetta looked like a miserable mess, she looked at her junior across the courtyard while panting heavily. That teen who was once a weakling, had now grown into an undefeatable fighter.

The two of them exchanged glares for a short while, and memories of the past seemed to flash between them.

"Where’s second senior brother? Where’s the boss?" Garen’s face returned to a peaceful expression.

"I knew you would come," Rosetta started catching her breath and stood up straight. She was about to say something else, but was stopped by Clark.

Clark’s face was filled with excitement, he slowly lifted up his long sword.

Hummmm!!

He violently brandished his sword in intimidation.

"As soon as I kill you, I will be able to advance to the next level!"

His eyes started to glow a mad red.

Garen looked at him

Rumble!!

A great amount of energy gathered around Clark, and crushed him.

Ka Cha!

Clark’s face turned into fear, the ground beneath him cracked, as he took a few steps back from the attack.

The whole courtyard fell to silence.

Chapter 163: The Star Lit Sky of the Night 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You!!" Lord Clark’s face went from a pale white to a furious green, then from green it went to a purplish red. His chest was rising and falling with his breathes, his face filled with disbelief as he stared at Garen.

The arena was silent, most of the members of the Crimson Sand Sword were sighing breaths of relief, so many had died on the arena, and all of them were their own. They all came from simple families, with ranks in the army, all loyal members to the sect. Now that the enemy of the Behemoth Gate had appeared, they were no longer the main attraction of the opponent.

Members of the Black Mark Association however, had their eyes on the King of Fist, Leo, whose eyebrows were locked together tightly. When Garen started relaxed for a bit, Leo turned his attention to the Sky Warrior Corbella.

Who knew whether if Corbella would be on Garen’s side, even the usually fearless Lord Clark was retreating in fear upon sensing Garen’s aura, even he was intimidated by the last Sky Warrior of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate.

Leo had originally thought that the Black Mark Association and the Behemoth Gate were sure to win, but who had expected this sudden change and interruption.

No, Lord Clark must’ve anticipated this right?

Leo turned his attention to Lord Clark and the two women behind him. The members of the Behemoth Gate that stood behind the trio didn’t seem too surprised by Garen’s sudden appearance, but were more shocked by Garen’s true power.

The other Sky Warrior Corbella looked at Garen from afar, he squinted, and crossed his arms as if he was thinking of something in the corner.

"Garen Lombard," Lord Clark stood still as ever, his face finally returning to normal,"shouldn’t you be in Galantia? What business do you have coming here?" He seemed to have forgotten the shameful exchange earlier.

Garen usually operated out of Galantia, where he was the most powerful figure, a position that was recognized by everyone within the region. The Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate had noticed that Garen had no plans to expand beyond Galantia, and had since recognized the entire state as the property of the White Cloud Gate.

Almost everyone in the martial arts world knew that Galantia was White Cloud Gate’s Garen’s territory.

Garen took a sweeping look at the entire arena.

"Looks like nobody is listening to me huh? Is nobody going to pull out?"

"Wait wait!" The leader of the Crimson Sand Sword yelled,"we the members of the Crimson Sand Sword are willing to grant this territory to White Cloud Gate’s Garen as the venue for him to settle his vendetta, we pull out!"

Reaching a situation like this, the Gate Master no longer cared about the reputation of his sect. Despite being usually proud, in the face of a life threatening situation, everything else was secondary.

Once upon a time when Lord Clark betrayed his original sect and got the Celestial Circle Gate knocking on his door demanding an explanation, he had given way then, hence there was no hesitation for this time as well.

"Gate Master!!"

Four of the elders alongside a few of the leading members of the sect yelled, their faces turned a gloomy grey, as they clenched their fists in anger. The rest of the members and followers however just stayed silent, only a few felt ashamed and angry.

On top of letting someone else invade their homeground, they now had to cede their land for the invader to settle his vendetta?! In the world of martial arts, this was a shame beyond description.

"Say no more!," The groundsman of the Crimson Sand Sword sect suppressed the anger of the followers,"retreat!"

Garen watched as all the members of the Crimson Sand Sword retreated hastily, even attempts to pick up corpses were halted by their founder.

Behemoth Gate’s Lord Clark and its members, alongside followers of the Black Mark Association didn’t stop their retreat, they merely stared at Garen.

As all this was happening, members of the Black Mark Association and Behemoth’s Gate silently surrounded Garen.

"I thought I could have a fair fight with you, but looks like that’s impossible now." Lord Clark’s face was sinisterly peaceful,"Garen Lombard, you grew too quick! You really thought nobody would ever discover your secret huh?"

"Hmm?" Garen’s expression turned into a confused gaze,"secret?"

"Hand over the secret technique to brewing the Blood of Secrets," Lord Clark’s sword suddenly started vibrating violently, turning from black to a bright red, like a high temperature piece of metal.

Garen was stunned, these idiots actually thought his rapid growth was because he had used the Blood of Secrets. For a moment he thought that Lord Clark had discovered his bizarre secret when Clark made that statement.

"Looks like you will never be satisfied unless I destroy you," Garen’s said with an expressionless face, Lord Clark smiled coldly and clapped his hands.

Two men of dressed in black cloth suddenly walked out from a corner of the courtyard, holding some sort of a weird blue machine gun in hand.

Upon seeing these two individuals, the other Sky Warrior’s expression changed, he tapped his foot on the ground rapidly, and instantly leaped to the side of Garen.

"I am Sky Warrior Corbella, be careful of the gun in the hands of those two men, that’s a specially made Ming Wen Gun, it uses the most powerful purple gunpowder!" he explained softly.

Garen looked at him.

"Purple gunpowder?"

"This is the Killer Hunters Squad! Lord Clark is a member of the Killer Hunters Squad!" Sky Warrior Corbella seemed to have suddenly remembered something important.

He wasn’t exactly quiet about it either, everyone in the courtyard heard him, even the Gate Master who was about to leave stopped in his steps.

"Killer Hunters Squad? What’s that?" Small Policeman Jia Ning stood by a side wiping his sweat.

The expressions of the Gate Master and the elders around him looked horrible.

"Killer Hunters Squad….is a collaborative effort between the Behemoth Gate and the Weisman Empire. It is responsible for the hunting and elimination of highly skilled fighters within the Confederation. While most martial art practitioners are vulnerable against firearms, skilled fighters are not threatened nor afraid of firearms at all. Hence the Weisman Empire created the Killer Hunters Squad with the sole purpose of reducing the potential threats within the populace of the Confederation!"

"Clark’s group was never here for the scroll, instead they just wanted to bait Garen. As soon as Garen left Galantia, they were awaiting him with a plethora of traps!" The Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword suddenly felt defeated, just like the days when he watched as Lord Clark slowly gained influence and strength, while he watched on powerlessly.

The once proud and self thought to be powerful Crimson Sand Sword Gate was now reduced to just bait and venue providers in the face of these true masters.

"What a grand setting…," he turned his head to look at the courtyard, the sky there was being occasionally lit up by brighter and brighter balls of light,"Behemoth Gate, Black Mark Association, they have both sent their best fighters here today. I reckon that most of the best fighters of the southside are gathered here today, whatever that transpires today will define the southside for years to come."

"Gate Master...what should we do then?" among the crowd, one of the elders inquired.

"We continue to retreat."

Members of the Crimson Sand Sword continued to retreat in an organised manner, everyone was filled with a good amount of angst inside their hearts.

"Killer Hunters Squad..."

Small Policeman Jia Ning seemed to only roughly understand the situation. He lifted his female colleague in one hand, comforting her, while he looked onto the courtyard.

"Mister Gate Master, so you would say that this Killer Hunters Squad is incredibly powerful?"

"They are VERY powerful. They might not be too strong alone, but if they were to group up, the threat they pose overpowers any top fighter." the Gate Master nodded.

"In that case, the man named Garen earlier must be in danger then?" Jia Ning asked softly.

"This is a trap set just for him, an entire nation’s resources pitted against him. Without a doubt, he will die here today." the Gate Master nodded again.

Jia Ning laughed,"I don’t know much about fighters or martial artists, that is your world," he rubbed his nose,"I only know that if it wasn’t for Garen earlier, we would all probably be dead already."

"What do you want to do?" his female colleague asked him,"Jia Ning you better not be having some stupid brainy idea again!"

"I’m not having a brainy moment!" Jia Ning laughed,"In the east we have a saying: ‘A man’s got to do what he’s got to do.’ Just now Garen saved me, now it’s my turn to save him."

He pushed his female colleague aside, and took big strides towards the courtyard.

Members of the Crimson Sand Sword looked at him stunned, at a loss for words at sight of his act.

"You will not save anyone by doing this! You’re just walking into certain death!" the Gate Master bellowed, his face confused.

Jia Ning stopped for a bit,"Didn’t you say earlier that they are weak alone? Who know if I could disrupt their formation somehow?"

He sped up and ran towards the courtyard, disappearing into the shadows.

"Gate Master!"

One of the leaders couldn’t help but yell.

The Gate Master lowered his head,

"What I’m doing…..is for the sake of our entire sect!"

Everyone was silent now, as they recalled how they were all ambushed by Lord Clark’s people earlier.

*************************************

Garen squinted his eyes, staring at the two individuals who had just walked out. He wasn’t certain how powerful that gun really was, but since the enemy was poised in such a formation, it was obvious they had studied his methods before this.

"A trap set just for me?"

"The Weisman Empire’s Killer Hunters Squad, paired with Behemoth Gate’s best fighters, we’re in some hot soup this time," Sky Warrior Corbella felt the situation not in their favour. Although he too was a top classed fighter, and had been a practitioner for many years, but against a setup like this, even he was in a bad spot.

Within the courtyard, Black Mark Association’s King of Fist Leo and the Killer Hunters Squad stood by a side.

On the other side, was Behemoth Gate along with Lord Clark, Angela and Rosetta. The courtyard was split into three distinct groups.

The two sects surrounded Garen, in a tight formation, as they fought the soldiers Garen brought with him outside the formation.

But anyone could tell that those normal soldiers stood no chance against these two major sects. The situation was not in Garen’s favor at all.

"Weisman Empire’s Killer Hunters Squad?" this was Garen’s first time hearing about them,"are they very powerful?"

Sky Warrior Corbella nodded,"Insanely so! They are as good as the best marksmen in the Confederation, selected as a few out of the five million strong army of the empire. The best of the best!"

"Garen, just hand it over. That technique is wasted in the hands of you alone. As long as you hand it over to us Behemoth Gate, we guarantee that you will receive an even greater amount of resources to build yourself. We can finally cut off The Immortal Palace Alliance’s monopoly! We will be able to those terrorists that dare to drive the government. The Empire will also take you in as a citizen, with at least a Baron or above as a title to start." Lord Clark’s lip turned into a sinister smile,"in fact, weren’t you almost killed by the Immortal Palace Alliance’s Sylphalan? Don’t you want revenge?"

"You know that too?!" Garen was shocked. He was having fun leading these people on their own mistake, or else it would be really hard to explain his rapid growth.

Chapter 164: The Star Lit Sky of the Night 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Sylphalan is a madman, if you can survive a fight with him, you can definitely provide us with valuable information about him. This would be beneficial to both of us," Lord Clark smiled,"if it were possible, I wouldn’t want to destroy such a powerful fighter like you. Not many are as merciful and open minded as I."

Garen was silent.

"Still can’t make up your mind?" Lord Clark’s sword tip touched the ground, releasing a small streak of white smoke where it touched the ground,"in fact, I even accidentally acquired some information." he stopped for a bit, lowered his voice.

"You seemed to have joined some underground society, you seem to be searching for something...?" he said with a light touch of suspicion.

Garen’s face dropped.

"You know too much..."

Rumble!!!

He suddenly disappeared from where he stood, the entire courtyard rumbled as ground exploded, forming a massive crater and sending small pieces of rock flying everywhere.

Boom!!

Lord Clark’s expression changed rapidly, a massive amount of crimson sand like speckles of light appeared in front of him, they were streaks of light made by the brandishing over an infinite amount of sword tips.

The red dot collided with a black shadow, releasing a loud and terrifying rumble.

Lord Clark blocked the attack with his whole body, but he felt his limbs go numb, they had been vibrated to the point of total numbness.

Another rumble and a loud sound came again from the front.

"Open fire now!!!" Lord Clark ordered at the top of his voice.

"He is too fast!" two of the Killer Hunters Squad’s marksmen panicked,"didn’t you say that he was really slow? How can be so fast! Fuck!"

They could only see a blackish grey shadow continuously collide with Lord Clark’s body, blow after blow it let out terrifying bangs that scared onlookers till they were numb in their limbs. Even the floor seemed to be vibrating.

Lord Clark’s body was surrounded by the red speckles as he tried to defend, but he wasn’t able to catch up to any of the actions. Ever since the first hit, it seemed as if he was alone in the courtyard.

A streak of black shadow kept attacking him all over his body, the Crimson Sand Sword Gate’s secret defense technique: Crimson Sword Veil, was about to fall apart.

"Quickly open fire! Open fire!!" Clark was losing his sanity, he swung his sword around desperately, each swing weaker than the one before.

Clark was a fighter that had honed his speed and strength to the pinnacle, even Garen was not as fast as him, but yet Garen was facing the tip of Clark’s sword with his bare fists. Each time Garen’s fists met Clark’s sword, Garen would continue unscathed, while Clark’s whole body would tingle, his strength slowly fading away.

Should Clark just miss Garen’s attacks once, it would mean certain death!

As if some sort of inexplicable fear was brewing within him, Clark released all his might like never before, his strong observation abilities were now able to see Garen’s movements as Garen swung his fist, took a step forward, swung his fist, took another step forward.

It was just two simple movements, Garen was expressionless, he was like a dead man, like the world around him had no effect on him whatsoever.

The ground would erupt in small explosions, leaving small craters in the wake of each step Garen took, like small bombs were exploding, they sent gravel and dirt flying all over the place.

Rosetta and Angela could only step away, keeping a distance so they would not be injured by the stray gravel.

At this moment, a huge empty space was made in the middle of the courtyard.

In the centre of it all, Clark was swinging his sword furiously alone like a red ball of light, a black streak kept flying around him, it was the mirage of Garen’s ridiculous speed.

Boom!!

Finally, Clark was hit on the waist by one of Garen’s palms, and was sent flying across the courtyard.

With a big splash, he landed in the fake mountain in the pond of the courtyard. The entire fake mountain was blasted apart, turning into dust instantly.

Clark lied in the pile of rocks with his sword, coughing loudly, his eyes, nose and ears were bleeding.

Pow! Pow!

Two sounds of gunshots went off at the same time.

Clang clang!

Garen’s chest was hit, producing two bright sparks, and forming two holes on his suit.

He casually tore his suit off, revealing two bleeding holes on his chest, the long purple and black bullets actually managed to penetrate about half of their lengths into his skin.

"Oh I’m hurt..." he flexed and swung his chest muscles, squeezing the two bullets out of his body, as they fell with soft dings.

"You folks actually managed to injure me, well done." Garen’s face produced a coy smile.

He stomped the ground.

With a loud bang, a massive piece of rock blew out from the ground, he whipped his feet and produced more.

A large amount of rocks flew out like cannon balls in every direction, taking down members of the Behemoth’s Gate around him in quick blow.

Two of the Killer Hunters Squad members evaded the rocks and lifted their guns ready to shoot.

Roar!!

Garen suddenly made a loud sound like the roar of an elephant, sending a minor earthquake about the entire courtyard.

The loud and terrifying roar shockwave headed straight for the two Killer Hunters, the both of them suddenly felt their whole bodies go numb, as their hands trembled and pointed their guns upwards, Bang bang!

Two bullets flew straight up and landed nowhere.

The two Killer Hunters’ faces were now filled with fear.

"Retreat!!"

With a swift movement, the two Killer Hunters rolled on the floor, evaded more oncoming rocks and took two blind shots.

They hit Garen’s wrist, shaking it slightly.

"Everyone attack!!"

Clark bellowed.

The two Killer Hunters quickly split up and aimed at Garen from two different angles.

At the same time, Clark and King of Fist Leo propelled themselves onto Garen. Angela clenched her teeth, suppressing her shaky hands, she produced two throwing stars and threw them at Garen’s back.

Rumble….

Two rockets appeared out of nowhere suddenly, and were headed towards Garen with a pillar of white smoke behind them.

In that split second, attacks were coming from every direction.

For inexplicable reasons, while being surrounded by all these threats, Garen suddenly thought of his conversation with Duskdune Shura by the cliffside…

"The you now, is just like the him of then," Duskdune Shura recalled,"before Palosa became the Saint of Fist Techniques, he was just like you. Young and undefeatable, even against Grandmasters from an older generation. However, sadly..."

"Sadly what?" Garen stared at him.

"You lack the aura of magnificence."

"Aura of magnificence?" Garen looked up into the sky as if he had just thought of something.

The night sky was littered with infinite stars, a great majestic sense of awe overwhelmed him.

"Without Defeat, Without Competition….." he muttered to himself.

Rumble!!

The rockets exploded, a large amount of bullets were shot in Garen’s direction, a thick fog mixed with dust and dirt formed after the explosions, for a moment nobody could tell what had happened.

Clark and King of Fist Leo still stood on the same spot, they were standing by for Garen’s evasion attempts, but surprisingly, Garen made no attempt to hide nor evade.

The dust finally settled.

Rosetta stood far behind Angela, suddenly cupped her mouth, she couldn’t believe what she was seeing.

Clark and Leo stood side by side, about ten plus meters away from the epicentre of the explosion, their pupils suddenly shrank.

As the smoke finally cleared where Garen stood, a several meters wide crater was revealed, and in the middle of it, was an unscathed Garen.

He had somehow evaded the primary area of effect of the explosions, and everything else didn’t have any effect on him.

"After this fight, I will challenge Palosa," Garen’s last word fell, and suddenly disappeared.

At the same time, a shadow appeared in front of Clark. With a loud "Ka Cha!", the sword in Clark’s hand was sliced into pieces, turning into many pieces of red speckles.

With a loud bang, a massive green and black hand penetrated through the broken pieces and pressed its palm on Clark’s forehead.

"No!!! I do not want to die!!! I DO NOT WANT TO DIE!!!" Clark’s face turned into a stroke of madness, the scars on his body suddenly started glowing. What was originally a thin shade of beige skin was suddenly filled with blood, and his veins glowed like he had been tattooed with blood.

In the split second before Clark’s skull was about to be smashed into pieces, he suddenly mustered a terrifying amount of counter strength and released himself from the grasp of Garen, his forehead now sliced open slightly by the nails of Garen’s palm.

Resisting a flurry of pain from his head, Clark flipped over skillfully, ready to escape.

Bang!!

He was hit by a palm technique, and spat out blood, the force sent him flying over the walls, his thoughts filled with fear of Garen. He didn’t even think twice and started running away as soon as he landed, disappearing into the night.

He was dead for sure.

Garen slowly pulled his right palm back, he was still being shot at by two machine guns and held back by the attacks of the Killer Hunters and Leo.

The seemingly endless rain of bullets on Garen’s body kept lighting up spark after spark, everyone felt chills as they watched Garen casually ignore the gunshots and begin to turn his attention to Leo and the Killer Hunters.

Upon seeing Clark’s cowardly retreat, Leo and the Killer Hunters wanted to run too, but they were so pulled in by Garen’s aura of courage that they simply couldn’t stop attacking. They knew that if they stopped, they would be killed within a split second.

They weren’t Grandmasters of Combat like Clark, and did not have terrifying amounts of explosive energy or durability.

All the attackers were starting to panic, members of the Behemoth Gate held back their fears as they remembered their strict training; members of the Black Mark Association however, were mostly convicts, they couldn’t stand the pressure that came with the fear, some of them started abandoning the mission.

Two of the heavy machine guns were operated by a total of four people. The ones responsible for feeding the chains, their hands were shivering out of fear. The ones responsible for aiming couldn’t even hold the gun still, most of the bullets started straying and hit the wall behind Garen instead.

King of Fist Leo and the Killer Hunters watched as Garen came closer, their foreheads, arms, their entire bodies started cold sweating. Some of the stray bullets flew past Garen’s face, leaving small cuts on his face as he walked.

The guns suddenly stopped, the two Killer Hunters saw Garen about to get close to them, suddenly exploded into a ball of fire.

They simply lit the gunpowder they were carrying on them, killing themselves.

At this moment, Garen was still a few metres away from the epicentre of the explosion.

"They….couldn’t take the pressure, and chose to kill themselves…."

Sky Warrior Corbella said, with sorrow and disappointment.

The surrounding houses around the courtyard were now on fire, the light of that fire glowed on Garen’s face, giving him a demonic look with a reddish shadow.

He stood before the fire, and turned to look at King of Fist Leo.

The gunshots had also stopped by now.

Leo stared powerlessly at Garen’s silhouette, he was shaking all over in fear, with a loud thump, he suddenly kneeled on the floor.

The fire continued to burn around them, making occasional crackles as the wood burned.

"It is finished..."

Corbella looked at that silhouette before the fire, his heart was suddenly filled with motivation, his body pumped up with adrenaline.

"After this battle, you are without competition!" He suddenly remembered the days of Palosa.

He suddenly felt like he had just witnessed history.

"He will become the next Saint of Fist Techniques," Corbella said, as he watched King of Fist Leo kneel before Garen.

Garen lifted up his head and looked at the night sky, as if he had just understood something.

Behind the fire, small policeman Jia Ning stood stunned, an unprecedented thirst rose from his heart.

Chapter 165: Follow Up 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few days later...

Stars filled the infinite sky, Garen had never felt more at awe looking up.

"Ever since that battle, you’ve seem to have gained an interest in looking at the stars, what’s so special?"

The Eighth Hoop donned a black cloak as he emerged from a corner of the courtyard. His face was the usual pale and aged, but the way he looked at Garen was complex.

"Specialty?" Garen smiled,"it just makes me feel minute that’s all."

The two of them were standing in a rural courtyard, it had beautiful plants and flowers growing all over it, the mixed colours making it extremely eye catching.

"Minute... Since the fight the other day, you’ve been recognised as the number one fighter of the Southern Secret Martial Arts world. You’re only second to Palosha now, and yet you still think you’re minute? What should other people think of themselves then?," The Eighth Hoop sighed.

"Any plans after this?"

"How’re the few leftover men?" Garen asked back.

"Still alright, just a little shocked, I got a few psychiatrists to check on them, the psychiatrists all agree that they went through too much stress and are shell shocked. Oh also, they would like to meet you."

"Meet me?" Garen smiled, ever since the day that he unlocked a new dimension of observation, he’s been able to clearly see and feel the flow and control of energy along his body, it’s as if he was now fully in control, and able to maximise his agility to a unprecedented level of accuracy and efficiency.

Just like right now, he can even sense the heartbeat of The Eighth Hoop who was standing a few meters away from him, he could hear every beat of his heart.

If a mere mortal were to focus all of his energy, he would conjure what would then be known as ‘focus’, but he would only be able to focus on one point at one time. In fact a mortal would feel tired very quickly after focusing for a while. Only after recouping his blood flow, would he be able to resume.

As for Garen now, his conscience, Qi, and spirit were all one now, energy flowed endlessly from his body, and his breaths were steady and strong. His ability to observe and focus on his surroundings was as if a mortal was focusing all of its attention on one thing, except that for him it was for many things.

Everything within a five metre radius of him was in total clarity.

"Why do they want to see me?"

Thinking back on that day, these were the people who surrendered and let Garen take them away without any resistance.

Rosetta, Behemoth Gate’s Angela, and the Black Mark Association’s King of Fist Leo, then there were some leftover members of both sects, totalling 54 individuals.

Over half of them had undergone too much shock, mostly by Garen’s aura, had seem to develop hallucinations and PTSD, and were being sent to a nearby mental hospital. The remainders quietly stayed in jail, their mental defenses completely crumbled since that day.

"I don’t know, they seem to have been both physically and mentally destroyed by you. No matter what it is, once they hear that you’re involved, they’ll play along and abide by it. In other words, you have completely defeated them," the Eighth Hoop said,"looks like it was right when I recommended you to join the Golden Hoop."

"Black Mark Association and the Behemoth Gate should still be active right?" Garen asked softly.

"Of course, but on the grand scale of national security, they aren’t much of a threat. Black Mark and Behemoth Gate’s strength lies in individual operatives, their macro influence on the Confederation is nowhere close to us at the Golden Hoop. What the Golden Hoop lacks are independent operatives. Now that we have you, we are complete!" The Eighth Loop laughed,"we don’t need to give a damn about them anymore."

Garen understood this as the Eighth Loop expressing his alliance with him, they too were interested in the total annihilation of the Black Mark Association and Behemoth’s Gate.

These two sects were not a force to be easily reckoned with, it was obvious that the Golden Hoop was placing a lot of faith in Garen.

"Oh right, what about Clark?" Garen suddenly remembered the palm technique he had landed on that Grandmaster from the Crimson Sand Sword sect.

"We just found his corpse, we came over to inform you about that. Would you like to go take a look?"

"Of course."

Garen followed the Eighth Hoop into the house, and onwards into a study room on the side. In the floor of the study room was a basement entrance.

The both of them walked inside in a single file, the walls were filled with bright electric lights.

Every short distance there would be two black uniformed soldiers on guard.

Each time the both of them passed a pair of guards, they would be greeted with formal salutes.

Garen quietly followed the Eighth Loop further downwards. The corridor seemed to be endless.

Very soon the both turned into a white room.

There were already two coroners inside the room who greeted them with salutes as soon as they entered.

"How's it going?"

One of the female coroners took off her blue gloves, pulled back a strand of hair and said,

"Before the individual died, his metabolism entered into an overstimulation of sorts. Not sure how or why, but sir you should see for yourself."

The Eighth Hoop walked closer to the cadaver.

Clark lied flat face up on a white high table. His lower body was covered by a white cloth, only his upper body was exposed. From his chest down to his lower abdomen there was a Y shaped cut.

The Eighth Hoop put on gloves, lifted the white cloth and took a quick sweeping look, then lifted his head to gesture Garen to come over.

"Come see for yourself."

Garen took the gloves from the coroner and walked over.

Clark’s body laid silently on the table, his whole body wasn't a pale white like a typical corpse, but somehow was glowing red like it had been cooked well done.

Garen touched Clark’s forehead softly, his eyebrows scrunched up.

"He was hit by my Red Jade Palm’s Hot Poison, his entire body overheated, this condition of death is normal, except..."

"Except what?"

"Someone tried to save him, in fact that someone was a skilled fighter."

"Oh?"

The Eighth Hoop was suddenly intrigued, "what level of a fighter?"

"Quite strong, but it doesn't matter, the moment Clark left that courtyard his fate was sealed," Garen’s face was an unusual peaceful.

"Red Jade Palm, pfft, you've practically boiled his blood and cooked him," the Eighth Hoop was incredibly impressed.

The two coroners stood in disbelief like they had just heard some crazy mystic talk.

"Sir you believe that there are methods to control someone's internal hormones and body temperature? This is absolutely illogical!" The female coroner looked at the both of them shocked, like she was staring at aliens.

"This person was obviously cooked by some high temperature weapon. My suggestion is that we collect samples from his body and cells to understand further. We must break this down from a scientific point of view!"

The Eighth Hoop and Garen did not know how to explain to someone who wasn't a member of the martial arts community.

Secret Martial Arts like this, is practically godspeak to laymen.

"This bastard’s belongings had all been stolen somehow. If we were able to get to that we might've been able to find some useful intelligence," the Eighth Hoop said disappointingly.

"Let's go, to where Third Brother is," Garen turned around and headed outwards. Joshuahad come with him earlier, except that before the action happened he refused to let him participate, in fact he deliberately kept him out of intelligence briefings so he wouldn't be informed until everything was over.

Of course Joshua was pissed off about it, but he understood that Garen did so for his own good. As soon as he caught up, he had been here looking after Rosetta and gang.

Leaving the morgue, the both of them washed their hands and headed further down the corridor.

Not long after, they came by the prison cells.

On both sides of were several prison cells, some empty and some with mortals locked inside.

The walls were filled with burn marks, and the ground was quite dirty, one could even find small traces of blood stains here and there. The prison guards each holstered a pistol while holding a baton in their hands as they patrolled the perimeter.

The corridor along the prison was very long, the both of them went straight for the end, as the warden quickly tried to catch up to them while explaining the situation here.

"Most of the inmates here came in the last few days. The ones that you specially ordered to give attention to, we’ve pierced their scapulae and put on the strongest chains we have on them. They won't be a problem!"

He said as he ran, his hands fumbling a huge chain of keys, standing by to open any door for the two leaders. As a small leader in the Golden Hoop, he had an eye for small details. Especially since this time the leader Eighth Hoop had brought this young man who didn't wear any golden loops to signify his position, and yet every time he passed a prison cell filled with mobsters and loud troublemakers, they would all shut up in his presence. For sure this young man was a big shot!

"We arrange the inmates by their abilities and how much of a great they pose to society. The deeper they're placed, the more dangerous they are," the warden explained carefully.

"We want to go to the deepest part of your supermax," the Eighth Hoop said plainly.

"Yes yes yes!"

The warden quickly bent over a door near them and took out his keys to point and instruct the prison guards to open the multiple metal gates before them.

Garen followed the group and entered the end of the prison.

The stench of blood was now stronger than ever, as more metal gates opened, the space in the prison widened, as well as the thickness of the metal bars.

Within the cells in this area, some inmates hid in a corner. One of them had bloodshot eyes and looked ridiculously skinny, but emitted an aura of death and violence about him.

Now and then a whistle would echo through the cells.

"Little Jack? Did you bring us fresh meat to sell butt again? Man it isn't easy at all~~," a man with long messy hair in a cell on the left laughed sinisterly.

"Wow you brought us some really fresh meat this time. This little one looks like he just turned twenty," a big bearded inmate stood up and took off his pants facing the visitors, ready to pee right there.

Boom!!

Garen’s shit an angry glare, he turned and grabbed one of the thicker-than-an-arm metal bars with his python like left hand.

Ka cha!

The metal bar broke and flew into the cell, hitting the inmate on the chest, stabbing him through the chest and sending him pinned to the wall behind.

The inmate couldn't even make another sound, and died instantly.

Everyone shut up at sight of that. Like terrified animals they all retreated into the shadow of their cells. Even some of the commotion from cells further down also silenced immediately.

Garen pulled his left hand back, just now that cell’s metal bar had been vibrated till it broke by him earlier, causing the entire metal door for this isolation cell to come loose too.

"Continue."

"Yes...yes yes," the warden unknowingly distanced himself from Garen, and walked closer to the Eighth Hoop instead. After seeing what had happened, he could feel goosebumps and cold sweat all over.

"That's too insane, too insane!" He chanted to himself as he continued leading the way. Occasionally he would steal a look at Garen to study his expressions, in case he did anything to cross him.

Chapter 166: Follow Up 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Eighth Loop intentionally lagged in the back, he took a quick look at the broken metal bars. While his face was expressionless, but his eyes expressed a bit of wary and fear.

He had heard of how Garen fought and won against a massive group once, but he has never seen it in person before so he never really felt the impact, but now, he could really feel goosebumps.

Now, he was personally there, and really close to the moment Garen killed someone.

The way Garen killed someone was like squashing an ant, an air of death and murder surrounded Garen.

This speed! This strength! The Eighth Loop now knew why the Behemoth’s Gate and Black Mark Association fell under his hand.

Against someone like Garen, one could only feel threatened and unsafe around him, if Garen were to expense his full arsenal, one could not even imagine what would ensue after.

Garen continued walking silently behind the warden. He could feel that despite the fact that his strength had not made significant advances, his speed had increased significantly, in turn this increased his explosive abilities, and the high speed also brought terrifying impacts. He had not implemented any secret abilities, just the mere increase of speed and strength, the metal bar gave and killed the prisoner.

"Unknowingly, I have improved to this level," He felt the cold, solid ground under him and smelled the scent of blood in the air. Very soon, Rosetta’s silhouette appeared on the right up front.

A group of people stood in attention by Rosetta’s cell. Joshua was guarding the cell, and he sat on a chair by the entrance. Once he saw Garen arrive, he slowly got up.

"Garen, you came," Joshua looked incredibly tired, like he had lost a whole lot of weight, his eye-bags were a dark black. Obviously he had not been resting for the past few days.

"Go rest, third brother," Garen said,"you’re just torturing yourself like this."

Joshua looked at Rosetta in the cell, and nodded.

"Go ahead an interrogate her then, she won’t say anything."

"Leave her to me," Garen nodded.

Garen turned around and said something to the Eighth Loop, then the latter left.

The Eighth Loop knew Garen wanted a private interrogation, and so he knowingly distanced himself and went to inspect the other parts of the prison.

The warden too, moved all of his minions away, himself included, he did not want to spend another minute close to Garen anymore, what happened earlier was enough to reinforce his fear for good.

Very quickly, the corridor was emptied, except for the inmates in their respective cells, there was only Rosetta and Garen left.

Rosetta still wore her black cloak, and was sitting cross-legged on the floor. Her brown long ponytail sat beneath her head, her face was peaceful, her eyes expressionless.

"Where’s second brother?" Garen looked at her and said,"tell me you have news about Farak."

"Farak?" Rosetta slowly lifted her head, blankly said,"if I tell you, will you promise to not kill me?" Her voice had an angry undertone.

Garen looked at her, and didn’t say a thing.

Rosetta smiled bitterly,

"I never thought I would see the day where I regretted the things I did. Farak…..he’s dead."

Garen stared at her, although he saw this coming, but hearing the news from the horse’s mouth, he still felt a little sad.

Farak was one of the most important guides and influences when Garen was still training his basics, he constantly pointed out and corrected Garen’s errors during training. Farak was one of those people who looked dangerous, but was actually warm and easygoing.

"How did he die?"

Rosetta smiled, "When I left White Cloud Gate, Farak caught up to me, and we fought for over thirty rounds, until I slashed his throat with my claw."

"What about the elder?"

"Dead too, I wanted to look for something in the archives. That old bastard actually had the gall to stop me! He was asking for death with his "wise-old-man" stunts, so I killed him with one palm technique," Rosetta explained casually.

Suddenly she lifted up her head, and made a sad smile.

"When it all ends, the victor becomes the king, and the losers vilified. I always knew someone was going to come after me, I just never thought it would be you."

"Is there anything else you would like to say?" Garen said plainly.

"So this is how fear feels like…" Rosetta lowered her head and continued laughing in sadness and desperation. Her body shivered as she said,"What do you plan to do to me?"

"According to the rules of our sect," Garen turned to leave with those words.

As he was walking, he could hear Rosetta humming.

"The boat shakes, and shakes….the water’s green, and green….you are here by my side….standing by the lotus leaves…"

That voice, that song, it was nostalgic, it made Garen think of Farak.

"You really liked Farak didn’t you?"

The singing stopped, Rosetta sat upright silently, and suddenly her whole body fell to the ground. In the darkness, sounds of her choking echoed through the cells.

Garen closed his eyes, his heart rippling with emotion.

He didn’t want to dwell on his thoughts anymore, and took big steps towards the exit.

Perhaps Rosetta regretted. Perhaps she regretted joining Behemoth’s Gate in pursuit of more powerful forms of martial art, regretted killing Farak and the elder, and regretted betraying her own sect family. Between her and Farak existed many stories that nobody will ever know, along with their deaths, these stories will flow away with time.

Garen didn’t inquire about it, and would not inquire about it.

His master passed away due to an extended coma that caused his body to be unable to take in anymore nutrients. His last wish, was for Garen to kill Rosetta.

He didn’t cite any reason, and Garen didn’t want to ask too much. Whatever it is, this situation has concluded. Perhaps someday in the future he might follow the seas eastward and find the roots of White Cloud Gate. But for now, everything was over.

"There are a lot of contradictions in life, that child did the wrong this, so she paid the price for it."

On the left side, in a solitary cell, a white haired old man spoke,

"Take it easy kid," the old man’s eyes seemed to reflect some sort of helplessness, perhaps Rosetta’s singing stirred up memories in him too.

"Who are you?" Garen stopped and turned to look at this man.

"I’m just an old man waiting to die. This is the Golden Hoop’s prison, and also the prison of the Confederation’s most wanted criminals." the old man responded.

"I’ll remember you," Garen could feel that this old man was not simple. Although he looked friendly at first glance, he was surrounded by an aura of death and murder. Garen took note of the cell’s number: 12.

Leaving the area, he continued walking forward. There were absolutely no guards in this part, even the bravest guards were afraid of this section. Two days ago the Eighth Loop had introduced this place to Garen, it had some terrifying inmates, some could even kill with a simple spit. Many of them have been locked up in here for god knows how long by the Confederation that they’ve become old men themselves. All of them had been convicted of some heinous crime so terrible that even if they were to die a dozen times over it still wouldn’t be enough. For that reason, they’ve stayed here all the time, as the guards and wardens changed generations after generations, these old prisoners continued to stubbornly stay alive.

Garen found Black Mark Association’s Leo at the Number 10 cell. Behemoth Gate’s Angela was locked up in a nearby cell as well. They were locked up here not because of their abilities, but because of how important they were.

The both of them were cuffed with massive black cuffs, as they saw Garen arrive, they both looked up from their seated positions at him.

"Garen Lombard! If it is possible, I wish to serve you!" King of Fist Leo seemed to be passionate towards Garen as a person,"In search of the pinnacle of Fist Skills, I killed my first man when I was only 15, by the time I turned 20 I had already killed a thousand! For the sake of finding more powerful secret martial arts, I joined the Black Mark Association! For the sake of more resources, I became the bond between Black Mark Association and Behemoth’s Gate! Yet despite all of that, I have gained nothing! Until today!"

He suddenly stood up, his metal cuffs making loud clangs.

"I am unsatisfied with just demonstrations of martial arts! I want to prove that martial arts too can fight firearms!! Now, this is possible, I have seen the light in you!!"

"What do you really want to say?" Garen frowned.

"I want to follow you!" Leo said passionately, his cuffed hands moving about,"you are destined to become a historical figure in the world of martial arts!! The direction you’re headed to has been my lifelong dream!"

"You madman!" Behemoth’s Gate’s Angela cursed,"why don’t you think about how Black Mark Association and Behemoth’s Gate is going to come after you instead?!"

Garen never would’ve thought that Fist King Leo was actually someone like this, this guy was obviously one of those people driven by the singular passion of finding purer and stronger forms of martial arts. These people have always existed in the martial arts world, although they’re just a small group, they’re very traditional and would give anything to achieve the pinnacle of martial arts mastery. Looks like Leo was one of these people.

But Garen still wanted to observe for a while, to see if Leo was truly sincere in his words of surrender and following. Should someone as powerful as Leo truly serve him and White Cloud Gate, it’ll be no small help. Afterall, a man such as him was at the peak of physical conditioning.

Settled on his thought, he turned to look at Angela.

"Why….why...why are you looking at me? I don’t know much about Behemoth’s Gate, we’re not members of the higher echelon, and only members of the higher ups are given access to information about other members. The organization is arranged in independent cells, each cell has no idea what the other cell is doing."

Angela seemed to shrink, and took a few steps backwards, obviously there was still fear from what she saw Garen do the other day.

"Then what use are you to me?" Garen frowned.

"I….I….I too can serve you! Serve the White Cloud Gate!" Angela phrased it in such a way that she would serve Garen first as an individual, then only White Cloud Gate.

Influence was just a means of getting resources and intelligence to Garen, he was more interested in improving himself, elevating his abilities, and becoming better at martial arts. Everything else, was secondary to him.

"What else?"

"There’s still more?!" Angela was a smart girl, she quickly analyzed Garen’s personality and intentions, so she thought a while and suddenly said,"I have news about the Blood of Eternal Life!!"

"Blood of Eternal Life?"

"Word is that after the Blood of Eternal Life flowed from the hands from Duskdune Shura, some parts of it was taken by the Poker Organization, the other part was taken by our people," Angela studied Garen’s expression carefully upon saying this, afraid she might lose her only lifeline.

"Taken by your people?" Garen was visibly shocked.

"Yes, some of the lower level people sent it to our middle level operatives, that’s why the leaders from the upper level wanted to get the brewing technique from you."

"Where is that part then?" Garen was lazy to talk bullshit with her.

"In somewhere secret," Angela hesitated.

Chapter 167: Follow Up 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Yes, it’s just part of it." Angela nodded.

"It’s unfortunate that I have no use for it." Garen regretted. "Do you have any information regarding the function of the Blood of Eternal Life?

"Now that one’s much easier; it’s widely known," Angela paused to align the relevant information before continuing, "Each Blood of Eternal Life has different functions. In fact, all of them come from non-humans."

"Non-humans?" This was the first time Garen had heard of the term.

"That’s right. Most of the non-humans have life spans that far surpass humans, and the special ones are called the Everlasting Beings. The most extreme fighters among us have interested in these non-human race’s long lifespans, as they’ve come to realize that they don’t have enough time to achieve the extreme edges of martial arts.

Angela exhaled and continued calmly, owing to Garen’s increasing interest in the topic.

"Hence, some of our top talents from the human race started investigating ways of attaining a lifespan equal to these Everlasting Beings. The two main methods were hybridization and food consumption, both of which are also the most effective methods. Hybridization is by far the best, as one could obtain a stronger blood lineage and offspring through copulation. This slowly begins to form some of the ethnic groups we see in certain countries. On the other hand, strong individuals like to increase their lifespan through edible consumption. After the Great Draught a millennia ago, which was the worst drought we’ve had, a lot of the Everlasting Beings left the land and went into the ocean. They took a boat and wandered the seas for decades. Humans are completely incapable of sailing the seas in the same way.

Naturally, their conflict with the humans gradually dissipated. "

"So the Blood of Eternal Life was something they left behind?" Garen asked.

"Yes. Due to the sparsity of these Everlasting Beings, you can only find a small amount of Blood of Eternal Life from some of the remains. But then again, these have already been contaminated by the ancient humans who consumed them into their bloodstream. Although the blood has been contaminated, its ability to lengthen one’s lifespan still remains." Angela explained.

"Since the Everlasting Beings left just a thousand years ago, there should still be human descendants who possessed the Blood of Eternal Life besides the corpses right? If they really have such a long lifespan, it should be just a few generations to them for the past millennia." Vampires and werewolves were the first thing Garen thought of when he heard the word Everlasting Beings. These mysterious creatures were known everywhere and became legends on Earth. The legendary vampire was said to be forever young and immortal. This gave earthlings a very strong impression.

"It is true that there are descendants from the Everlasting Beings. However, they hide themselves within the human world and it would be difficult to trace them unless they transformed, or use a specially made soul detector."

"There are detectors for them?"

"Li Gaode, the academician of the Champagne Empire’s Science Academy invented a detector called the boiling blood. It’s very expensive to manufacture and we, the Behemoth Gate could only buy two sets. It’s very impractical as well due to its high electricity consumption."

The Champagne Empire was one of the three large empires in the Azure Continent, currently in a minor conflict with the Republic of the Tulip. The Champagne Empire was once a well developed country with a deep background. They were not afraid to go up against three dominating empires.

Garen understood well since he had learnt the world’s geography.

"Furthermore, there are a lot of types of Blood of Eternal Life." Angela added on as she glanced at Garen.

"Types?"

"Other than increasing one’s lifespan, they can give humans different talents." Angela observed Garen’s expression closely as she explained. She found out that Garen was genuinely surprised as if it was his first time hearing such a common knowledge. This shook her assumption of Garen being a mixed between an Everlasting Being and human.

"What species are you guys mixed with?"

"We are mixed with the white dog’s bloodline. Once you have absorbed the bloodline, you can live for a maximum of 300 years and about two hundred years on average, which is about 145 years of increased lifespan. You can live for more than two hundred years if you incorporate a series of Essence Locking Techniques."

"White Dog Man…" Garen was said aimlessly, as he had lost interest after hearing such a bloodline. With the talent he possessed, there was no need for him to obtain such a thing. He had reached the utmost limits of a human being before the age of 20. There was no rush for him to pursue such a thing as he still had at least seventy to eighty years to explore his options.

"What about the origins of the telekinesis from the Immortal Palace?" He asked a question that he had been very curious about.

"The Immortal Palace represents the bloodline of the Everlasting Beings. They are the last remaining organization which consists mainly of tainted half-breeds, so it is common for them to have special abilities. Furthermore, the majority of those humans, including those tainted half-breeds, would do whatever it took to kill the Everlasting Beings and obtain the Blood of Eternal Life. Once the tainted half-breeds were revealed, they would be in an unimaginable state, like becoming a experiment subject or a blood slave. Flamingo and Sylphalan, the powerhouses of the Immortal Palace, are prime examples. Both of them are tainted half-breeds, and their family members were mercilessly murdered. They have an insatiable hatred towards human kind."

She stopped for a while and continued.

"The Immortal Palace consists of five people in total. Now that Duskdune Shura has left due to his severe injury, there are only four left. All of them have their own secret organizations under them. Flamingo and Sylphalan have revealed their identities to the public, and we also know that Ghette, the general of Weisman, is one of them as well. Unfortunately, the last member is still in the dark."

Garen stroked his chin as he processed the information he had obtained in his mind. He recalled Celine stating that the Immortal Palace initially had five members and there are currently four as one of them had left the group. This matched the information Angela had given.

"Alright, what is the Behemoth Gate’s motive? You used Rosetta to lure me here so that Clark and the Killer Hunters Squad may attempt to murder me. What do you want?" Garen finally brought the issue up.

"I think you know why. We are after the Blood of Eternal Life that you are hiding." Angela confessed.

"Unfortunately, I am not a carrier of the Blood of Eternal Life." Garen shrugged. "There are a lot of humans with strong talents too. It’s not just the tainted half-breeds."

"No one will believe that." Angela helplessly smiled.

"This can be proven by using the detecting device, right?" Garen needlessly explained.

Angela’s eyes were wide open as she couldn’t believe what she heard.

"Why are you staring at me? I am born from a normal family. I don’t have any Blood of Eternal Life. All of this information can be obtained with some research." Garen explained.

Garen didn’t stay long since he had obtained enough information. He went back to the study room through another prison tunnel.

The eighth Golden Hoop was already sitting inside the room serving himself drinks from the pot of hot coffee on the table in front of him.

When he saw Garen, he silently took out a roll of dark red paper from his arms, and used a white porcelain cup to hold it down, placing it on the table..

Garen sat in front of the eight Golden Hoop, taking the cup and open the roll of paper.

‘Nominating NO.9 as Province Galantia’s regional director. Granting authority to mobilize all stationed military within the province.’ With a stamping at the back, ‘Golden Hoop Headquarters’

Garen understood intention of the piece of paper in his grasp.

"Is this prepared specially for me?"

"Yes." The eight Golden Hoop replied. "The upper management needs to evaluate your performance. If you can finish a small, specific task, you will have the authority to secretly mobilize the military of this province. Galantia’s chief commander and most of the commanders are our people."

Garen understood that the Golden Hoop wanted him to continue staying in the organization as his value had increased. It is also probably that they wanted him to depend on the organization’s power. Judging from the looks of it, it was so powerful that influencing the country leaders was no problem.

No. It might be the opposite, where the country leaders were planning to use him through the Golden Hoop. It was definitely a possibility.

"What do you want me to do with such authority?" Garen asked as he put down the paper.

"Just to clean up some trouble for the government." the eighth Golden Hoop smiled. "Although this is equivalent to hiring a mercenary, we won’t mobilize you most of the time. It would considered remarkable to receive a task once in a few years."

"I need something solid. I do not want these vague answers." Garen knew that with his strength, he could not live a good life even without the Federation’s support. Hence he didn’t oppose such headhunting.

"How about a mission once every three years?" The eighth Golden Hoop had obviously reached an agreement with the upper management. "The success rate of the mission must be at least fifty percent and the government will supply you the necessary monetary resources."

"Fine." Garen wasn’t stingy at all. It was preferential treatment to him as the best among the grandmasters of combat, to have a mission only once every three years.

Firearms, which were once a threat to him were no longer so, due to his rapid growth.

It showed that the government was experienced in these affairs, based on their arrangements. They were able to protect the country when needed, by gathering enough power from the citizens even with regulations this loose. It was similar to an arrangement of hiring bounty hunters.

Garen, who was seated well, poured himself a cup of coffee and surmised his recent lifestyle.

From studying sincerely in Huaishan City to finding the Antique of Tragedy. He initially thought that he could study in a university and find a job after graduation while slowly climbing up to the top of the martial arts world with his talent. It was unfortunate that things had changed so quickly.

He had unknowingly made a name for himself by helping Su Lin with his troubles since he had owed Su Lin two favors. He was also made known in the time the Immortal Palace invaded, and the changes to his master’s dojo.

He had reached the highest level in the martial art world in a very short amount of time.

Now that he had taken over the White Cloud Gate, he had become an important person in the eyes of the government, as he was also in a powerful organization in the martial arts world.

Garen felt surreal recalling these events. Practically speaking, he hasn’t even reached 19 yet, he was barely 18.

Chapter 168: Follow Up 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Oh by the way, what happened to that small policeman who was catching up from behind?" Garen recalled the incidents one at a time from his memories, and thought of the small policeman, Jia Ning who came rushing back. According to the Sky Warrior Corbella, this small policeman was a righteous young man who was trying to help him escape the ambush. However, it hadn’t occurred to him that Garen was able to deal with the Behemoth Gate and Black Mark association single-handedly.

"No idea. I think he’s still at the Crimson Sand Sword."

Garen nodded. He admired such a grateful person.

As he collected his thoughts, the eighth Golden Hoop had already arranged an airplane to Harmony City.

Not far away from Harmony City was Wei Maen City, which was also where the headquarters of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate was located. The fastest way to Wei Maen City was to go from the Skylark Mountain Range, nearby the city.

It was also the secret hideout of White Bird Holy Fist Palosa.

The two of them were engaged in further discourse; the eighth Golden Hoop was asking advice on techniques in practicing secret martial arts. Garen truthfully answered as much as he knew.

Most of his experience and techniques were taught by his master and acquired from his physical exercise. Although he had not plan his training to be as as detailed as some other fighters, he was knowledgeable in some training that could injure muscles in the body.

These were the riches of every fighter that would never be enough.

The next morning, the gate master of the Crimson Sand Sword brought along two of his disciples and the small policeman Jia Ning to a visit.

Just as they sat down, Corbella of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate came with two of his disciples as well.

The courtyard was densely surrounded by the Men in Black. They were all special forces mobilized by the Golden Hoop. The two of them were hints to Garen’s background.

Inside the white spacious living room.

The Crimson sand Sword Gate sat on a white sofa on the left, whereas the people from the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate sat on the sofa on the right. In the middle were Garen and the eighth Golden Hoop.

The morning rays seeped in from the entrance and formed golden enigmas shaped onto the ground, brightly reflected by the white floor tiles and lighting up the whole living room.

As everyone sat down, Garen glanced and observed both parties.

On the left, the gate master of the Crimson Sand Sword Gate and two of his disciples carried a weary look. They obviously had not recovered from the incident a few days ago. The small policeman Jia Ning was looking at him helplessly as if he was lost in thought.

On the right, the Sky Warrior Corbella noticed Garen’s eyes upon him and politely smiled back.

He had brought two of his very similar looking disciples along, one male and the other female, who looked like they were in their thirties. Not only did they look like twins, they also seemed to possess good demeanor. On hindsight, these two were skeptical of Garen as they greeted him. They obviously could not believe that Garen, who was supposedly about the same age as their son could have achieved the top of the martial arts world.

"And what might be the reason for this visitation?" Garen questioned them directly.

"Gate Master Garen, we the Crimson Sand Sword are here today because of your help a few days ago. The Crimson Sand Sword Gate could have been destroyed if you had not reached out." He glanced at his beautiful disciples.

Although this disciple looked like she was below 15 years old, she already had an developed figure. With a full cheongsam-like uniform and a short skirt on her body with a brown ponytail hairstyle, she walked towards Garen and passed him a white bank cheque with both of her hands.

"Please accept this as our thanks Gate Master Garen." The girl smiled sweetly with her big eyes. Her skin was flawless like a porcelain doll even when viewed from such a close distance.

She obeyed his father’s arrangement and passed Garen the cheque on her own accord. This allowed her to showcase her pure and charming seduction. Garen looked vigorous and imposing as he sat firmly in the middle of the living room. He was like an aggressive beast in the living room, pressuring others with power and influence. Anyone who entered his presence would feel a strange feeling of oppression.

This was not the cause of spirit but the effect of his reputation. Like a commoner meeting someone with authority, psychological pressure is not uncommon. .

"If I could seduce him, perhaps we can put this man onto the Crimson Sand Sword’s Chariot, and the success rate of father’s plan would increase tremendously." The idea kept churning inside the girl’s mind.

Although she knew that Beo had a crush on her, it was an incomparable difference between the man currently in front of her. She was a girl with extreme greed. After being appointed as a navigator by her father, she started recruiting potential fighters into the Gate. This visit was most probably suggested by her as well.

The girl smiled sweetly again as dimples appeared on her cheeks.

The cheque had ten million dollars in Federation currency presented by a pure, beautiful and seductive young woman.

Any hot blooded young fighter would not be able to resist.

Since fighters were all hot blooded, this meant that their body would produce more endocrine. Naturally, their natural desire would amplify tremendously as well.

Unfortunately, Garen didn’t give her a second look after glancing at her.

"I don’t need the cheque. To me, money is as of no significance. If you really want to thank me, please allow me to enter your secret martial arts treasury and read on some non-core based secret martial arts."

"Studying secret martial arts?" The Crimson Sand Sword Gate Master was stunned. Then he smiled. "I see. You’d need these since the White Cloud Gate Master had already reached such a level. We will naturally comply but please understand that we will not show you any high class secret martial arts related to the Crimson Sand Sword. However, the others are fine." As he was afraid of any misunderstanding from Garen, he continued after pausing a while. "Don’t worry, There are at least fifty types of middle range secret martial arts."

"Thank you,. Mr..." Garen thought for a while and realized that he did not know his name yet.

"Call me Luther."

"Thank you, Gate Master." Luther

Both of them smiled in satisfaction as they looked at each other.

"It’s our turn to talk since both of you have finished chatting." The Sky Warrior Corbella voiced out as he sat at the sofa that could only fit one person.

"Please do, Sky Warrior Corbella." Garen focused his attention onto him after he waved his hand to dismiss the girl.

Corbella introduced both of his disciples.

"These two are from our headquarters. Under the Gate Master’s instruction, we would like to invite Gate Master Garen to our headquarters to meet the Gate Master."

Both of the youngsters were wearing a white suit. The man with mustache stood up and bowed slightly towards Garen.

"Dear respected Gate Master Garen, we have come to greet you with the utmost respect in place of the Gate Master. The Gate Master is very happy that there is a new grandmaster of combat in the martial art world. Unfortunately, due to the immense workload he is currently facing, he is unable to visit you in the flesh. If Gate Master Garen could pay him a visit personally..."

Paying a visit to each other’s place was a common social practice to indicate that the respective Gates were of the same level. The Gate Master of the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate had obviously positioned Garen of the White Cloud Gate as the same social standing as him.

Once Garen visits him, the opposite party must welcome him in an extravagant manner.

"I appreciate the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate Master’s attention. I will definitely pay a visit very soon. Please do not worry." Garen had already planned to visit the Southern Sky Holy Fist Gate so it was natural for him to do so, since the opposite party had shown more than enough respect.

Both of them bowed once more before they sat back down.

Sky Warrior Corbella had finished his most important task.

"Please voice out freely if Gate Master Garen had any more request. Corbella has some connections in the southern area."

"I shall thank you in advance, Sky Warrior Corbella."

"Then I will await your visit soon." Corbella nodded. He already knew that Garen planned to challenge White Bird Holy Fist. He planned to find a few good spots in the Skylark Mountain Range for this high level duel. He had also invited a few good friends to spectate the duel as well as it was a battle that no fighter would wish to miss.

He couldn’t help but to look at Garen once more as he thought about it.

He recalled that inhumane battle that night. Clark, who was many times stronger than him was beaten like he was a rubbish bag. He had clearly been broken by Garen as he hadn’t even dared to turn around and insult Garen as he escaped.

How much difference in battle power could cause such a result?

Was the martial art world going to rise to its prime again?

Garen and Andrela, who were both geniuses appeared in the same generation.

Corbella’s mind churned.

Garen didn’t know what Corbella was thinking, and started with both parties on the topic of the status of the martial art world. He then had a general knowing of the martial artists around the world.

In the martial art world, those who were below the grandmasters of combat were extremely weak against firearms. Any slightly trained gunner could pose a great threat towards the fighters, much less go against them head on.

Only the people who were the grandmasters of combat could go square ahead with firearms. Since they were different from the lower ranks, the government of each country has different attitudes towards the grandmasters of combat.

The Federation’s view towards them wasn’t too serious, but they did not take them lightly either. A grandmaster of combat was just one man after all. They could kill him instantly with specially made ammunition, from a few kilometers away with a special firearm.

On the other hand, Weisman respected the grandmasters of combat. However, they did not have many information regarding them as they had the least number of them. Most of the grandmasters of combat were from the east, as all of them were mostly influenced by ancient martial arts. Most of the ships from the east made landfall at the Yalu Confederation, as the Weisman Kingdom was too far away. Geographical location was a major factor.

As for Galantia, the majority of their martial arts were bred locally. There, martial arts based on ancient weapons were advocated, with a variety of styles and types due to the sizeable amount of grandmasters of combat they inhabited. However, it was not similar to the east.

"The position of being a grandmaster of combat is gaining momentum internationally. It may be because technology is getting more advanced and there are less foundations as time goes on. As a result, people who practice martial arts become few and far between. Most people view martial arts as a form of sports that helps them train their bodies." Corbella sighed. "Although our positions are getting more and more important, the quantity of the new generation of the grandmaster of combat is much lower when compared to previous ones. For the past decade, there have been less than five grandmaster of combat that are from the new generation. Same goes for the North."

"There’s less than ten in total?" Garen frowned. The martial art world was in a worse state than he had previously thought. "This means that there are only two more people who became a grandmaster of combat in the southern region, excluding myself; Andrela and Beo?"

Chapter 169: Consultation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"That seems to be the case. Although the Celestial Circle Gate and the Crimson Sand Sword have been training a few potential candidates that could become Grandmasters of Combat, there are too little of them that might actually manage to become one." Corbella nodded with confidence.

"If this keeps up, both the public and the secret martial arts worlds would become dimmer and dimmer." Gate Master Luther of the Crimson Sand Sword nodded as he frowned.

"Don’t the governments that value them not raise ones themselves?" Garen asked curiously.

"They don’t have what it takes to raise one." Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword smile wryly. "A Grandmaster of Combat requires huge amount of herbal resources to provide nutrients and enhance the body. It takes a long time to train them as well. Excluding talented ones like you, a Grandmaster of Combat normally requires to train the secret martial arts since young for at least a decade before they qualify to become a Grandmaster of Combat."

"The problem lies in the qualification itself. The success rate is too low. It would be considered impressive if one out of a hundred candidates qualify as a Grandmaster of Combat." Corbella continued. "A low success rate combined with the long duration required to nurture them to reach the utmost limits of a human being. Only the crazy ones are daring enough to try and train their bodies for that. Furthermore, they would need to maintain the training for long periods of time as well to prevent the body from regressing. In short, producing one is extremely difficult.

"That’s true. A country can nurture a few sharpshooters within the time and resources required to nurture one Grandmaster of Combat. Furthermore, sharpshooters pose more threat on the battlefield. All three of us here would be helpless if we go up against a canon, right?" The Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword sighed.

The atmosphere in the living room had started to stale up.

"The technology of missiles and the power of firearms are getting stronger and stronger. This means that an individual’s effectiveness diminishes as the day goes by. Each country’s military armor and air force are exceedingly powerful. The current role of a Grandmaster of Combat is mainly protection and assassination. This is one of the main reasons why The federation does not value the Grandmasters of Combat as much." Luther explained.

Garen nodded in agreement.

It’s true that even if he had already mastered the body hardening technique, he would still be injured if he go against a person with firearms. If it were to be other Grandmaster of Combat, they would be torn in half in no time.

However, he felt that this was because the countries were not aware of the value the importance of special operations yet. Once special operations similar to that of Earth’s were in motion, the importance of having a Grandmaster of Combat would be obvious.

"Let’s not talk about this. The military has already arranged an airplane and I will leave two days later. " Garen looked at the Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword.

The Gate Master was skeptical. "Looks like you’re here purely to gather information?"

"Yes. There’s no problem, I assume?"

"Of course."

On the other side, Corbella stood up and said: "Then we shall pardon ourselves."

"See you."

Garen sat as he looked at Corbella and his two disciples leave. After that, he chatted with the Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword for a while and went to their headquarters.

They embarked with a convoy of well guarded red carriages as they left the courtyard of the headquarters that he visited a few days ago.

The house located in the middle of the courtyard was charred black, and most of the place was in a mess. The houses which were on the left looked fine, however.

"This way." The Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword lead Garen into the the left side area of the courtyard and passed through a few houses, reaching another small courtyard again.

This courtyard had a small garden, a false mountain pool and a huge locust tree. The courtyard was densely packed with trees and shades.

Garen followed behind the Gate Master and saw the same row of houses and a small courtyard across from the pool. He saw servants walking to and fro carrying water and a used bandages.

The Gate Master smiled and explained as he saw Garen’s gaze, "Beo lives in that courtyard. He is still resting as he was heavily injured from the mission given by the Federation’s government."

"Is that so?" Garen replied.

Both of them kept walking passing through the small courtyard and reached a small remote house.

There were two old women sitting in front of the red-brown door, facing each other. Each of them were holding a book on their hand as they muttered gloomily.

Both of them stood up as they saw the Gate Master approaching them.

"Is he here?"

"He’s here. Please open the door." The Gate Master of the Crimson Sand Sword nodded his head.

They proceeded to swing open the wooden door.

After giving some simple precautionary instructions, Gate Master Luther left the place alone.

The door was then closed, leaving Garen alone inside the house.

The room had the same rectangular reddish brown, wooden floor.

A row of bookshelves was placed by the wall opposite the door. There was a spiral staircase on the right side of the bookshelf that lead to the second floor of the house.

There was a table and chair in front of the bookshelf, with a stone carving of a big black man on it.

The statue was a man with curled hair, wearing a black coat. He wore a stern facial expression and seemed to be in a walking position with a book in his hand.

Garen walked passed the statue and stood in front of the bookshelf.

There were a total of four bookshelves and the books were categorized properly.

They were categorized into experience, practice, methods and low grade secret martial arts.

The bookshelf was sparse; most of them were strewn this way and that. At most, there were about ten to twenty books per bookshelf.

Garen went directly towards the low grade secret martial arts category and ignored the first three.

The secret martial arts bookshelf was once again sub-categorized into physical movement, palm method, kicking method, finger method and weaponries.

Among them, books related to the weaponries were the most abundant, amounting to about seven to eight books. Garen picked them up and glanced through them.

Kris Dagger Technique, The Sword of Glory, Twin Sword Art, Trio Sword Art, Double Handed Sword, Single Handed Sword, Heavy Sword.

He glanced through all of them. As they were all low grade secret martial arts, they did not require high physical attribution. Now that he had maxed out his physical attribution and reached the utmost limit of a human being, he effortlessly memorized everything on the book by giving them a cursory glance.

While he did not need it now, that didn’t mean he won’t be needing it in the future. These secret martial arts were at the most, third rated, which was on par with the Iron Body and the Boulder martial arts.

After scanning through the weaponry secret martial arts, he set his gaze upon the physical movement category.

He gently brushed over the physical movement column with his finger.

Seasnake Walk, Greenwood Impact, Raid, Stella Assassination Step.

There were only these few books. Garen picked them up and flipped them open. Although most of the training methods made use of special techniques that require a sudden release in muscle and qi, they did not mention the methods in making up what it lacked. They were just very strong techniques with great power and Garen found most of them overbearing.

"These styles were all very different. Is this the secret techniques of the Galantia that I hear about?" He memorized all of them.

He took only a few minutes to memorize one whole book.

The important ones were the Palm Method and Finger Method.

However they were not a lot of them.

Finger Method: Wicked Claw, Double Finger Method.

Palm Method: Hundred Compound Palm, Javier Punch.

These were not so helpful towards Garen. However he could learn from the different training methods and perhaps he could gain some useful effects.

He walked up to the second floor as there was nothing interesting on the first floor.

There was only one bookshelf on the second floor. Similarly, there were only ten plus books scattered about.

However, Garen’s eye was burned with excitement as he laid his eyes upon them.

Most of the secret martial arts books on this bookshelf were much more suited for him.

He simply picked out a book called the Lion King Fist. It was a secret martial art that hardens the user’s fist, which suits his fighting style. It was rumored that it could enhance one’s self-confidence through exercise. It would be very helpful in changing a person’s personality. It was considered as one of the Magic Fist Art.

He memorized the Lion King Fist down in detail and continued looking for more.

Boulder martial arts, Iron Body and Firestream Fist could be seen on the bookshelf too.

Garen took out all the secret martial artss that he had yet to know and placed them on the second floor’s table.

Speed Shifting Palm, Bronze Statue Technique, Steel Statue Technique, Gold Statue Technique, Hodman’s Gun Jabbing Fist, Ember Claw.

There were a total of six secret technique books that Garen had never seen before, and they were all complete sets. They were all second rated or third rated secret techniques, which were the same grade as the Mammoth Secret Technique and beyond.

The Crimson Sand Sword seemed to not keep anything other than techniques with complete sets.

Garen then reread the secret techniques such as the Firestream Fist that he already knew to see if there was anything different from what he knew. After that, he memorized the remaining six new secret techniques.

Bronze Statue Technique, Steel Statue Technique and Gold Statue Technique was obtained by the Crimson Sand Sword by eliminating body hardening factions. It was obvious that they had prepared this for Garen since they hadn’t taken them away.

Although these three techniques were strong, their differences in power were not that far apart. However, there was one crucial factor.

Although the three levels, namely Bronze, Silver and Gold were not much of a difference to an outsider, there was a difference between the users. The Steel Statue users could restrain the Bronze Statue users and the Gold Statue users could restrain the Steel Statue users easily.

This was an obvious way to form a hierarchy within the Gate.

The Speed Shifting Palm Technique could be use to increase the agility of the palm techniques, which could be considered as a small secret technique regime.

On the other hand, the Hodman’s Gun Jabbing Fist was a secret technique with a powerful force. It was a palm technique derived by a fighting form mimicking the gun. It could produce at least three times the power of a commoner.

However, Hodman, who had invented this technique died before reaching forty due to this technique. Whoever practiced this technique had either died of young or possessed huge prowess. There were no exceptions.

The age of the users when they passed away was recorded in the book. None of them died from disease.

"This could be used to train sacrificial pawn." Garen memorized this secret technique as well.

The last one was Ember Claw.

It was a simple secret technique that trained both hands. Although it was able to increase the temperature of both hands to very high temperatures, its power was average. It was invented by a mediocre Grandmaster of Combat who wanted to improve himself in his late forties. However, he died from the fire he created..

As Garen was reading the secret technique, he was tempted. He closed his eyes and looked at his attribute pane after memorizing the whole thing.

Strength 2.66. Agility 2.72. Vitality 2.65. Intelligence 2.53. Potential 626%.

Secret Technique ----

Mammotth Variation: Explosive (Max Level), Epidermal Hardening Grade 1 (Iron Body), Blood Qi Stabilization Grade 1 (Boulder martial arts).

Red Jade Palm: rudimentary level (Grade 1), Burning Strengthen Level 1 (Dark Crimson Technique), Vitality Enhancement Level 1 (Dark Crimson Technique)’

"Another point from Potential." Garen smiled in satisfaction. "The Golden Sword Throne is indeed a good item. It was worth my time to take the risk and obtain it. It’s good to be able to obtain one potential point per week."

Chapter 170: Consultation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He had six potential points. In terms of secret techniques, the lower grade, middle grade and upper grade required 1 point, 2 points and 5 points respectively. The difference could increase the level of the secret techniques. Naturally, this was under the assumption that the user had the prerequisite needed to learn it.

After some consideration, Garen decided to learn the Ember Claw in hope that it would merge with the Red Jade Palm.

He finally understood that the merging of secret techniques was connected to his technique’s level.

This was the case for his Mammoth Secret Technique, as it acted as a foundation which most of his techniques were merged with and became an enhancement, as it had the highest level.

This meant that whichever technique had the higher level would become the foundation for the other techniques. Perhaps the grade of the techniques would affect it but it was not important.

He could learn two secret techniques up to the middle level with six points.

At the second floor of the house, Garen raised both of his hands and followed the instruction to learn the Ember Claw. With minimum movement, he kept changing his posture with his palm’s joints. Combined with the flow of his qi, he placed both of his hands on the lit kerosene lamp and moved back and forth above the fire.

The scorching fire burnt Garen’s skin.

Both of his hand’s skin was completely covered in burns after ten minutes or so. Garen’s hands started to go numb, and at the same time, a clear feeling flowed into his palms from his brain and it felt like his hands were completely different.

"I’ve learnt it!"

He quickly looked at the skill pane.

‘Red Jade Palm: Preliminary Level (Grade 1), Burning Strengthen Level 1 (Dark Crimson Technique), Vitality Enhancement Level 1 (Dark Crimson Technique), Enhanced Ember Claw Level 1’

He focused his view onto the Ember Claw and the related information popped up out of thin air.

"Ember Claw has increases the fire resistance of the arms and the strength resistance under normal enhancement. Able to produce high temperature injuries."

Garen softly explained to himself

He looked at the 6 attribute points and thought:

"I don’t think I can increase the grade of the Red Jade Palm. Celine is a cunning fellow, she would have definitely noticed my irregularity. I should increase the rest of my techniques first."

He hesitated for a while, but his vision ultimately fell onto Ember Claw.

As he focused his vision on the skill, the attribute points immediately decreased by three.

Hence, the Ember Claw was no longer an enhancement effect and became an independent secret technique. On the other hand, the Red Jade Palm and the remaining secret techniques merged into Ember Claw.

‘Ember Claw: Grade 2 (Total of 4). Red Jade Palm Enhancement Level 1. Dark Crimson Technique Enhancement Level 1 (Vitality Enhancement, Burning Strengthen)’

There was a indent on the back of the skill.

"Quantity of similar Secret Techniques have exceeded by three; conflicts among the training regimes. Do you want Ember Claw to cover the Firestream Fist and a part of the Red Jade Palm?"

A conflict among the training regimes?

Garen was stunned. Naturally, it was possible that there would be conflicts in training regimes among the secret techniques.

"Cover."

As he just made his decision, the Dark Crimson Technique immediately disappeared in the skill pane and what was left was the higher tier second rated secret technique Ember Claw.

All of the sudden, the bunch of enhancement effect was simplified in the skill pane.

‘Ember Claw: Grade 2 (Total of 4). Burning Strengthen Level 1 (Total of 3, from the Dark Crimson Technique and Red Jade Palm’s training regime

"Since my body has reached its limit, I can only use the attribution points to increase my skills. Ember Claw would be the best choice, since it is the most all rounded and its tier is greater than the Mammoth Secret Technique." Garen directly focused his attention onto the Ember Claw.

Next up was the Golden Statue Technique.

This body hardening technique was easy to learn as it only required Garen to apply the golden oil on his body, which was a specially made butter. However, he didn’t meet the condition.

Garen had no choice but to note it down in his head and bring it up another time.

He then memorized all the information in the treasury once more to make sure of the information.

It was already afternoon when he came out of the secret techniques treasury.

There were two disciples waiting for him outside the door.

"Have you finished reading, Gate Master Garen?"

"Almost done. Thank you." Garen nodded. "Please thank Gate Master Luther for me."

He didn’t speak much to the people from Crimson Sand Sword afterwards and walked directly out of the place. A black car from the Golden Hoop had been waiting for him.

He had cleared up the relationship between the Crimson Sand Sword and him. He even paid a visit to Beo, who was bedridden and covered in bandages, before finally boarding the plane.

*********************

Huaishan City Public Cemetery, at the suburbs

It was cloudy with a slight drizzle as the dark clouds covered the sky.

There were a group of people standing in front of a white tomb, deep in the cemetery.

Garen and Joshua stood in front of the tombstone. Behind him were Cynthia, jack and the fat Bouvini. All of them were in black; the men were in suits and the girls in skirts.

The area was surrounded by the men in black.

A woman in a black dress, who was escorted by two soldiers, stood behind the crowd.

"What do you plan to do?" Cynthia looked at Garen.

"According to the rules of the sects, traitors or murderers of the disciples shall be subject to capital punishment." Garen replied calmly.

Garen felt troubled as he turned around and looked at Rosetta, who was being escorted.

The capital punishment for every sects was brutal and cruel. Although it wasn’t used often, Garen felt that it was the appropriate time to use it…

"You should know the capital punishment of the White Cloud Gate." Garen showed no expression.

"Let ants bite the person after peeling off one’s skin and douse the body with honey water." Cynthia barely nodded her head. "But Rosetta is…"

"I know." Garen closed his eyes. "I know she is already dead."

Rosetta was motionless at the back as she was being held by two subordinates of the Golden Hoop.

She had already committed suicide after Garen left prison. What was brought here was merely a corpse.

"Do it. I was generous enough to let her commit suicide." Garen didn’t waver at all.

The subordinates sent by the Golden Hoop were experts in capital punishment; both females.

They swiftly took off Rosetta’s shirt and cut open a small wound using a scalpel, slowly peeling off her skin.

Soon, the white, naked female had her skin stripped and what was left was red, stiff muscle. They immediately threw her onto the tomb after the pouring water all over her body.

Another person poured a bag of black ant’s nest onto her.

The black ants swiftly covered the whole corpse’s surface.

Everyone on the scene felt like they were on a cold war as they saw their senior disciple’s red flesh being covered up by the black ants.

A cold drizzle poured incessantly on the crowd. Garen stood still in front of the tomb, taking out a black woodring and stroking it gently. The emblem of the Golden Hoop had been shifted to his left ear lobe.

He felt a soothing feeling of peace that he had never felt before, as he looked at the ants devouring Rosetta.

A few black crows were attracted by the corpse. They landed onto the corpse and started to biting out big chunks of flesh, ignoring the onlooking crowd beside them.

Garen and the others ignored the crows as well.

Now that the incident with his senior disciple had been dealt with, Garen and Cynthia were the only disciples left from the older generation, as the elder and second senior disciple had passed away. The rest of the members were rookies. If he wanted to challenge the white Bird Holy Fist, now was the time…

***************

After coming back from the cemetery, Garen sat alone in the hall of the White Cloud Gate’s main dojo. The surrounding was covered in darkness, as the faint moonlight filtered in from the window and landed on the slightly broken floor.

He didn’t know when it had started, but he started to enjoy sitting alone and letting his thoughts run wild after that night’s battle. He realized that he could easily linking a lot of things together after maxing out his intelligence. He had also gained a tremendous amount of knowledge in martial arts.

"Master, are you there?" Simon’s voice came from the entrance of the staircase but there seemed to be someone else as well, judging from the sound of the footsteps.

"Please come up if you have anything to say."Garen replied as he opened his eyes.

Soon, footsteps of multiple people came from the staircase. Simon brought along a gentle and calm handsome man, where Corinne brought along a cool and beautiful woman to see him.

Corinne and Simon were the disciples of Garen’s ex-subordinate, and they were not related at all. However, they chose to stay and not give up during the White Cloud Gate’s darkest times. Hence, Garen decided to make them his disciples and teach them martial arts with all his knowledge.

At this stage, both of them were very strong in terms of martial arts. They were at the same level as Cynthia after training for a long time; the level of the Tenstar Ni from the Celestial Circle Gate and the Crimson Sand Sword.

They played a major role in reviving the White Cloud Gate. With the addition of Garen becoming a Grandmaster of Combat, they had a clearer understanding of the body’s qi and all of the results of this effect.

In addition, both of them were continuously consuming the body quenching pill that Garen once had when he was mastering his secret techniques. This meant that their physical quality was above average, which was the main cause of of their big improvement.

"Yes?" Garen looked at his audience. Simon and Corinne were both wearing their black tight practice uniforms, whereas their partners behind them wore white silk practice uniforms. They had an exceptionally respectful demeanor towards Garen.

"Master, we have brought our disciples to greet you." Simon replied carefully because Garen who was sitting in front of him was like a beast in the dark. He was giving off a sense of oppression just by sitting there.

Unlike last time, it was still easy to talk to him due to his casual personality. However, Garen changed into another person ever since he had beat up the Behemoth Gate.

"These two are your disciples?" Garen was stunned. He had heard it from both of them last time, but hadn’t asked about it in detail. They had finally met each other.

"Hello Grand Master." Both of the youngsters greeted Garen at the same time. they looked elegant, even though they were about fourteen or fifteen years old.

"Karina is Bouvini’s niece." Corinne explained as the girl quickly lowered her head and paid her due respect respect to Garen.

"Yuan Reese is the second successor of the Di Youwen Household." Simon quickly introduced him to Garen as well.